<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cyber Sluttery on Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/tag/cyber-sluttery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cyber Sluttery on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 10:58:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/tag/cyber-sluttery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wide World Of Sex Apps</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/17/the-wide-world-of-sex-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 10:58:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/17/the-wide-world-of-sex-apps/</guid>
      <description>The Wide Wild World of Sex Aps Caution: The following post deals with frank talk about sex prudes need not proceed.
Beloved Stumpers:
Let’s say you’ve read my background posts, done some thinking, had a talk with your partner (if you have one) and maybe you’ve explored fantasy literature and even got yourself a copy of the Ethical Slut, and now you’re feeling ready for the next step, you want to get out there and explore the world of kink and group sex hookups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valentines Day For Dummies</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/11/valentines-day-for-dummies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 10:48:02 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/11/valentines-day-for-dummies/</guid>
      <description>Valentines Day For Dummies Dearest Stumpers:
If I wish one thing for you all this Valentine’s Day it is for you all to achieve sexual satisfaction be it alone, or with a partner. Valentine’s Day is perhaps the most awkward day of the calendar year and the sexual revolution hasn’t done it any favors. Presently, the prevailing winds indicate that it is a day for children to trade heart themed and punny pre-made notes, for teenagers to run around confused and for adults to express their affection through themed gifting or feel lonely if they are single.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Consent</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/01/cyber-consent/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 10:20:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/01/cyber-consent/</guid>
      <description>Cyber Consent Dear Stumpers:
It’s time to have a little talk about cyber boundaries and cyber consent. This isn’t going to be one of my friendly Mom talks. Because many of you are not being very nice. If I have done it right, you will all feel sufficiently chastised before reaching the end of this article.
For a few weeks now, I have been ruminating on all of the talk about dick picks and cyber whores and good girls and bad girls and sluts and fuckbois, on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex For Every Body</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/29/sex-for-every-body/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 14:34:34 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/29/sex-for-every-body/</guid>
      <description>Stumpers:
For those of you that follow me on twitter or catch up with me on guest blogs, or have even read my full catalogue you may be aware that I am going through a bit of a personal health crisis right now. I have badly injured my lower back. You all know I write about sex but none have you been brave enough to ask. What has the impact of your lower back injury been on your sex life?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Massively Multiplayer</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/15/massively-multiplayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 10:28:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/15/massively-multiplayer/</guid>
      <description>Massively Multiplayer If you’ve been keeping up with #cyberslut, you may have intimated that I have been a little bit adventurous, in recent years, when it comes to my sex life. I have had some experiences in group sex, tried out fantasy scenarios and visited specialty clubs and the like. I also enjoy a robust fantasy talk relationship with my main partner which has been going strong for 3 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owning Sex</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/08/owning-sex/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 10:05:49 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/08/owning-sex/</guid>
      <description>Owning Sex Dear Stumpers:
This past week, I received my first feedback from a self described, lifestyle kinkster, about the #cyberslut. I admit, I went out on a limb and inserted myself into their conversation, hoping to reach out to new audiences and expand my reach. This feedback described some of my assertions as inaccurate fundamentally wrong. I asked them to share resources on the topics but they did not respond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Fantasy Talk</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/01/advanced-fantasy-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/01/advanced-fantasy-talk/</guid>
      <description>Advanced Fantasy Talk Dear Stumpers:
Two entries ago I promised to get into some more advanced fantasy tips and I am nothing if not a woman of my word. These are my more advanced tips for a slightly kinkier level of fantasy play. I claim zero expertise in kink; for that you’re going to have to go to different corners of the internet but those corners can be scary and intimidating, even if they really are actually filled with regular people who just happen to enjoy novel sexual if experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dabling in Kink</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/17/dabling-in-kink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 19:43:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/17/dabling-in-kink/</guid>
      <description>Dabling in Kink Dear Stumpers:
Are you frustrated with mainstream sex advice? Do you find the world fo kink frightening or inaccessible? I don’t blame you if you do. I do too, but I have dabbled enough in the virtual world of kink to get a handle on the basics. I have noticed that mainstream sex advice couples to, “explore role play” if they are bored and stops there. Which really isn’t fair, it is a deep subject when many nuances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginning Fantasy Talk</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/11/beginning-fantasy-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:06:13 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/11/beginning-fantasy-talk/</guid>
      <description>Beginning Fantasy Talk Dear Stumpers:
I’ve been inspired by other bloggers to talk about the things I really enjoy. And one of my favorite sources of entertainment is sex and fantasy talk. If twitter is any indication there is a lot of stigma around cyberesex, sexting and fantasy talk and that’s reason enough to talk at length about it. I do so love pissing twitter prudes off.
Credentials: I haven’t gone to school for sex therapy or been in the sex industry in any way or anything like that but what I have been doing is talking dirty with people online since 1999.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Path of the Cyberslut</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/04/the-path-of-the-cyberslut/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/04/the-path-of-the-cyberslut/</guid>
      <description>The Path of the Cyberslut Dear Stumpers,
Following my separation which occurred under such specifically scandalous circumstances that it would completely compromise my anonymity if I were to recount it, I went through a period of complete and reckless internet chatting and dating abandon. In my younger days and with my ex-I had dabbled in cybsex, sexting and a radical 90’s trend called phone sex. But in this stretch of newly found adult independence I decided to dive headlong into the most idiosyncratic corners of the online dating scene.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>