<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cyber Sluttery on Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/tag/cyber-sluttery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cyber Sluttery on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 19:43:22 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/tag/cyber-sluttery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dabling in Kink</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/17/dabling-in-kink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 19:43:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/17/dabling-in-kink/</guid>
      <description>Dabling in Kink Dear Stumpers:
Are you frustrated with mainstream sex advice? Do you find the world fo kink frightening or inaccessible? I don’t blame you if you do. I do too, but I have dabbled enough in the virtual world of kink to get a handle on the basics. I have noticed that mainstream sex advice couples to, “explore role play” if they are bored and stops there. Which really isn’t fair, it is a deep subject when many nuances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginning Fantasy Talk</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/11/beginning-fantasy-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:06:13 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/11/beginning-fantasy-talk/</guid>
      <description>Beginning Fantasy Talk Dear Stumpers:
I’ve been inspired by other bloggers to talk about the things I really enjoy. And one of my favorite sources of entertainment is sex and fantasy talk. If twitter is any indication there is a lot of stigma around cyberesex, sexting and fantasy talk and that’s reason enough to talk at length about it. I do so love pissing twitter prudes off.
Credentials: I haven’t gone to school for sex therapy or been in the sex industry in any way or anything like that but what I have been doing is talking dirty with people online since 1999.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Path of the Cyberslut</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/04/the-path-of-the-cyberslut/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/04/the-path-of-the-cyberslut/</guid>
      <description>The Path of the Cyberslut Dear Stumpers,
Following my separation which occurred under such specifically scandalous circumstances that it would completely compromise my anonymity if I were to recount it, I went through a period of complete and reckless internet chatting and dating abandon. In my younger days and with my ex-I had dabbled in cybsex, sexting and a radical 90’s trend called phone sex. But in this stretch of newly found adult independence I decided to dive headlong into the most idiosyncratic corners of the online dating scene.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>