<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 19:44:45 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Creeper</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/07/my-first-creeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 19:44:45 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/07/my-first-creeper/</guid>
      <description>My First Creeper Dear Stumpers:
I’m about to let you in behind the scenes of StumpedMom.com. While the casual or even careful reader could never be blamed for assuming I pull this entire website out of my ass. I try to organize my ideas and put them out in an organized and orderly fashion. I use an Airtable (Please sponsor me) spreadsheet to organize my work from the idea stage, through to publishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monday Mom Hacks Infant Stytle</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/04/monday-mom-hacks-infant-stytle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 10:55:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/04/monday-mom-hacks-infant-stytle/</guid>
      <description>Monday Mom Hacks Infant style:
If I am committed to anything here at StumpedMom.com it is learning things the hard way so you don’t have to. If you have young children or are anticipating the arrival of a new baby you’re going to be bombarded with advice. Some of it helpful-some of it pushy and unnecessary. I’m not here to sell you a product, just to entertain you and hopefully make your life a little better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Consent</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/01/cyber-consent/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 10:20:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/01/cyber-consent/</guid>
      <description>Cyber Consent Dear Stumpers:
It’s time to have a little talk about cyber boundaries and cyber consent. This isn’t going to be one of my friendly Mom talks. Because many of you are not being very nice. If I have done it right, you will all feel sufficiently chastised before reaching the end of this article.
For a few weeks now, I have been ruminating on all of the talk about dick picks and cyber whores and good girls and bad girls and sluts and fuckbois, on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex For Every Body</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/29/sex-for-every-body/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 14:34:34 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/29/sex-for-every-body/</guid>
      <description>Stumpers:
For those of you that follow me on twitter or catch up with me on guest blogs, or have even read my full catalogue you may be aware that I am going through a bit of a personal health crisis right now. I have badly injured my lower back. You all know I write about sex but none have you been brave enough to ask. What has the impact of your lower back injury been on your sex life?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind Over Matter</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/23/mind-over-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 19:49:15 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/23/mind-over-matter/</guid>
      <description>Mind over Matter
Dear stumpers:
I can’t tell you how excited I am to have been invited to do my first guest post. When Christina G. invited me to post on her site I was incredibly excited and flattered. She is literally one of five other bloggers out there I consistently enjoy reading. If you’re a stumper you owe it to yourself to check her out.
Mind Over Matter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Segregation</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/20/supermarket-segregation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 10:32:10 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/20/supermarket-segregation/</guid>
      <description>Supermarket Segregation Dear Stumpers:
There is segregation going on right under our noses in a place you depend on and likely bring your children. It is Supermarket segregation and it’s happening in grocery chains that have invested heavily in cultivating progressive images and niche markets. This isn’t an overt kind of Jim Crow segregation, where specific people are banned from employment or shopping at the stores. This segregation is a coded message written in product grouping, placement and signage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Massively Multiplayer</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/15/massively-multiplayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 10:28:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/15/massively-multiplayer/</guid>
      <description>Massively Multiplayer If you’ve been keeping up with #cyberslut, you may have intimated that I have been a little bit adventurous, in recent years, when it comes to my sex life. I have had some experiences in group sex, tried out fantasy scenarios and visited specialty clubs and the like. I also enjoy a robust fantasy talk relationship with my main partner which has been going strong for 3 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Dysfunctional Ways to Avoid a bad Boss</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/09/10-dysfunctional-ways-to-avoid-a-bad-boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 20:46:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/09/10-dysfunctional-ways-to-avoid-a-bad-boss/</guid>
      <description>10 Dysfunctional Ways to Avoid a bad Boss If you’re looking for advice on how to be an efficient part of the capitalist machine the American news media and the internet have you covered. Forbes, the Wall Street Journal and LinkedIn supply a steady stream of content designed to help you be a compliant and striving little worker bee. I haven’t seen any metrics but these pieces wouldn’t proliferate so freely if they weren’t popular and therefore profitable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owning Sex</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/08/owning-sex/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 10:05:49 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/08/owning-sex/</guid>
      <description>Owning Sex Dear Stumpers:
This past week, I received my first feedback from a self described, lifestyle kinkster, about the #cyberslut. I admit, I went out on a limb and inserted myself into their conversation, hoping to reach out to new audiences and expand my reach. This feedback described some of my assertions as inaccurate fundamentally wrong. I asked them to share resources on the topics but they did not respond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Struggle With Ableism</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/03/my-struggle-with-ableism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/03/my-struggle-with-ableism/</guid>
      <description>My Struggle With Ableism About two years ago while I was stuck working night shift for a few weeks, I got really into the Harvard Implicit Bias test project. The tests ask you to react quickly to a series of images and is designed to measure your unconscious bias towards groups. I felt super great about myself when I took my first test and found out I was biased in favor darker skinned people and against lighter skinned people (an outlier result for a white woman).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Fantasy Talk</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/01/advanced-fantasy-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/01/advanced-fantasy-talk/</guid>
      <description>Advanced Fantasy Talk Dear Stumpers:
Two entries ago I promised to get into some more advanced fantasy tips and I am nothing if not a woman of my word. These are my more advanced tips for a slightly kinkier level of fantasy play. I claim zero expertise in kink; for that you’re going to have to go to different corners of the internet but those corners can be scary and intimidating, even if they really are actually filled with regular people who just happen to enjoy novel sexual if experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Purge</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/20/the-purge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/20/the-purge/</guid>
      <description>The Purge Welcome Stumpers,
to the good vibes only zone. Come along with me on a journey to awesomeness while improving your life, your mind, your body and your soul with a thorough and complete cleansing. Now is the time to rid ourselves of negativity in our lives. You don’t need negative people or influencers pulling you down with them. If they don’t affirm you and all of your most ardent desires, or make your sandwiches and give you orgasms, flatter your taste and intelligence, block them, delete them, ignore them and feel free to abandon with abandon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dabling in Kink</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/17/dabling-in-kink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 19:43:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/17/dabling-in-kink/</guid>
      <description>Dabling in Kink Dear Stumpers:
Are you frustrated with mainstream sex advice? Do you find the world fo kink frightening or inaccessible? I don’t blame you if you do. I do too, but I have dabbled enough in the virtual world of kink to get a handle on the basics. I have noticed that mainstream sex advice couples to, “explore role play” if they are bored and stops there. Which really isn’t fair, it is a deep subject when many nuances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Brain</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/13/twitter-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 08:30:27 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/13/twitter-brain/</guid>
      <description>Twitter Brain Twitter Brain; Noun:
 The condition resulting from excessive attention to Twitter characterized by intense effort toward building your personal brand and attracting new followers. A person who thinks too much about their Twitter following.  Example: Stump Mom’s writing and research and overall attention were suffering because she had Twitter Brain.
I have recently come to terms with a reality that much America has been living with or some time - It doesn’t take much to come down with a case of Twitter Brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginning Fantasy Talk</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/11/beginning-fantasy-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:06:13 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/11/beginning-fantasy-talk/</guid>
      <description>Beginning Fantasy Talk Dear Stumpers:
I’ve been inspired by other bloggers to talk about the things I really enjoy. And one of my favorite sources of entertainment is sex and fantasy talk. If twitter is any indication there is a lot of stigma around cyberesex, sexting and fantasy talk and that’s reason enough to talk at length about it. I do so love pissing twitter prudes off.
Credentials: I haven’t gone to school for sex therapy or been in the sex industry in any way or anything like that but what I have been doing is talking dirty with people online since 1999.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whiteclaiming</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/06/whiteclaiming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/06/whiteclaiming/</guid>
      <description>Dear Fellow White People,
The time has come for us to stop Whiteclaiming. The time has come for us to stop feigning in aspects of the cultures of non-white people by virtue of proximity. For the sake of brevity I am dubbing this phenomenon whiteclaiming. Whiteclamining occurs when a white person claims specific special understanding of something they associate with an ethnic group based on who they know or where they are from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Path of the Cyberslut</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/04/the-path-of-the-cyberslut/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/04/the-path-of-the-cyberslut/</guid>
      <description>The Path of the Cyberslut Dear Stumpers,
Following my separation which occurred under such specifically scandalous circumstances that it would completely compromise my anonymity if I were to recount it, I went through a period of complete and reckless internet chatting and dating abandon. In my younger days and with my ex-I had dabbled in cybsex, sexting and a radical 90’s trend called phone sex. But in this stretch of newly found adult independence I decided to dive headlong into the most idiosyncratic corners of the online dating scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Best Teacher Holiday Gifts</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/29/5-best-teacher-holiday-gifts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/29/5-best-teacher-holiday-gifts/</guid>
      <description>5 Best Teacher Holiday Gifts Dear Stumpers:
I expect you saw right through my veiled attempt at click bait and you are not expecting to see a straightforward list of suggestions for teacher gifts. I’m not going try to trick you. It is my opinion that purchasing gifts for school teachers is a socially corrosive and ethically corrupt trend. I can’t blame you for looking for suggestions, especially if you have a kinder or first grader just starting school and you just found out the other parents have been gifting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Replace Your Husband with Amazon Prime</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/26/replace-your-husband-with-amazon-prime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 13:16:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/26/replace-your-husband-with-amazon-prime/</guid>
      <description>Replace Your Husband with Amazon Prime Dearest Stumpers,
(Do you mind if I call you Dearest? I feel like we’re getting so much closer these days)
I hope that one of the things I can accomplish through sharing is to show that I have learned the hard way so that you don’t have to. My divorce struck like a sudden car wreck, the causes of which were multiplicitous. Explaining it all might take going into the sort of exacting excavation and slow revelation that might make you feel like you were being made to watch Roger Stone’s JFK and I am not a lazy, sophomore American History teacher, so I am not going to waste four hours of your time trying to convince you of a version of events, when there is no ready path toward rectification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrooge Shaming</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/22/scrooge-shaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/22/scrooge-shaming/</guid>
      <description>The Casual Cruelty of Scrooge Shaming Proceed with care and self directed compassion.This post deals with trauma triggers surrounding the loss of a child.
Dear Stumpers:
The clock has struck! Tis Thanksgiving and America has officially plunged into a six week, long commercially fueled onslaught of seasonal Christmas themed celebration, commonly known as the Holiday Season. An army of Christmas enthusiasts enabled by naked commercial interest go to work and transform virtually all public, commercial and private spaces (save those of the non Christian religions) to conform to their concept of winter festiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>