<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Monthly Mindfulness</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/08/22/monthly-mindfulness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/08/22/monthly-mindfulness/</guid>
      <description>Monthly Mindfulness Religion is the opium of the people. It is the sigh of the oppressed creature, the heart of a heartless world, and the soul of our soulless conditions.-Karl Marx
“Monthly Mindfulness Zoom session starts in 10 minutes,” Chimed the automated google calendar alert.
“I should go,” I thought. But why did it feel like such a drag? My therapist wants me to do at least 20 minutes of mindfulness practice every day, this counts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secret Husbands, Lost Jobs and Dead Alter Egos</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/08/15/secret-husbands-lost-jobs-and-dead-alter-egos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/08/15/secret-husbands-lost-jobs-and-dead-alter-egos/</guid>
      <description>Secret Husbands, Lost Jobs and Dead Alter Egos Dear Stumpers:
Today’s Advisory: This post is rated H for heavy; contains themes of real death, real loss, real life and real consequences.
My beloved grandmother had a secret first husband. While she was in the blossom of her youth, (some-time between 1939 and 1942), she ran away from her home in Oregon eloped and moved to Chicago. He abused her, she called home for help, and her brothers went out the midwest to retrieve her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret Lives of Barbies</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/06/21/the-secret-lives-of-barbies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 11:55:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/06/21/the-secret-lives-of-barbies/</guid>
      <description>The Secret Lives of Barbies The first rule about Barbies is that you don’t talk about Barbies
My peak imaginative play years were dominated by play with Mattel’s Barbie brand plastic dolls. The rooms that I shared with my older sister and then later, with my younger sister were inundated with an overwhelming the flotsam of Mattel parts, and accessories. My mother organized them into mini rubbermaid dressers and organizers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Words</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/05/24/words/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 12:18:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/05/24/words/</guid>
      <description>Words Dear Bloggers:
Today I come write to you in the spirit of rebellion as I declare my unbridled desire to experience the English language at its fullest.
Last week my dear friend Will Qualls (@WKQualls) sent out a tweet asking about how important grammar and convention is to bloggers. Will has a special talent for getting people thinking and my thoughts on this topic can’t be contained to the limitations of twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hand and Foot</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/05/21/hand-and-foot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/05/21/hand-and-foot/</guid>
      <description>Caution: this post deals with violence toward women
Hand and Foot Dear Stumpers:
I’m narcissistic enough to assume that for some of you, my recent 10 week absence from posting has been notable and for that reason alone I shall preface today’s posting with a brief explanation on where I have been. I do this not because it happens to be any of your business what I do. For me writing is a habit easily gotten out of and recently, inescapably so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Guy 20 Questions</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/04/06/white-guy-20-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 12:20:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/04/06/white-guy-20-questions/</guid>
      <description>White Guy 20 Questions Dear Stumpers,
When I put on my cyberslut cape and tights and sit down at my keyboard, it is with one mission and one mission alone in mind and that is to get us all laid, real good. Most of the time,I like to turn to positive psychology. I serve up digestible short articles with punchy titles and bullet pointed lists that include tips and tricks, aimed at helping my fellow adults navigate the ever changing world of cyber-sex internet dating and sex in a post-monogamy world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wake Up Call</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/04/02/wake-up-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 16:23:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/04/02/wake-up-call/</guid>
      <description>A word of caution to readers: This post deals with suicidal ideation and impulses to self harm.
My Wakeup Call When I was just three years old, a teenage boy from up the block grabbed me out from the driveway of our duplex and held a switchblade knife to my throat. His identity, his motivations and his current fate are unknown to me. He held me just long enough to let go before my panicked older sister could return with my bemused and skeptical father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Not MeToo Its You</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/30/its-not-metoo-its-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 09:30:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/30/its-not-metoo-its-you/</guid>
      <description>It’s Not #MeToo It’s You Dear Men,
I understand some of you feel like you are having a hard time, lately. Things that you have always taken for granted are being questioned. The days headlines are reporting an accelerating decline in Male sexual activity in America. Some of you feel like you aren’t quite sure what you get to laugh at, what you get to say and who you get to touch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wide World Of Sex Apps</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/17/the-wide-world-of-sex-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 10:58:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/17/the-wide-world-of-sex-apps/</guid>
      <description>The Wide Wild World of Sex Aps Caution: The following post deals with frank talk about sex prudes need not proceed.
Beloved Stumpers:
Let’s say you’ve read my background posts, done some thinking, had a talk with your partner (if you have one) and maybe you’ve explored fantasy literature and even got yourself a copy of the Ethical Slut, and now you’re feeling ready for the next step, you want to get out there and explore the world of kink and group sex hookups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fallen Stars</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/04/fallen-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 19:19:35 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/04/fallen-stars/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stumpers:
This weekend HBO premiered Leaving Neverland, A documentary series, that tells the stories of the men who survived Michael Jackson’s grooming and sexual abuse. I don’t have HBO go so I haven’t seen it. Instead I’m watching American Crime Stories: the Trial of OJ simpson. The Simpson story of is the fall of another cultural icon and a sad moment for our national media culture. The chatter about Leaving Neverland on new sites and on social media all week makes it pretty clear that the picture of Jackson is damning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like A Girl</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/28/like-a-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 11:00:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/28/like-a-girl/</guid>
      <description>“Like a Girl” Now is a good time to be a girl. The future is female, so we are told. Girl boss is a hashtag and girls can be anyone they want to be. Thanks to a razor maker’s clever marketing, masculinity is toxic now. My daughter enjoys wearing glittery pink sneakers with jeans and a tutu and a boy’s superhero t-shirt to school and no one bats an eye accept to compliment her on her superior sense of style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Defense Of Guys</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/23/in-defense-of-guys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 11:21:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/23/in-defense-of-guys/</guid>
      <description>In Defense of “Guys” Come along with me stumpers, as I take a nerdy deep dive into the intersection of regional identity, feminism and language.
First off I am going to reveal one of my thinly veiled secrets. I am from the Pacific Northwest (PNW). My whole family is from the Pacific Northwest. My family roots in the PNW go back four generations. If you look at the population trends for the Northwestern States, the growth, powered by transplants from other states has been explosive over the course of my lifetime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valentines Day For Dummies</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/11/valentines-day-for-dummies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 10:48:02 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/11/valentines-day-for-dummies/</guid>
      <description>Valentines Day For Dummies Dearest Stumpers:
If I wish one thing for you all this Valentine’s Day it is for you all to achieve sexual satisfaction be it alone, or with a partner. Valentine’s Day is perhaps the most awkward day of the calendar year and the sexual revolution hasn’t done it any favors. Presently, the prevailing winds indicate that it is a day for children to trade heart themed and punny pre-made notes, for teenagers to run around confused and for adults to express their affection through themed gifting or feel lonely if they are single.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s His Story</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/10/whats-his-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 09:36:39 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/10/whats-his-story/</guid>
      <description>What’s His Story? Last night, during his annual address to the United States Congress, in a move aimed at retaining his party’s grip over the religious right, the Kleptocrat who holds executive office of the world’s most powerful oligarchy, took aim at women’s rights. He piously declared the sanctity of all life, even the unborn (though let us not speak of diabetes patients in puerto rico) and attacked laws passed in New York and Virginia aimed aimed at securing access to reproductive care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Creeper</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/07/my-first-creeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 19:44:45 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/07/my-first-creeper/</guid>
      <description>My First Creeper Dear Stumpers:
I’m about to let you in behind the scenes of StumpedMom.com. While the casual or even careful reader could never be blamed for assuming I pull this entire website out of my ass. I try to organize my ideas and put them out in an organized and orderly fashion. I use an Airtable (Please sponsor me) spreadsheet to organize my work from the idea stage, through to publishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monday Mom Hacks Infant Stytle</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/04/monday-mom-hacks-infant-stytle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 10:55:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/04/monday-mom-hacks-infant-stytle/</guid>
      <description>Monday Mom Hacks Infant style:
If I am committed to anything here at StumpedMom.com it is learning things the hard way so you don’t have to. If you have young children or are anticipating the arrival of a new baby you’re going to be bombarded with advice. Some of it helpful-some of it pushy and unnecessary. I’m not here to sell you a product, just to entertain you and hopefully make your life a little better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Consent</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/01/cyber-consent/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 10:20:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/01/cyber-consent/</guid>
      <description>Cyber Consent Dear Stumpers:
It’s time to have a little talk about cyber boundaries and cyber consent. This isn’t going to be one of my friendly Mom talks. Because many of you are not being very nice. If I have done it right, you will all feel sufficiently chastised before reaching the end of this article.
For a few weeks now, I have been ruminating on all of the talk about dick picks and cyber whores and good girls and bad girls and sluts and fuckbois, on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex For Every Body</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/29/sex-for-every-body/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 14:34:34 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/29/sex-for-every-body/</guid>
      <description>Stumpers:
For those of you that follow me on twitter or catch up with me on guest blogs, or have even read my full catalogue you may be aware that I am going through a bit of a personal health crisis right now. I have badly injured my lower back. You all know I write about sex but none have you been brave enough to ask. What has the impact of your lower back injury been on your sex life?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind Over Matter</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/23/mind-over-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 19:49:15 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/23/mind-over-matter/</guid>
      <description>Mind over Matter
Dear stumpers:
I can’t tell you how excited I am to have been invited to do my first guest post. When Christina G. invited me to post on her site I was incredibly excited and flattered. She is literally one of five other bloggers out there I consistently enjoy reading. If you’re a stumper you owe it to yourself to check her out.
Mind Over Matter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Segregation</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/20/supermarket-segregation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 10:32:10 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/20/supermarket-segregation/</guid>
      <description>Supermarket Segregation Dear Stumpers:
There is segregation going on right under our noses in a place you depend on and likely bring your children. It is Supermarket segregation and it’s happening in grocery chains that have invested heavily in cultivating progressive images and niche markets. This isn’t an overt kind of Jim Crow segregation, where specific people are banned from employment or shopping at the stores. This segregation is a coded message written in product grouping, placement and signage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>