<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Features on Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/tag/features/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Features on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:55:47 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/tag/features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hemophilia Hustle Part I</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/09/17/hemophilia-hustle-part-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:55:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/09/17/hemophilia-hustle-part-i/</guid>
      <description>Hemophilia Hustle Part I Dear Stumpers:
One of the things about abandoning anonymity means that I get to write about more of my peculiar, identifying characteristics. As Stumped Mom and just Stumped Mom, I could be banal, outrageous, relatable and even, if the mood struck me, heartfelt, but there were certain things- things that were truest about me - that I could not express without completely compromising my identity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tweet That Launched at Least One Complaint</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/09/02/the-tweet-that-launched-at-least-one-complaint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 19:51:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/09/02/the-tweet-that-launched-at-least-one-complaint/</guid>
      <description>Warning: This post is littered with inaccuracies and fictionalization, but I’m also pretty sure it&amp;rsquo;s still true enough to keep anyone who thinks any of it is about them from suing me.
The Tweet That Launched at Least One Complaint Dear Stumpers,
I have been surprised and deeply touched by your positive responses to my triumphant blogging. People have saluted my bravery and encouraged me to write more. Many readers have asked me, “What was the tweet that got you fired?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monthly Mindfulness</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/08/22/monthly-mindfulness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/08/22/monthly-mindfulness/</guid>
      <description>Monthly Mindfulness Religion is the opium of the people. It is the sigh of the oppressed creature, the heart of a heartless world, and the soul of our soulless conditions.-Karl Marx 
“Monthly Mindfulness Zoom session starts in 10 minutes,” Chimed the automated google calendar alert.
“I should go,” I thought. But why did it feel like such a drag? My therapist wants me to do at least 20 minutes of mindfulness practice every day, this counts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secret Husbands, Lost Jobs and Dead Alter Egos</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/08/15/secret-husbands-lost-jobs-and-dead-alter-egos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/08/15/secret-husbands-lost-jobs-and-dead-alter-egos/</guid>
      <description>Secret Husbands, Lost Jobs and Dead Alter Egos Dear Stumpers:
Today’s Advisory: This post is rated H for heavy; contains themes of real death, real loss, real life and real consequences.
My beloved grandmother had a secret first husband. While she was in the blossom of her youth, (some-time between 1939 and 1942), she ran away from her home in Oregon eloped and moved to Chicago. He abused her, she called home for help, and her brothers went out the midwest to retrieve her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wake Up Call</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/04/02/wake-up-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 16:23:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/04/02/wake-up-call/</guid>
      <description>A word of caution to readers: This post deals with suicidal ideation and impulses to self harm.
My Wakeup Call When I was just three years old, a teenage boy from up the block grabbed me out from the driveway of our duplex and held a switchblade knife to my throat. His identity, his motivations and his current fate are unknown to me. He held me just long enough to let go before my panicked older sister could return with my bemused and skeptical father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valentines Day For Dummies</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/11/valentines-day-for-dummies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 10:48:02 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/11/valentines-day-for-dummies/</guid>
      <description>Valentines Day For Dummies Dearest Stumpers:
If I wish one thing for you all this Valentine’s Day it is for you all to achieve sexual satisfaction be it alone, or with a partner. Valentine’s Day is perhaps the most awkward day of the calendar year and the sexual revolution hasn’t done it any favors. Presently, the prevailing winds indicate that it is a day for children to trade heart themed and punny pre-made notes, for teenagers to run around confused and for adults to express their affection through themed gifting or feel lonely if they are single.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Segregation</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/20/supermarket-segregation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 10:32:10 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/20/supermarket-segregation/</guid>
      <description>Supermarket Segregation Dear Stumpers:
There is segregation going on right under our noses in a place you depend on and likely bring your children. It is Supermarket segregation and it’s happening in grocery chains that have invested heavily in cultivating progressive images and niche markets. This isn’t an overt kind of Jim Crow segregation, where specific people are banned from employment or shopping at the stores. This segregation is a coded message written in product grouping, placement and signage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Dysfunctional Ways to Avoid a bad Boss</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/09/10-dysfunctional-ways-to-avoid-a-bad-boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 20:46:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/09/10-dysfunctional-ways-to-avoid-a-bad-boss/</guid>
      <description>10 Dysfunctional Ways to Avoid a bad Boss If you’re looking for advice on how to be an efficient part of the capitalist machine the American news media and the internet have you covered. Forbes, the Wall Street Journal and LinkedIn supply a steady stream of content designed to help you be a compliant and striving little worker bee. I haven’t seen any metrics but these pieces wouldn’t proliferate so freely if they weren’t popular and therefore profitable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Fantasy Talk</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/01/advanced-fantasy-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/01/advanced-fantasy-talk/</guid>
      <description>Advanced Fantasy Talk Dear Stumpers:
Two entries ago I promised to get into some more advanced fantasy tips and I am nothing if not a woman of my word. These are my more advanced tips for a slightly kinkier level of fantasy play. I claim zero expertise in kink; for that you’re going to have to go to different corners of the internet but those corners can be scary and intimidating, even if they really are actually filled with regular people who just happen to enjoy novel sexual if experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Purge</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/20/the-purge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/20/the-purge/</guid>
      <description>The Purge Welcome Stumpers,
to the good vibes only zone. Come along with me on a journey to awesomeness while improving your life, your mind, your body and your soul with a thorough and complete cleansing. Now is the time to rid ourselves of negativity in our lives. You don’t need negative people or influencers pulling you down with them. If they don’t affirm you and all of your most ardent desires, or make your sandwiches and give you orgasms, flatter your taste and intelligence, block them, delete them, ignore them and feel free to abandon with abandon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Path of the Cyberslut</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/04/the-path-of-the-cyberslut/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/04/the-path-of-the-cyberslut/</guid>
      <description>The Path of the Cyberslut Dear Stumpers,
Following my separation which occurred under such specifically scandalous circumstances that it would completely compromise my anonymity if I were to recount it, I went through a period of complete and reckless internet chatting and dating abandon. In my younger days and with my ex-I had dabbled in cybsex, sexting and a radical 90’s trend called phone sex. But in this stretch of newly found adult independence I decided to dive headlong into the most idiosyncratic corners of the online dating scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catalogue of Privledge</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/20/catalogue-of-privledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/20/catalogue-of-privledge/</guid>
      <description>Catalogue of Privilege Stumpers:
Do you mind if I call you Stumpers? It feels more personal than Dear Reader.
One of the principles I have committed myself in this endeavor is include “privilege awareness”. I operate on the theory that the first step to creating a more equitable and just society is to acknowledge inequality. For those of us that benefit in some way from inequality we need to be able to name those benefits, we must be aware of our privilege.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down With The PTA</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/08/down-with-the-pta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/08/down-with-the-pta/</guid>
      <description>Down With The PTA No bourgeoisie institution makes me want to lock arms with my proletariat brethren and forcibly seize the means of production from the soft, plump hands of our capitalist overlords quite like the Parent Teacher Association otherwise known as PTAs or PTOs .
Their reasons for existing and means of sustaining themselves are entirely dependent of systems and structures that perpetuate inequality.
What are you talking about Stumped Mom?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How did we get here?</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/10/25/how-did-we-get-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/10/25/how-did-we-get-here/</guid>
      <description>Dear reader: All endeavors must have a beginning and this endeavor will begin with an attempt to answer a question. How did we get here? We; being you the reader me the writer. Here being the virtual space that manifests itself in this blog.
Let us start with me. I am here because I became convinced of the narcissistic conceit that the vast and overcrowded world of mommy blogs, feminist writings, parenting advice and armchair political philosophy could possibly benefit from a space dedicated to my idiosyncratic musings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>