<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Body Politic on Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/tag/the-body-politic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Body Politic on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 15:55:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/tag/the-body-politic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets_Talk_About_1999</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/09/12/lets_talk_about_1999/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 15:55:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/09/12/lets_talk_about_1999/</guid>
      <description>Dear HBO:
After two weeks of having it appear on podcasts like “The Alaramist” and “What are you Into”, I watched “Woodstock 99: Peace, Love, and Rage”, and unsurprisingly it was triggering as fuck! I saw myself in it, but I did not feel seen by it. I felt like the film focused a lot on the women at the festival as victims and some of them as witnesses, but few as active agents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hand and Foot</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/05/21/hand-and-foot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/05/21/hand-and-foot/</guid>
      <description>Caution: this post deals with violence toward women
Hand and Foot Dear Stumpers:
I’m narcissistic enough to assume that for some of you, my recent 10 week absence from posting has been notable and for that reason alone I shall preface today’s posting with a brief explanation on where I have been. I do this not because it happens to be any of your business what I do. For me writing is a habit easily gotten out of and recently, inescapably so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Not MeToo Its You</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/30/its-not-metoo-its-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 09:30:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/30/its-not-metoo-its-you/</guid>
      <description>It’s Not #MeToo It’s You Dear Men,
I understand some of you feel like you are having a hard time, lately. Things that you have always taken for granted are being questioned. The days headlines are reporting an accelerating decline in Male sexual activity in America. Some of you feel like you aren’t quite sure what you get to laugh at, what you get to say and who you get to touch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fallen Stars</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/04/fallen-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 19:19:35 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/04/fallen-stars/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stumpers:
This weekend HBO premiered Leaving Neverland, A documentary series, that tells the stories of the men who survived Michael Jackson’s grooming and sexual abuse. I don’t have HBO go so I haven’t seen it. Instead I’m watching American Crime Stories: the Trial of OJ simpson. The Simpson story of is the fall of another cultural icon and a sad moment for our national media culture. The chatter about Leaving Neverland on new sites and on social media all week makes it pretty clear that the picture of Jackson is damning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like A Girl</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/28/like-a-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 11:00:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/28/like-a-girl/</guid>
      <description>“Like a Girl” Now is a good time to be a girl. The future is female, so we are told. Girl boss is a hashtag and girls can be anyone they want to be. Thanks to a razor maker’s clever marketing, masculinity is toxic now. My daughter enjoys wearing glittery pink sneakers with jeans and a tutu and a boy’s superhero t-shirt to school and no one bats an eye accept to compliment her on her superior sense of style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s His Story</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/10/whats-his-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 09:36:39 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/10/whats-his-story/</guid>
      <description>What’s His Story? Last night, during his annual address to the United States Congress, in a move aimed at retaining his party’s grip over the religious right, the Kleptocrat who holds executive office of the world’s most powerful oligarchy, took aim at women’s rights. He piously declared the sanctity of all life, even the unborn (though let us not speak of diabetes patients in puerto rico) and attacked laws passed in New York and Virginia aimed aimed at securing access to reproductive care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Segregation</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/20/supermarket-segregation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 10:32:10 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/20/supermarket-segregation/</guid>
      <description>Supermarket Segregation Dear Stumpers:
There is segregation going on right under our noses in a place you depend on and likely bring your children. It is Supermarket segregation and it’s happening in grocery chains that have invested heavily in cultivating progressive images and niche markets. This isn’t an overt kind of Jim Crow segregation, where specific people are banned from employment or shopping at the stores. This segregation is a coded message written in product grouping, placement and signage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Struggle With Ableism</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/03/my-struggle-with-ableism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/03/my-struggle-with-ableism/</guid>
      <description>My Struggle With Ableism About two years ago while I was stuck working night shift for a few weeks, I got really into the Harvard Implicit Bias test project. The tests ask you to react quickly to a series of images and is designed to measure your unconscious bias towards groups. I felt super great about myself when I took my first test and found out I was biased in favor darker skinned people and against lighter skinned people (an outlier result for a white woman).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whiteclaiming</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/06/whiteclaiming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/06/whiteclaiming/</guid>
      <description>Dear Fellow White People,
The time has come for us to stop Whiteclaiming. The time has come for us to stop feigning in aspects of the cultures of non-white people by virtue of proximity. For the sake of brevity I am dubbing this phenomenon whiteclaiming. Whiteclamining occurs when a white person claims specific special understanding of something they associate with an ethnic group based on who they know or where they are from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No duh</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/01/no-duh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 19:56:48 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/01/no-duh/</guid>
      <description>A word of caution: The following post has heavy feels and addresses sexual trauma.
#NoDuh I was eleven the first time a friend confided in me that she had been sexually abused. I was fourteen the next time. When a friend told me that a neighbor had molested her and another girl on her street. I was sixteen when an adult, female, relative told me her abuse story. I was 18 the first time a male told me his story….</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>