<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mom Hacks on Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/tag/mom-hacks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mom Hacks on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/tag/mom-hacks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Best Teacher Holiday Gifts</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/29/5-best-teacher-holiday-gifts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/29/5-best-teacher-holiday-gifts/</guid>
      <description>5 Best Teacher Holiday Gifts Dear Stumpers:
I expect you saw right through my veiled attempt at click bait and you are not expecting to see a straightforward list of suggestions for teacher gifts. I’m not going try to trick you. It is my opinion that purchasing gifts for school teachers is a socially corrosive and ethically corrupt trend. I can’t blame you for looking for suggestions, especially if you have a kinder or first grader just starting school and you just found out the other parents have been gifting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Replace Your Husband with Amazon Prime</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/26/replace-your-husband-with-amazon-prime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 13:16:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/26/replace-your-husband-with-amazon-prime/</guid>
      <description>Replace Your Husband with Amazon Prime Dearest Stumpers,
(Do you mind if I call you Dearest? I feel like we’re getting so much closer these days)
I hope that one of the things I can accomplish through sharing is to show that I have learned the hard way so that you don’t have to. My divorce struck like a sudden car wreck, the causes of which were multiplicitous. Explaining it all might take going into the sort of exacting excavation and slow revelation that might make you feel like you were being made to watch Roger Stone’s JFK and I am not a lazy, sophomore American History teacher, so I am not going to waste four hours of your time trying to convince you of a version of events, when there is no ready path toward rectification.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>