<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/category/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/category/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Best Teacher Holiday Gifts</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/29/5-best-teacher-holiday-gifts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/29/5-best-teacher-holiday-gifts/</guid>
      <description>5 Best Teacher Holiday Gifts Dear Stumpers:
I expect you saw right through my veiled attempt at click bait and you are not expecting to see a straightforward list of suggestions for teacher gifts. I’m not going try to trick you. It is my opinion that purchasing gifts for school teachers is a socially corrosive and ethically corrupt trend. I can’t blame you for looking for suggestions, especially if you have a kinder or first grader just starting school and you just found out the other parents have been gifting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Replace Your Husband with Amazon Prime</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/26/replace-your-husband-with-amazon-prime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 13:16:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/26/replace-your-husband-with-amazon-prime/</guid>
      <description>Replace Your Husband with Amazon Prime Dearest Stumpers,
(Do you mind if I call you Dearest? I feel like we’re getting so much closer these days)
I hope that one of the things I can accomplish through sharing is to show that I have learned the hard way so that you don’t have to. My divorce struck like a sudden car wreck, the causes of which were multiplicitous. Explaining it all might take going into the sort of exacting excavation and slow revelation that might make you feel like you were being made to watch Roger Stone’s JFK and I am not a lazy, sophomore American History teacher, so I am not going to waste four hours of your time trying to convince you of a version of events, when there is no ready path toward rectification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrooge Shaming</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/22/scrooge-shaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/22/scrooge-shaming/</guid>
      <description>The Casual Cruelty of Scrooge Shaming Proceed with care and self directed compassion.This post deals with trauma triggers surrounding the loss of a child.
Dear Stumpers:
The clock has struck! Tis Thanksgiving and America has officially plunged into a six week, long commercially fueled onslaught of seasonal Christmas themed celebration, commonly known as the Holiday Season. An army of Christmas enthusiasts enabled by naked commercial interest go to work and transform virtually all public, commercial and private spaces (save those of the non Christian religions) to conform to their concept of winter festiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catalogue of Privledge</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/20/catalogue-of-privledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/20/catalogue-of-privledge/</guid>
      <description>Catalogue of Privilege Stumpers:
Do you mind if I call you Stumpers? It feels more personal than Dear Reader.
One of the principles I have committed myself in this endeavor is include “privilege awareness”. I operate on the theory that the first step to creating a more equitable and just society is to acknowledge inequality. For those of us that benefit in some way from inequality we need to be able to name those benefits, we must be aware of our privilege.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to Cook this Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/15/what-to-cook-this-thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 14:27:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/15/what-to-cook-this-thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>What to Cook this Thanksgiving Is Thanksgiving the only day of the year that you get serious about cooking? If you’re like most Americans it probably is. Recent surveys and market trends like meal kits and steady restaurant growth as well as the ever popularity of processed and frozen foods indicate that most Americans don’t cook. Cooking,like so many other activities in America has become a commodified spectector’s sport. While less than 15% of us enjoy cooking, 80% of us enjoy watching cooking shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down with the PTA!</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/13/down-with-the-pta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 10:33:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/13/down-with-the-pta/</guid>
      <description>Down with the PTA! No bourgeoisie institution makes me want to lock arms with my proletariat brethren and forcibly seize the means of production from the soft, plump hands of our capitalist overlords quite like the Parent Teacher Association otherwise known as PTAs or PTOs .
Their reasons for existing and means of sustaining themselves are entirely dependent of systems and structures that perpetuate inequality.
What are you talking about Stumped Mom?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No duh</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/01/no-duh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 19:56:48 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/01/no-duh/</guid>
      <description>A word of caution: The following post has heavy feels and addresses sexual trauma.
#NoDuh I was eleven the first time a friend confided in me that she had been sexually abused. I was fourteen the next time. When a friend told me that a neighbor had molested her and another girl on her street. I was sixteen when an adult, female, relative told me her abuse story. I was 18 the first time a male told me his story….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How did we get here?</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/10/25/how-did-we-get-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/10/25/how-did-we-get-here/</guid>
      <description>Dear reader: All endeavors must have a beginning and this endeavor will begin with an attempt to answer a question. How did we get here? We; being you the reader me the writer. Here being the virtual space that manifests itself in this blog.
Let us start with me. I am here because I became convinced of the narcissistic conceit that the vast and overcrowded world of mommy blogs, feminist writings, parenting advice and armchair political philosophy could possibly benefit from a space dedicated to my idiosyncratic musings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>