<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/category/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 14:27:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/category/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What to Cook this Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/15/what-to-cook-this-thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 14:27:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/15/what-to-cook-this-thanksgiving/</guid>
      <description>What to Cook this Thanksgiving Is Thanksgiving the only day of the year that you get serious about cooking? If you’re like most Americans it probably is. Recent surveys and market trends like meal kits and steady restaurant growth as well as the ever popularity of processed and frozen foods indicate that most Americans don’t cook. Cooking,like so many other activities in America has become a commodified spectector’s sport. While less than 15% of us enjoy cooking, 80% of us enjoy watching cooking shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down with the PTA!</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/13/down-with-the-pta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 10:33:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/13/down-with-the-pta/</guid>
      <description>Down with the PTA! No bourgeoisie institution makes me want to lock arms with my proletariat brethren and forcibly seize the means of production from the soft, plump hands of our capitalist overlords quite like the Parent Teacher Association otherwise known as PTAs or PTOs .
Their reasons for existing and means of sustaining themselves are entirely dependent of systems and structures that perpetuate inequality.
What are you talking about Stumped Mom?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No duh</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/01/no-duh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 19:56:48 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/01/no-duh/</guid>
      <description>A word of caution: The following post has heavy feels and addresses sexual trauma.
#NoDuh I was eleven the first time a friend confided in me that she had been sexually abused. I was fourteen the next time. When a friend told me that a neighbor had molested her and another girl on her street. I was sixteen when an adult, female, relative told me her abuse story. I was 18 the first time a male told me his story….</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How did we get here?</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/10/25/how-did-we-get-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/10/25/how-did-we-get-here/</guid>
      <description>Dear reader: All endeavors must have a beginning and this endeavor will begin with an attempt to answer a question. How did we get here? We; being you the reader me the writer. Here being the virtual space that manifests itself in this blog.
Let us start with me. I am here because I became convinced of the narcissistic conceit that the vast and overcrowded world of mommy blogs, feminist writings, parenting advice and armchair political philosophy could possibly benefit from a space dedicated to my idiosyncratic musings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>