<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nerds Only on Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/tag/nerds-only/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nerds Only on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 11:21:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/tag/nerds-only/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>In Defense Of Guys</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/23/in-defense-of-guys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 11:21:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/23/in-defense-of-guys/</guid>
      <description>In Defense of “Guys” Come along with me stumpers, as I take a nerdy deep dive into the intersection of regional identity, feminism and language.
First off I am going to reveal one of my thinly veiled secrets. I am from the Pacific Northwest (PNW). My whole family is from the Pacific Northwest. My family roots in the PNW go back four generations. If you look at the population trends for the Northwestern States, the growth, powered by transplants from other states has been explosive over the course of my lifetime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owning Sex</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/08/owning-sex/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 10:05:49 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/08/owning-sex/</guid>
      <description>Owning Sex Dear Stumpers:
This past week, I received my first feedback from a self described, lifestyle kinkster, about the #cyberslut. I admit, I went out on a limb and inserted myself into their conversation, hoping to reach out to new audiences and expand my reach. This feedback described some of my assertions as inaccurate fundamentally wrong. I asked them to share resources on the topics but they did not respond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Brain</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/13/twitter-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 08:30:27 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/13/twitter-brain/</guid>
      <description>Twitter Brain Twitter Brain; Noun:
 The condition resulting from excessive attention to Twitter characterized by intense effort toward building your personal brand and attracting new followers. A person who thinks too much about their Twitter following.  Example: Stump Mom’s writing and research and overall attention were suffering because she had Twitter Brain.
I have recently come to terms with a reality that much America has been living with or some time - It doesn’t take much to come down with a case of Twitter Brain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>