<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Opinion on Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/tag/opinion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Opinion on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 09:30:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/tag/opinion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Not MeToo Its You</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/30/its-not-metoo-its-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 09:30:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/30/its-not-metoo-its-you/</guid>
      <description>It’s Not #MeToo It’s You Dear Men,
I understand some of you feel like you are having a hard time, lately. Things that you have always taken for granted are being questioned. The days headlines are reporting an accelerating decline in Male sexual activity in America. Some of you feel like you aren’t quite sure what you get to laugh at, what you get to say and who you get to touch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Creeper</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/07/my-first-creeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 19:44:45 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/07/my-first-creeper/</guid>
      <description>My First Creeper Dear Stumpers:
I’m about to let you in behind the scenes of StumpedMom.com. While the casual or even careful reader could never be blamed for assuming I pull this entire website out of my ass. I try to organize my ideas and put them out in an organized and orderly fashion. I use an Airtable (Please sponsor me) spreadsheet to organize my work from the idea stage, through to publishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrooge Shaming</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/22/scrooge-shaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/22/scrooge-shaming/</guid>
      <description>The Casual Cruelty of Scrooge Shaming Proceed with care and self directed compassion.This post deals with trauma triggers surrounding the loss of a child.
Dear Stumpers:
The clock has struck! Tis Thanksgiving and America has officially plunged into a six week, long commercially fueled onslaught of seasonal Christmas themed celebration, commonly known as the Holiday Season. An army of Christmas enthusiasts enabled by naked commercial interest go to work and transform virtually all public, commercial and private spaces (save those of the non Christian religions) to conform to their concept of winter festiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>