<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/about_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/about_me/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About me:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a fiction - an artistic alter ego created to emphasize key traits of my creator’s personal identity, hile intentionally masking others. All biographies and human self presentations include exaggeration as well as obfuscation for it is only in fiction that we dispense with the pretense of factual authenticity, and free ourselves to explore larger truths. That being said, I identify as a slutty, white, divorced mother of one in the year 2018. I live in a West Coast American city, there is no hiding that. I am college educated and I own a modest home in an, “up and coming neighborhood” (The whole foods 8 blocks up just opened 2 years ago). I have a job that pays me just enough to be able to afford the mortgage on that home and do enough repairs to keep it from falling down. So I guess that makes me part of the “coastal elite.” My favorite Muppet is Gonzo. I am a weirdo, who has learned to assimilate with everyday life but every, single day I see elephants in rooms and I want to talk about them. This room is parenting and mothering in contemporary America and I want to talk about pesky pachyderms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In the words of the great Rowdie Roddie Piper, “I am here to kickass and chew bubblegum and I am all out of bubblegum!” - Stumped Mom is here to slay!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catalogue of Privledge</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/20/catalogue-of-privledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/20/catalogue-of-privledge/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;catalogue-of-privilege&#34;&gt;Catalogue of Privilege&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stumpers:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you mind if I call you Stumpers? It feels more personal than Dear Reader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the principles I have committed myself in this endeavor is include “privilege awareness”. I operate on the theory that the first step to creating a more equitable and just society is to acknowledge inequality. For those of us that benefit in some way from inequality we need to be able to name those benefits, we must be aware of our privilege. In an attempt enhance my own privilege awareness I worked on creating a Catalog of Privilege.  I am sharing it with my readers in interest of transparency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Actually spent more time developing this than any of my other posts. I’ve been working on it for close to 8 weeks. The primary reason it took me so long is I tried to create a two column feature with privileges in one column and disadvantages in another. And then I realized what I really need for this post is the privileges. The disadvantages were unnecessary. My disadvantages are going to come out in my writing. They are the part of my story I don’t have to remind myself about because they create challenges in my life every day.  The very nature of privilege is that it doesn’t demand our attention in order for us to succeed.  Millions of people are walking around every day completely oblivious to it and while it might be holding them back from some spiritual, intellectual and relationship growth it generally doesn’t hold people back in any material form.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I plan to update this list as my consciousness expands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table style=&#34;border: 1px solid black; border-collapse: collapse&#34;&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;h2&gt;Privilege Catalog:&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;White&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            This is the Big Grand-daddy of all privileges. I carry all of the markers of Whiteness: White parents, white siblings, pale skin, a first and last name with English origins, the whole thing. This impacts my life and the way people treat me in ways that I can only view by contrasting my experience with those of people who do not receive this treatment, which is frustrating because I can’t even look at it without being ethnocentric.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Straight (ish)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            I put this down in the privilege column with a few caveats.Not all of my sexual relationships have been heterosexual. I’m in a long term heterosexual relationship, so for most social purposes I carry straight privilege. Personally I see this most in the stories society tells me about the relationships I am in and how desirable they are. The relationships that feel most natural for me personally are reflected everywhere in our culture.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cis Gender&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            With the exception of a period of my life that I will call my awkward phase, during which I was frequently mistaken for a boy and harangued for my lack of appropriate girlish femininity, I have always fit squarely and comfortably into the gender I was assigned at birth. I have all kinds of qualms with the ways we enforce gender but here I am, quite assuredly a woman.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;American&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            I was born ensconced incomparable physical security of the 20th century American Military Industrial Complex. Wherever I go the power of my nation of origin and its economic and military might has an influence on my personal safety and esteem.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Temporarily Able Bodied&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            I enjoy the luxury of experiencing an urban and consumer landscape that is engineered almost exclusively for bodies that are sized and function like mine.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Average-ish body size&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            While almost all women experience fat shaming because that’s just how messed up our society is, I wear a size L in most stores and that regular everyday dress size exempts me from the bullying, and marginalization people with larger bodies experience.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Conventionally Attractive&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            I don’t want to talk about this there is no way to talk about it without “humble bragging” and no one likes humble braggers. It’s a thing and it has been shown to make the world more well disposed toward me than it otherwise could be.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;                                                                    
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to Cook this Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/15/what-to-cook-this-thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 14:27:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/15/what-to-cook-this-thanksgiving/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;what-to-cook-this-thanksgiving&#34;&gt;What to Cook this Thanksgiving&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is Thanksgiving the only day of the year that you get serious about cooking?  If you’re like most Americans it probably is. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/personalfinance/2017/09/27/90-americans-dont-like-cook-and-its-costing-them-thousands-each-year/708033001/&#34;&gt;Recent surveys&lt;/a&gt; and market trends like meal kits and steady restaurant growth as well as the ever popularity of processed and frozen foods indicate that most Americans don’t cook.  Cooking,like so many other activities in America has become a commodified spectector’s sport. While less than 15% of us enjoy cooking, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.marketingcharts.com/television-13719&#34;&gt;80% of us enjoy&lt;/a&gt; watching cooking shows. Thanksgiving, however centers around a traditional old fashioned home-cooked meal. Our popular images of this Holiday include friends and family gathered around a copious meal produced with loving care. For one day a year millions of would be home cooks roll up their sleeves, open up cookbooks, consult packaging instructions, and even more likely cooking blogs, and get to work. And the results? They are mostly pathetic.  Millions of Turkeys are lead to the slaughter for the Holiday and most of them turn out dry, over oiled, under flavored or fall victim to countless other faux pas.  To eat these birds family members drown the meat in overcooked gravy.  Hundreds of thousands of us pretend to enjoy dishes so dreadful they only get made once a year.  Meanwhile millions of pounds of food waste are produced because too many people are trying to get in on the cooking action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take, for instance, my sister’s green-bean casserole. This dish is is a travesty, a mushy, salty travesty composed of canned products dumped into a casserole dish and baked until warm. If you are like my sister - if you you can’t tell the difference between mincing and chopping, if you don’t know your chef’s knife from your paring knife and and you’re hoping to find recipe’s and tips in blogs, please stop now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re doing the culinary equivalent of attempting to run a half marathon when you’ve never run further than a mile in your life. You are not ready for this. Meanwhile there are a few Americans, the few, the proud the 15% that enjoy cooking and cook most nights of the week, we have been training for this day all year. Your cooking compatriots have been boiling, roasting, chopping, slicing braising, and chilling call year long. Fifteen percent is a small minority but still a significant one. Chances are you know and love one of these people. If you want my advice, you should call this person-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom who Makes phone calls?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Right then text this person  and ask them what they want to do for the holiday, ask for instructions on how you can help and make sure to get yourself invited. Humble yourself before their experience and preparation, as the novice you are, before the master. If you are told just to bring wine, pick up a good bottle of Bordeaux.  Arrive on time, not early and not late because your gracious cook has been prepping for a while and is relying on years of experience to time every dish just right. And when it’s all said and done when the once majestic indigenous American bird is naught but a stripped carcass, as uncles are dozing on couches while aunts look at holiday circulars and children turn on early holiday specials, do the damn dishes and help box the leftovers! Not everyone can be lucky enough to know a home cook that is up to the task.  On the day of Giving Thanks you should lean into gratitude and recognize the home cooks in your life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But stumped Mom I want to radiate in the joy of knowing I fed my family!  I want to take the credit for making the blessed thanksgiving event a success!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If that’s what you want if and if you are really sincere about it. Start reading my Sunday Cooking section (starting this next Sunday) and get ready to train hard for Thanksgiving 2019 because all things worth doing are worth doing right and it’s going to take at least a year of applied training to get you ready.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down with the PTA!</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/13/down-with-the-pta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 10:33:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/13/down-with-the-pta/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;down-with-the-pta&#34;&gt;Down with the PTA!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No bourgeoisie institution makes me want to lock arms with my proletariat brethren and forcibly seize the means of production from the soft, plump hands of our capitalist overlords quite like the Parent Teacher Association otherwise known as PTAs or PTOs .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their reasons for existing and means of sustaining themselves are entirely dependent of systems and structures that perpetuate inequality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are you talking about Stumped Mom? The PTA strengthens our communities and schools by promoting parental involvement at our schools and brings much needed resources and interest on to our campuses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumpers I can’t blame you for taking this perspective, because this is entirely what society wants you to think and I’m pretty sure it’s what makes those self righteous PTA board members look down their noses at us barely making it schleppers. Mom’s like me who are lucky if they get their kids to before-school care with clean faces each morning, let alone make it aross town after work to make the monthly PTA by 5:30 p.m. on a Wednesday are the famous objects of PTA mom disdain. I will confess, my own personal laziness makes me resent their industriousness. However, there is more to my beef with the PTA than simple personal envy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But stumped Mom, our schools are chronically underfunded, there is insecurity in staffing, and the teachers are underpaid and parental involvement at school helps kids to succeed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do not contest those points but let us and take a more critical eye and ask some crucial questions. When we do we find the classist, racist patriarchal and capitalist structures that buttress these groups are easily laid bare&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes for a good PTA?&lt;br /&gt;
Parents with organizational skills and spare time
A Community with Resources and Capital
Relationships and Connections between those parents and the people with the Capital&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of these critical components more abundant in more affluent communities, which thanks to the well documented racial income gap in this country, are overwhelmingly white. PTA participation is also a ladies game, with Mom’s far outnumbering Dad’s in participation. So the pressure to join and support the PTA weights heavily on women adding to their emotional labor burden and straining marriages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t just take my word for it. Reports show that PTA fundraising contributes to the achievement gap, that has been well documented, between white and affluent neighborhoods and communities with less resources.  And even in diverse or well integrated schools white parents hold a disproportionate influence over decision making.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cross sections factors that make for successful PTA’s allow affluent mostly-white, people to perpetuate the privilege of their children over that of others. And most of this happens on the barely recognized volunteer efforts of women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your a parent with a kid in school you likely understand the pressure to join the PTA.  I get invitations in the school newsletter every week. Parents pressure each other into pouring time, money and energy into stop gap measures meant to fill in the holes created by and tragically unequal public education system. Many of us visit our schools and see run down facilities, stressed staff, and outdated materials. We want to do whatever we can to help our children. But shouldn’t we be talking about campaigning against the policies that undermine funding and support for public education?  Nobody talks about this at back to school night or in the school newsletter. Instead we are treated to constant plugs for more PTA volunteers and lend special thank you’s to those lovely PTA Mom’s (sorry Dads the stats show this is a ladies game).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a more just society we would stop valorizing the systemic hoarding of privilege through support of Parent Teacher Associations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But those PTA invitations won’t stop. So what’s a woke parent to do? The next time a PTA pusher approaches me on the school yard. Here is what I’m saying:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No thanks I’m going to invest what little spare time I have in direct involvement in the classroom and any spare resources I have will be dedicated to campaigns for just and equal schools,”  but I’m also gonna wait till my daughter is ready to start our daily foot-race home before I shout “DOWN WITH THE PTA” as I flee the scene. For PTA Moms are brutal are as brutal as they are industrious and I’m not hanging around for a beating.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No duh</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/01/no-duh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 19:56:48 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/01/no-duh/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A word of caution: The following post has heavy feels and addresses sexual trauma.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;noduh&#34;&gt;#NoDuh&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was eleven the first time a friend confided in me that she had been sexually abused.
I was fourteen the next time. When a friend told me that a neighbor had molested her and another girl on her street. I was sixteen when an adult, female, relative told me her abuse story.
I was 18 the first time a male told me his story….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pattern continues like a thread through my life. The confidences weaving in during late night talks in bedrooms, in basements, on rooftops - with hushed tones, clasped hands and numbed, griefed expressions. As a girl and later a woman, no-one taught me how to receive these stories, what to do with them or how to contain them but as they came it was clear to me that they must be contained. Like monthly cycles, and family christmas card lists this was something for women and girls to manage; quietly, discreetly and independently. My whole life prepared me for it. The tiny details of my socialization as a girl taught me to listen, to feel and not to act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2017 when #metoo splashed on to the scene my initial reaction was “#noduh” or “#abouttime”. How could this possibly be a surprise to anyone? But as things moved forward I realized no one was really shocked by the stories or the prevalence. The shock was the act. The act of women speaking publicly and people paying attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new refrain of the #metoo backlash is a so called “rejection of victimhood”. A slight few conservative women had come out to say it that they two have been abused but that it doesn’t matter it hasn’t affected them, “Let’s all move on” They say “Let’s talk about something else.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The weekend of October 5th I was seething with anger. There was a walkout to protest the pending Kavanaugh confirmation in my city but I knew participation would get me disciplined at work. I can’t risk the income stream that feeds my child. When the confirmation was completed.I wanted to do more than just walk out. I wanted to wreck things. I wanted to burn it down. I wanted to go through the richest, whitest neighborhood in town and rip the male symbols off of old volvos. I wanted to smash the windows out of a hooters and drag frat boys from their beer splattered dens into the streets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had my daughter by myself all weekend, she is six.  We, ran errands, got out the halloween decorations, painted mini pumpkins, and cooked together. I took some great photos to send to her great grandparents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I got to work on Monday the 8th. I wanted, so badly, speak my anger to my co-workers. I talked about the pumpkin painting.  Unless you were working in media or workplace diversity or education no one was talking about it.  When I see other parents, we don’t talk about it. Sometimes at the dojo we make sad jokes about it. But even there we dampen our anger.  We chuckle it off as just another postmodern absurdity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our late night whisperings have a new sphere now. Don’t talk about it with your neighbors or co-workers. We should take it to twitter where can feel like we are telling the world but people can filter it out of their feeds. Block it. Silence it. Stick it back into those virtual version of bedrooms, rooftops and basements so women can get back to carrying it without showing it so as not to upset the men around us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a mother of a daughter I am constantly vigilant against signs of a threat that could come from anywhere. I want her to be able to declare her boundaries, to defend them if necessary and to tell if someone crosses them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other day my daughter presented with a rash on her vulva and labia. I asked her gently, “Have you been rubbing your vulva a-lot?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No” She said casually&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I squeezed out a dollop of cream onto her finger for her, I followed up in the most casual and clinical tone I could manage “Has anyone else been touching your vulva?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No” she replied,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A wave of qualified relief washed over me. As far as I can tell she’s been kept safe thus far from the most frightening forms abuse or exploitation. But we live in a world where the Kavanaughs win and even young girls have their secrets. And what of the faithful night when she is initiated into the real covenant of womanhood? When she becomes the first keeper of someone’s horrifying story? How am I preparing her for that? I haven’t seen it in the parenting guides, her pediatrician hasn’t mentioned it. Will there be hashtag for it?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How did we get here?</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/10/25/how-did-we-get-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/10/25/how-did-we-get-here/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;dear-reader&#34;&gt;Dear reader:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All endeavors must have a beginning and this endeavor will begin with an attempt to answer a question. How did we get here? We; being you the reader me the writer. Here being the virtual space that manifests itself in this blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let us start with me. I am here because I became convinced of the narcissistic conceit that the vast and overcrowded world of mommy blogs, feminist writings, parenting advice and armchair political philosophy could possibly benefit from a space dedicated to my idiosyncratic musings. While I am not specifically trained as a writer, I have always carried a certain vanity concerning my language skills and I have been nudged along by a few people in my life with increasing urgency to channel myself into writing. So reader it appears I am able to write, I am driven to write, I can write and I am going to write.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My life is quite full and I have no shortage of responsibilities. I have a child, a full time office type job, a dog, a cat, a three bedroom home to maintain, an uncooperative co-parent, a hungry and distracting boyfriend to feed and enjoy, and a fairly demanding recreational fitness hobby. A blog is like a whole other THING to take on. If I must write could I not collect it all in a private journal and keep it to myself?  I have attempted this but I have never been able to sustain it past thinking about how great it would be to set aside journaling time each day. Journaling is like a romantic fantasy that clearly belongs to some other class of much cooler, authentic and self assured sort of person. I can’t motivate myself to do it. It seems I require the focus of a potential audience. I would be content to stuff messages into a bottle and toss them into the ocean. That distribution method is probably just as likely to reach as many people another mommy blog.  But I do not want to add any more than I already have to the Pacific Garbage Patch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright let’s get to you, because we all want to hear about ourselves. Who are you? Most likely you’re someone very close to me because this is the first post on a new blog and I haven’t even figured out how to get readers, so my first audience will most likely be a tight and trusted circle. If you are someone very close to me I ask that you take my sharing this place with you as an evidence of trust. My goal for this space is for it to be a capital R-E-A-L real. I want to be as transparent as I can be about opinions, perspectives and experiences. But I also have people in my life who depend on me who I would like to protect. Privacy doesn’t really exist in  the internet world. So if you do know me or you read this and you are able to cross reference enough about my geographic location and life particulars to triangulate who I am then you know me well enough to picture the face of my beautiful innocent child. That face that will not be appear on this blog. If you need help calling that face to mind; find me on FB. I trust you to protect her by keeping quiet about who I am because the internet can be a cruel place and there is no telling what will set people off against a writer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a little bit of luck, persistence and pluck, you could be another sort of reader.  We shall call you Not too Distant Future Reader (NTDFR).  If your a NTDFR I am guessing you became engaged through social media promotion or maybe viral sharing of my work.  You read through my more recent and more mature posts and now you’re working your way through my back catalogue. I can’t say much about you NTDFR, but I can say that your haircut is way better than it was when I wrote this. Just take a look at that selfie you took back in the fall of 2018 what were you thinking?  Perhaps we share some things in common. Maybe you’re a recently divorced parent looking for perspectives on making it work that challenge the old “single mom” paradigm?  Maybe you ask yourself, “am I the only who feels like this is not okay?” just about everywhere you go. You’re also way more patient and smart than the internet marketing firm surveys say you are because here you are reading all the way down into word 740, or so, of this post and it doesn’t even have a slideshow.  And they all said smartphones were killing our attention spans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We covered me and we’ve talked about you, so what of here? Here is a place for exploring ideas about 21st century parenthood, through the perspective of a flawed, divorced, full-time working mom, living in a rapidly changing west coast american city, without any “my kids are my life” or “#blessed” bullshit. I plan to be frank about things that can get prickly, issues like race, sex, dating, class and money.  I hope you’ll to laugh at my failures and maybe celebrate some triumphs with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yours Truly,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/contact/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact-stumped-mom&#34;&gt;Contact Stumped Mom&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;form method=&#34;POST&#34; action=&#34;https://formspree.io/StumpedMomblog@gmail.com&#34;&gt;
  &lt;b&gt;Email:   &lt;/b&gt;&lt;input type=&#34;email&#34; name=&#34;email&#34; placeholder=&#34;Your email&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  &lt;b&gt;Subject: &lt;/b&gt; 
  &lt;input type= &#34;radio&#34; name=&#34;subject&#34; value=&#34;questions&#34;&gt; Questions
  &lt;input type= &#34;radio&#34; name=&#34;subject&#34; value=&#34;threats&#34;&gt; Threats&lt;br&gt;

  &lt;textarea name=&#34;message&#34; placeholder=&#34;Enter Message&#34; style=&#34;height: 150px; width: 500px&#34;&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  &lt;button type=&#34;submit&#34;&gt;Send&lt;/button&gt;
  
&lt;/form&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>