<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/about_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/about_me/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About me:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi I’m Robin and Stumped Mom and I used to be a  poorly kept secret. I like to write confessional, satirical essays and I enjoy sharing them with people, hearing their feedback and getting to know more about life in the process. I wanted to be able to be myself, write real and avoid the consequences. So my blog used to be anonymous, but then I crashed it into my life. So I killed Stumped Mom, but after two years in the literary desert I have brought her back and she’s bringing me with her.
I find doing this work on an open forum empowering and healing. Confessional essay blogs are an artform that excels in supply but lags in demand. So if you’re here reading this. Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monthly Mindfulness</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/08/22/monthly-mindfulness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/08/22/monthly-mindfulness/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;monthly-mindfulness&#34;&gt;Monthly Mindfulness&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Religion is the opium of the people. It is the sigh of the oppressed creature, the heart of a heartless world, and the soul of our soulless conditions.&lt;/em&gt;-Karl Marx
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Monthly Mindfulness Zoom session starts in 10 minutes,” Chimed the automated google calendar alert.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I should go,” I thought. But why did it feel like such a drag?
My therapist wants me to do at least 20 minutes of mindfulness practice every day, this counts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I logged in while still fussing with my headset and my audio settings. I haven’t been able to get my setup quite right since I sent my old, corporate client’s  computer back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other co-workers from teams all over the country are already chiming in. The COO is already on the call.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Glad I showed up. I haven’t been logging very many billable hours this week, I wouldn’t want to be missed in the free meditation session, I don’t want to look like I don’t care about improving myself.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our mindfulness expert is a pleasant mannered woman with bleach blonde hair and bright pink lipstick.  She is sitting in front of a neutral backdrop with chakra symbols stenciled onto the,  residential wall behind her.
A fake palm tree with fairy lights looms over her on the left side of the frame.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not a bad set-up for this sort of gig. If she was fancier I wouldn’t trust her and if she did less, people might think she isn’t trying.  I put some effort into not contemplating the layers of post-colonial and capitalistic disassociation required to make this zoom call happen . It won’t be productive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She kicks the session off with a call for a deep breath focusing on whatever two words come to mind as most “true” for us in that moment, “Check in with yourselves and share in the chat.” I get my headset paired just in time to start the first deep breath.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All I can feel is the giant knot in my shoulder and an overwhelming weight, I can only describe as weariness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m still breathing in but my co-workers are already chiming in to the chat with open and cheerful sentiments.  I’m still breathing out when I type “sore, wary”. She repeats my words back to me in a slightly pitious tone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Let us start with a body scan, starting at the top of the head,”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Oh I know this one&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I take a deep Breath in and I’m still breathing in and she has already forcefully breathed out and she’s giving more instructions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Now the neck.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In that breath I  had already moved to my chest. Okay back to my neck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;span-style-color-grey-with-only-about-half-of-the-u-s-population-fully-vaccinated-against-the-novel-coronavirus-hospitals-across-the-country-are-straining-to-respond-to-a-deadly-fourth-surge-of-infections-driven-by-the-delta-variant-washington-post-says-https-www-washingtonpost-com-health-2021-08-18-covid-hospitals-delta-span&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:grey&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;“With only about half of the U.S. population fully vaccinated against the novel coronavirus, hospitals across the country are straining to respond to a deadly fourth surge of infections driven by the delta variant.” &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2021/08/18/covid-hospitals-delta/&#34;&gt;Washington Post Says&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“And Let out another deep breath.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven’t finished filling my lungs with the last in-breath.  I can’t get in sync. I make sure my palms are turned up in the proper meditation position and wiggle in my chair. I give a little wiggle with my out-breath to try to settle in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Now scan your body. Where are you feeling the most tension or strain? “&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Oh here is the part where we breathe into the part of our body with the most tension.I got this!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I start taking in a long slow breath imagining I’m filling the stabbing knot in my neck with happy, warm loving  space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Now imagine a warm blanket.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Blanket thing? We&amp;rsquo;ve never done a blanket thing! Ok blanket I’m draping myself with the warm -&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s right out of the dryer”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cancel blanket draping. Initiate blanket out of the dryer. Do not think about how you need to clean the laundry room.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Wrap that part of yourself with the warm blanket and feel ensconce you with comfort”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;span-style-color-grey-this-remains-a-pandemic-of-the-unvaccinated-white-house-press-briefing-https-www-whitehouse-gov-briefing-room-press-briefings-2021-08-18-press-briefing-by-white-house-covid-19-response-team-and-public-health-officials-50-span&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:grey&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;This remains a pandemic of the unvaccinated.- &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/press-briefings/2021/08/18/press-briefing-by-white-house-covid-19-response-team-and-public-health-officials-50/&#34;&gt;White house press Briefing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“And now your at the precipice of&amp;hellip;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A cliff?!?!
In the space of that very pregnant pause, I’m totally contemplating the cold hard edge of  steep and windy dropoff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“A warm body of water.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cancel existential dread cliff, initiating  my  South Pacific fantasy reel.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I imagine the salty, azure lagoons I only know from the pictures in my clients vacation photos and the shots of The White Lotus. My bare feet are patting down fine, toasty sand. I wade in and float my consciousness as instructed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chime!- It&amp;rsquo;s another reminder. I try not to peek but I’m scared I might have forgotten a client meeting.  “Order back-to-school lunch box” it says.  My daughter is only nine, she can’t get vaccinated yet.  I have been putting off getting her ready for school with as much earnestness as she has had in looking forward to going back to class and seeing her teachers and friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“And now take in one more long, deep breath.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I take another breath and open my eyes but I’m ahead of things again. She says we’re slowly wading back out.  My breaths are still too long and slow to sync with the instructions.. I slowly wade my imagined self out of my fantasy beach and take in the two computer monitors in front of me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Chime!” Another Notification “Your Chase Card credit statement is ready”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Now take one more deep breath and focus on the two words that speak your truth now at the end of the session.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;is-fml-one-word-or-three&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Is FML one word or three?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secret Husbands, Lost Jobs and Dead Alter Egos</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/08/15/secret-husbands-lost-jobs-and-dead-alter-egos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2021/08/15/secret-husbands-lost-jobs-and-dead-alter-egos/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;secret-husbands-lost-jobs-and-dead-alter-egos&#34;&gt;Secret Husbands, Lost Jobs and Dead Alter Egos&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today’s Advisory: This post is rated H for heavy; contains themes of real death, real loss, real life and real consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My beloved grandmother had a secret first husband. While she was in the blossom of her youth, (some-time between 1939 and 1942), she ran away from her home in Oregon eloped and moved to Chicago. He abused her, she called home for help, and her brothers went out the midwest to retrieve her.  She lived at home with her parents, babysat and rosie’d, her way through the war and into the 1950’s unti, at the perilously mature age of 29, she met and married another sort of scoundrel, my grandfather.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/secrete_husband_img.png&#34; style=&#34;width:300px;height:736px;float:left;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 15px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first husband - the abuse - the forced haul home, all of this crucial biographical detail was successfully concealed from four successive generations for more than sixty years. The secret was held  via some sort of family pact, one that I can only assume was held securely through the bonds of shame. Shame held this secret right up to the day before her death. After speaking her last words and going into the long chain-stoking coma-state that characterizes a heart failure death, her oldest brother Harry shared this deepest darkest secret with my Mother, Sisters and I as we held vigil at her bedside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My uncle was a thoughtful and emotive man. Deaf and mute since a childhood bout of meningitis, he communicated with our extended family through pen and paper notes, broad expressive gestures, hugs and almost constant kisses on the head. We hadn’t learned to sign. If you pressed Harry, asked the wrong question it was easy for him to clam up and ignore you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why at that moment in the apex of our distress and grief, did he choose to share her secret? I wish I had asked him then, or in the months following. He’s gone now, along with anyone else who would be able to tell me any more. I think he wanted us to learn something, not just about her but about ourselves. It&amp;rsquo;s been 13 years since she died and this little incidental family history detail has been sitting in my brain as an unanchored bit of family trivia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was a grandma&amp;rsquo;s girl, it was no secret at all that she showed a strong preference for me, over my two sisters and cousins, and even her own daughters. She was my primary caregiver during my preschool years and lived with me for most of my formative years. She was a major influence on me. This woman who raised me, kept one of the greatest dramas and lessons of her life a secret. Why didn’t she share with me what it was like leaving her family to try something new and have it all crash down? Why didn’t she see that she could be proud of it because she survived it? I can only assume because she considered it a mortifying failure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have my own secret and I have done  a really poor job of keeping and managing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like to write confessional satirical essays and I enjoy sharing them with people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find doing this work on an open forum empowering and healing.  Confessional essay blogs are an artform that excels in supply but lags in demand. When I started this blog anonymously, three years ago, I gradually built up a small following of people. People who found something in my little thoughts and quips. It was nothing big but I was proud of it because I didn’t expect anyone to read me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I lost track of my responsibilities and commitments to my family, and my employer. I broke the rules and I got fired for tweets that I wrote at work to promote my blog persona.  It bears little mention that my insensitive tweet was aimed at highlighting the hypocritical enforcement of a misogynistic gendered dress code. My tweets specifically targeted my workplace and some of my co-workers.  My greatest shame is over what harm I may have caused them. I was fired because of it, well I assume that’s why I was fired.  I was dismissed from my employer of 13 years with nothing but a letter accusing me of harassment and electronic communications policy violations, without explanation, investigation or hearing.  I was denied unemployment. I’m pretty sure my old boss got me black balled in the Industry that I dedicated 13 years of my life to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The day that it happened. I pulled the plug on my blog and my twitter persona Stumped Mom was dead. I told no-one but my family and closest friends what had happened and then in only the vaguest of detail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then I have bounced around from under paying  job to job, a nervous wreck at work, terrified of my secret coming out. Every day I have worn the fear of failure like a suit of wet clothes.Dragging and chaffing my way through my days, desperate to re-establish myself, all teh while leaving a messy trail. My voice was smothered by guilt and shame every task and every email was laden with guilt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I lost another job yesterday, two actually, when I think about it. I could list out a bunch of reasons and circumstances that point away from myself, but I think the real issue has been me and who I am. I haven’t fired because I’m a weirdo, dweeb bitch who says too much and lacks the discipline to properly proof-read and sensor herself. It&amp;rsquo;s because I am all those things and I have been trying to hide it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m done hiding. It&amp;rsquo;s time for me to find my way in the world as my complete self. I have no idea what the consequences will be. Maybe I’ll never work in administration again but maybe that will be good for me. Maybe I’ll make my dreams come true and become a professional humor essayist, comedy writer, pod-caster-bad-bitch. Perhaps I’ll find another hum drum job and be able to plug along without anyone noticing my quiet little blog and what it reveals about my sordid history. Or I’ll start a daycare out of my home or be a dog trainer or grocery store cashier. Whatever happens I’m doing it honestly and openly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re reading me now and you’ve read me before, hi I’m Robin.  If you’ve known me before and you’re just now reading me, hi this is stumped-mom.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret Lives of Barbies</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/06/21/the-secret-lives-of-barbies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 11:55:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/06/21/the-secret-lives-of-barbies/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-secret-lives-of-barbies&#34;&gt;The Secret Lives of Barbies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The first rule about Barbies is that you don’t talk about Barbies&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My peak imaginative play years were dominated by play with Mattel’s Barbie brand plastic dolls. The rooms that I shared with my older sister and then later, with my younger sister were inundated with an overwhelming the flotsam of Mattel parts, and accessories. My mother organized them into mini rubbermaid dressers and organizers. There were drawers for shoes, drawers for clothes, furniture, and spare legs. Barbie’s activities were not restricted to my bedroom, her adventures spilled out to the porch, the yard, the bathroom, the garage and any other playspace she could requisition. Nor did she limit her material wealth to the off the shelf products acquired off of toy shelves, at box stores, thrift shops and garage sales; her imaginary life was furnished with found objects converted to suit her, jewelry boxes as beds, towels, buckets became pools, cereal boxes decks, washcloths were beach towels, paper towels and toilet paper rolls were constructed with tape into furniture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This situation was not unique to my house. I saw it iterated in the homes of cousins, neighbors and classmates. I played with these dolls from as early as I can remember until the age of about eleven and I did so with girls (and very occasionally boys) of many ages ranging from up to six years older or younger than me, at any given time. We would gather in groups of 2-10 and disappear into bedrooms and gardens for hours of quiet cooperative play for hours on end. Every girl I knew had Barbies and every girl knew how to play&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;What was there to know?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was no official rule book but the world of playing Barbies had a social code.The hostess had exclusive rights to her newest or most favored doll, she may show her favor toward a special friend by offering her doll but she was never expected to share it. Doll names, back-stories, bedrooms and clothes had to be picked at the beginning of a play session. You could take anything you wanted from the bins boxes and common areas but once a girl claimed an item as her doll’s you were not to touch it without permission. Ken dolls, however were shared, if you wanted a date with a Ken you needed to reserve it for the night. Any child who could not go with this flow of play was typically kicked off the island. The youngest always seemed to get last pick unless she had an older sibling who was in the mood to pitch for her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Barbie time moved in a series of rapidly simulated days. In a single day our dolls might wake up, do chores, host events, go to work, go camping, go to the moon, go on dates, have sex, get married, get pregnant, give birth and go back to bed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But there was one thing I never saw Barbie do. Barbie did not leave the home. Sure I would take some dolls in the car with me or to a friend’s house. But she never left the bubble of the domestic sphere. We did not talk about Barbie play at school, EVER.  We never wore barbie branded clothing, or dared dream of carrying school supplies. We didn’t tell adults about or fantasy worlds and we certainly didn’t ever answer as to why mom found Barbie and Ken stacked on top of each-other in the dreamhouse sweet without their clothes. We saw almost no depictions of our play in popular culture or media outside of advertisements. There was no equivalent of sandlot for the Barbie set. Somehow these toys dominated the lives of millions of girls for decades, but the way we played with them and the place they had in our lives is hardly discussed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before millennials ruined sex, Applebees, or cars or fast food, or toast, we had it out for Barbie. Barbie’s official fall from dominance over American girl culture was marked by a flurry of news stories in 2014-2015 announcing five consecutive years of dropping sales. I did not read any of these news stories. I passed over the headlines and did little more than register my complete lack of surprise. Barbie’s sentence had been passed in the 90’s it’s just that nobody in the media took notice until her once most dedicated followers achieved the social power to carry it out -the power of motherhood. Sometime around Middle school my friends and I started to distinguish ourselves through deliberate declarations of rebellion against the ultra femme world of pink that marked our Barbie bedecked girlhooods. It was the 90’s baby! GI Jane was a thing Sineade O’connor was out there in her bald headed combat booted glory tearing up pictures of the Pope, Alanis Morisset was shrieking about what you oughta know. We began making our pledges not to give these dolls to our daughters. Our emerging understanding of feminism made it painfully obvious to us that Barbie was detrimental, with her we had been playing out a hypersexualized, white, blonde, body dysmorphic, materialistic version of womanhood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We talked about the absurdity of it all and the alternatives we wanted for our own daughters some day. The sales plummets noted from 2010-2015 bore out the choices that my friends and I were making. We wanted a bigger world for our daughter’s than the one Mattel built for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are some hobbyists and collectors and aficionados who have carried an interest in the dolls into adulthood. But it’s generally relegated to a niche, eccentricity or punchline (see Titus Andromedon). The dolls are still easy to find but as the mother of a seven year old girl, I can tell you that Barbie has moved from the center of girlhood home life into the margins. My own girl has a few barbie style dolls, she thinks the Malibu Dreamhouse animated series is hilarious but she has no idea how large they loomed over my childhood play and they have never made their way onto a Christmas or birthday list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Barbie’s place in our culture has faded into a quiet mist of nostalgia. But unlike the nostalgia that my male counterparts enjoy for their G.I. Joes or Ninja turtles, I hold mine in a quiet secret place. I think my peers may have the same experiences and feelings but I haven’t even spoken with my sisters of in over 20 years.  It was easy to bury our Barbies without discussion. Barbie was so easy to scorn. Like countless inconvenient and complicated women before her she was easy to dispose of and even easier to forget about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We learned from playing with our Barbie’s that we were expected to aspire to be white, blonde, rich, pretty and thin. No sooner did we internalize these lessons than we were told that to aspire to these things was to be shallow, selfish, frivolous and vain. We learned from the way our play was set up and its absence from public discourse, that all the feminine things that Barbie did - the things that captivated our minds and seemed to dominate the lives of the adult women around us - were concerns of little consequence to be excluded from serious discussion. And so we go on living our secret lives and we hardly know we’re doing it, so practiced are we at playing pretend.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Words</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/05/24/words/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 12:18:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/05/24/words/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;words&#34;&gt;Words&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Bloggers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I come write to you in the spirit of rebellion as I declare my unbridled desire to experience the English language at its fullest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week my dear friend Will Qualls (@WKQualls) sent out a tweet asking about how important grammar and convention is to bloggers. Will has a special talent for getting people thinking and my thoughts on this topic can’t be contained to the limitations of twitter. When it comes to grammar, there are not a lot of excuses for bad punctuation and misspellings. Though I tend to play my dyslexia card more often then I probably should.  With AI enabled word processors and an entire internet world of style and writing guides there is no shortage of resources to keep a writer on track.  With a few tutorials and the right programs you two can haz good sentences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But then again who decides what constitutes “good” or “bad” language?  Proper language, like all forms of propriety is dictated by the people in power and when it comes to systems of power I want to burn it all down! Or at least etch my name into the supporting beams of the superstructure. If I’m going to have one calling card, I would like for it to be my anarchistic philosophy on word choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So to Will and all the other aspiring bloggers out there I say. Give me your words! Your righteous, eclectic, dangerous words.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plump and beautiful, shapely, ripe and heavy, oozing with meaning. The fruits of language surround us.  Reach out to pluck them off of the lofty tree tops, stash them in your pocket and bring them out at the out at opportune times for all to consume.  Salvage them from forgotten shady boughs and thrill me as you pair them in unexpected couplings. Cultivate them and delight us with new and unexpected hybrid varieties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This my esteemed cohorts is my declaration of linguistic independence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The established heterodoxy surrounding blogging is that blogs need to be simple and easy to read.  Popular guides and posts implore bloggers to write short paragraphs, use simple sentence structures and write to a third grade reading level. If you want to get those clicks you had better be palatable and easy to digest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t want to be massively appealing or palatable. I refuse to churn out chicken nuggets of content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I invite you to join me in eschewing popular advice. Take a step toward further rhetorical sincerity and own your meaning. Use whatever the fuck words you want. I am reminded of the lessons of the 19th Century French Absurdists. Their explicit disdain for popular criticism laid the groundwork for modern and contemporary art. The French poet Baudelaire famously illustrated the movement in his allegory of the Perfume and The Dog.  He presents his beloved canine companion with the finest perfume in Paris. The pet is rather unsurprisingly revolted by scent.  The poet laments:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ah! wretched dog, if I had offered you a mass of excrement, you would have smelled it with delight, and probably have devoured it. So even you, unworthy companion of my unhappy life, resemble the public, to whom one must never offer delicate perfumes, which exasperate, but carefully raked-up mire’&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Baudelaire and his compatriots unshackled themselves from the norms and expectations of their literary times and in so doing achieved lasting influence (they are well known enough to find their way into this sparsely educated Pacific Northwesterners blog)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I shall employ a sophisticated word to make my intentions clear: Iconoclasm. I reject the accepted wisdom on the basis of its inflexible dogmatism and its basic assumptions on value. Clicks do not equal quality!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My intention is to make m word selections and sentence structure on my own judgments of precision and value.  The search for meaning and the quest to communicate it is far too important to surrender any tools of expression over to the editorial the edicts of conventional wisdom, promotional algorithms, or popularity contests.  Words are too dear to be abandoned so readily&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join me friends in full word liberation.  Don’t jettison a word or expression from use simply because you fear syllables, accents or obscurity.  Bring it out and show it.  We are not dogs or children we can challenge our audiences and ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let us strive for greatness in our language. Let us not be afraid fall on our faces as mis-apply and misspell and even, occasionally, abuse our language. We can dust ourselves radiate connotation with our elegant selections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t take this as a nullification of the axiom, “You must first learn the rules to break the rules”. If working well within the the established wisdom makes you comfortable. Then stick with it.  A musician must learn her scales before she can improvise. Step along the well-trodden path for there is much to be learned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But if you’re ready to break out on your own and blaze new paths.  If you wish to unhitch your vocabulary from monotony.   Then join the rebellion!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bloggers! Give me your words!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If  you are reading this and you are thinking “I do not have these words to display” “where can I find them?” or  “I have them but I don’t know how to use them”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have good news for you friends. The world of language is as endless as it is accessible. Walk into a library and get lost in the groves of great romantic poets and allow yourself to be influenced by their delicate syntax.  Subscribe to a streaming service drill into the reaches of classic 20th century film and extract its vernacular riches.  Wade into the great American novels and sink into their sparse deft sentences. Turn on podcasts and allow yourself be activated by the great orators and debaters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Become word pioneers and make your mark as you teach others what you’ve learned. Try out your multisyllabic finds in an ironic tweet. Revive an antiquated expression you found in a meme generator. Challenge yourself and find ways to feature new words and use them to express your individual thoughts in unconventional ways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join me and feel the thrill of freedom as you run roughshod over the rules as you bend language to your will and make it do your bidding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fellow bloggers. Give me your words!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hand and Foot</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/05/21/hand-and-foot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/05/21/hand-and-foot/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Caution: this post deals with violence toward women&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;hand-and-foot&#34;&gt;Hand and Foot&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m narcissistic enough to assume that for some of you, my recent 10 week absence from posting has been notable and for that reason alone I shall preface today’s posting with a brief explanation on where I have been. I do this not because it happens to be any of your business what I do. For me writing is a habit easily gotten out of and recently, inescapably so. In April I had my second lumbar back surgery in five years. The procedure opened me up both physically and emotionally. Though I had plenty of time to myself, at home for the sort of contemplation that lends itself to blogging, I was too vulnerable to access my voice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am pleased to report that my physical recovery has been coming along quite well thanks, in large part, to the considerate and attentive care of my boyfriend. I’ve never been cared for in such a way and such relational harmony has no business in the blogosphere accept in rare cases, such as this one, where it provides crucial illuminating context. You see, after months of household-life focusing on my limitations and recovery my partner and I found ourselves thrown into a sudden, dramatic and extreme role-reversal, when he didn’t make it home for dinner on a Friday night. He was badly injured in a motorcycle accident. There were three days in the hospital, the first of which he has no memory of and two surgeries. When I brought him home he was scooting on a walker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After two and half weeks, he is now able to handle most of his own care and he is moving about on crutches. He is mostly off of pain medications and we are out of crisis mode. But for over a week days, I kept him organized with his care appointments and medications, cooked and brought him all of his meals, arranged his clothing and helped him dress.  Each of these days was physically, mentally and emotionally exhausting. On one of those nights, while I was bouncing back and forth between my child and my partner’s needs - carrying a tray back to the kitchen, and asking after everyone - I realized that the role I was playing had been modeled for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had seen my aunt tend to my uncle in just this way, day in and day out for my entire childhood. She waited on him, as other family members disapprovingly observed, “hand and foot”. She brought him all of his meals and snacks on a TV tray as he perched on a recliner, remote in hand. She would sit down after doing all the cooking and the serving and pull out a planner and organize the finances and his activities. I never saw him enter the kitchen or the laundry room of his home. Unlike my partner, who is both physically incapacitated and simultaneously grateful and humbled by the constant care, my uncle had no physical or mental disability that prevented him from looking after himself. The dynamic between my uncle and aunt was sickening and dangerous. It was a controlling and abusive relationship, that included observable verbal, emotional, financial and physical abuse. My parents did not stop sending my sisters and I for long summer weeks and weekend sleepovers with their daughter until my uncle put my aunt her in the hospital. He broke her nose so badly she nearly choked to death on the impounded pieces of her sinuses. My mother brought me to see her in the hospital, her face was crushed, she had a tube up through her blackened nostril to deliver oxygen. He sat in the corner of her room glowering her face I was in my teens. “It was an accident,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Family lore informed me that my aunt was not an anomaly. Many of my forebearers and kinswomen worked both in and outside the home under a near constant assault of seemingly inescapable verbal, mental and physical violence - they worked each and every day like this, laboring to appease mercurial and demanding household overlords, while raising children. I can only imagine the way the collapsed into bed each night. These women were not weak, nor were they stupid the, sheer volume of work they put out on a given day testifies to that; they were trapped. Trapped by relationships, expectations and threats. The threats were not just to their physical person. The threats were: social ostracization, poverty, dispossession, and loss of their children be it through state intervention, kidnapping or violence. The threats were carried out by their husbands but enabled by laws, practices assumptions and the people that surrounded them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That same night of my realization after, after helping my partner into bed, I talked with him about how such relationships surely have not died and absolutely live in the recent memory. “How can some people act like patriarchy is gone when people my age were brought up in homes like that?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, as I was taking a break between cleaning the kitchen and putting my daughter to bed, I found out that my sister’s fiance, of seven years, had beaten her the night before, in-front of my other sister and her husband. No two relationships are the same and I am in no position to give an accounting of the complexities of this specific incident but there are parallels in the unequal division of labor, family disapproval and now in my sister’s reluctance to leave. It is easy for me to say that I never liked him much anyway, that I’d complained of his sexism, his drunkenness, and laziness for years but I didn’t see the danger or the urgency in it.  I tried to get her out yesterday. I will try again today. I will ask her, “Are you safe?” and nothing will make me believe she is again.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Guy 20 Questions</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/04/06/white-guy-20-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 12:20:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/04/06/white-guy-20-questions/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;white-guy-20-questions&#34;&gt;White Guy 20 Questions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I put on my cyberslut cape and tights and sit down at my keyboard,  it is with one mission and one mission alone in mind and that is to get us all laid, real good. Most of the time,I like to turn to positive psychology. I serve up digestible short articles with punchy titles and bullet pointed lists that include tips and tricks, aimed at helping my fellow adults navigate the ever changing world of cyber-sex internet dating and sex in a post-monogamy world. However on occasion I find my attention drawn to annoying or negative behaviors that I feel need to be stamped out. Some of them are more serious than others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today’s topic qualifies as a minor one. A pet peeve, but it’s a behavior that I believe will benefit the entire social ecosystem if we address it and it should be pretty easy to address. I am calling this behavior “White Guy 20 Questions.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How am I defining White Guy 20 Questions or WG 20Q? WG 20Q  is when a guy, mostly on the internet, though sometimes in person, attempts to gain the attention of a woman and engage her in conversation by asking her a series of questions which do not relate to each other in any way except for how he feels about the answers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Stumped Mom Why White Guys?That’s not fair you are stereotyping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hear you stumpers but I have slutted it up all over the internet and this is a behavior I have observed exclusively in white, heterosexual men. I also see it as reflective of a persistently self referential worldview and privileged narcissism that I have also observed in white men. I will be taking submissions examples of non-white guy 20Qs in the comments section. But for now hear me out while I continue to define this perverse phenomena:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a simulated WG 20Qs conversation compiled from actual conversations with actual white guys:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WG: Hello&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SM: Hi there what can I do for you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WG: I was just saying hello is all. I saw your blog. I like that you talk about sex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SM: Thank you for reading, I love to hear from readers but so you know I don’t sext with readers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WG: Who said anything about sexting?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SM: You brought up my sex writing and some men try to manipulate me into sexting so I just like to put it out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WG: OH ok well I’m not like that.
WG: How old are you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WG: So what does Stumped Mom mean?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SM: It’s a pun and a multiple play on words but most of all, its a veiled reference to my city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WG: What are your five favorite movies of all time?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SM: (lists first 5 movies she can think of because she doesn’t rank things)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WG: Okay cool. Where are you from?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SM: It’s a riddle, it’s in the name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WG:  Are you Single?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this excerpt we have gotten about five questions deep but that’s where I usually reach the end of my patience. Yes asking people questions is a key part of getting to know them but  can any of our readers tell us where WG went wrong?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of his questions were aimed at trying to figure out if you like what he likes or if you are available to him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You got that right. Asking a woman questions like this, as if you are evaluating a job candidate for the job of your girlfriend, a job to which she isn’t applying, will keep you from ever receiving any applicants for the position. It is uncomfortable, no one wants to submit themselves to your evaluation for relationship compatibility or dating fitness. If that doesn’t convince you just know this; I have never gone on to be good friends, lovers, fuck-besties or even dance partners with a man who has started off his interactions with me by asking me if I like Marvel or DC, what music I listen to or to list my top 5 of anything. It is Absolutely ok to ask a woman questions. If you are trying to get to know a woman try asking her pertinent questions that show you have a sincere interest in getting to know her. Then, when she answers the question, engage with the answer and share something about yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s it that’s the blog for today. This will be on the quiz on Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wake Up Call</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/04/02/wake-up-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 16:23:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/04/02/wake-up-call/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;A word of caution to readers: This post deals with suicidal ideation and impulses to self harm.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-wakeup-call&#34;&gt;My Wakeup Call&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was just three years old, a teenage boy from up the block grabbed me out from the driveway of our duplex and held a switchblade knife to my throat. His identity, his motivations and his current fate are unknown to me. He held me just long enough to let go before my panicked older sister could return with my bemused and skeptical father. My parents didn’t believe that it happened and for years that memory remained mostly buried but it never quite left me. I knew the feeling of cold, sharp steele, below my chin and any time I felt panic or fear I held it up against that seminar memory. For more than 30 years this incidental memory just hung out in the background, I thought I might have made it up in my prolific youthful imagination but my older sister remembers it exactly the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re anything like me, dear readers, you spend a good portion of your mental and emotional energy contemplating the small decisions that add up to your path in life. Purchases, conversations, personal gestures, appointments, trips, and activities clog the mind competing for evaluation. We make choices on all of these things every day hoping to cobble together a meaningful, ethical, fulfilling existence yet our present condition is governed as much by the law of unintended consequences as anything else. Life offers us few moments in life where the time, necessity and weight of a decision is abundantly clear. Those moments are gifts. I call them wake up calls. This is how I got mine:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I married-myself a nice guy from a middle class family, at the tender, idealistic age of twenty. At the time, I felt like I was flying in the face of the notions that my peers had about life and relationships. As far as I knew, I had found something that made me happy and I wasn’t going to let it pass me by just because of some presumed rule book about how old I was supposed to be or how long I should date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For years, from the outside and even from the inside, my marriage looked like a successful partnership. We both finished college, we started careers, bought a house, had a baby all in good careful succession. Sure I had things that I wasn’t happy about but relationships are all about compromise right? Sometimes he spent money in ways I didn’t agree with but it wasn’t like he was out gambling. Yeah, all my vacation time and money was spent on  activities with his family, who blatantly disrespected me but we lived near my family. Okay, so what if made me feel like my family was second class and that they didn’t deserve respect? And well yeah, maybe,  I didn’t trust him with my sexual needs because he shamed me about my body during sex early in our relationship. I mean he made fun of my night terrors, and treated my anxiety like it was an inconvenience but it really was silly right? My ex-husband was a nice guy, he never ever yelled at anybody, and he said I was his equal, he had a job (most of the time). He took the garbage out (when I asked him to). He walked the dog (for a week after I gave birth). I was a broken neurotic person, from a dysfunctional family and he was normal I didn’t really deserve him in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My ex-husband is a charming and socially affable man, he makes friends easily. I on the other hand, am socially anxious and occasionally outlandishly blunt. People viewed him as being charitable and patient with me. He was a nice guy. I was a handful. I accepted that narrative and willfully ignored all the little things. I supported his plethora of hobbies, schemes and dreams as I waited for my turn. I fed his constant unending need for praise while I subsisted off of crumbs  of reluctant approval and cooperation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For fifteen years I lived with a man who treated my emotional needs like they were secondary and I accepted it as normal. Like the proverbial frog in the slowly heating pot I seeped in a slowly warming stew and paid no attention to the rising temperature. In order to live with i, I had pretty much completely cut myself off from my ability to feel my emotions, I was proudly numb. I wore my ability to endure indignity and call it compromise as a badge of pride. But then something happened. The temperature abruptly ticked up and I started to feel the heat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When our marriage hit the rocks, he was the one veering us off the charts. He started behaving erratically and betrayed my trust, by violating explicitly agreed upon boundaries. In the course of a few weeks, he went from saying he was depressed to talking about leaving me. He refused to go to therapy. He refused to make changes to his behavior but said he still wanted to maintain our life and our home together. I couldn’t see that all he was really conflicted about was how to get out and take as much as he could with him on the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this time, I started struggling with thoughts of self harm and suicide. The health professionals I talked to asked me to commit to going to the hospital if I had any urges to self harm. I tried literally begging my ex to come to counseling with me. I literally groveled begging him to tell me what I could change to fix things. My thoughts about hurting myself came from a very dark place in which I saw myself as the source of my partner’s unhappiness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One night things came to a head. We were cleaning up dinner, (ok I was cleaning up dinner while he glowered over me from the other side of the kitchen counter). Our daughter was upstairs and we were having one of our circular arguments. In that moment, in the middle of the argument, I looked at the kitchen knife block and had a very strong suicidal ideation. I formed the intent to use that knife to hurt myself after my daughter’s bedtime. I had formed plan. Somehow the guard rails were still on in my head. I felt the pulse that was the thirty year old memory of a blade at my throat.This was a life threatening situation, but this time my own hand was reaching for the blade. I remembered that this wasn’t good and I was supposed to ask for help. I did as my therapist and doctor had asked me to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I looked at my spouse and in a measured, serious tone, a tone I had used before to in real life and death matters, “I am having suicidal thoughts and urges to hurt myself. I need you to take me to an emergency room.” For background, I had never made this kind of request before, I had struggled with depression and anxiety and sought care on my own. I had no history of destructive attention seeking behavior, rather I had a history of deferring self care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He balked and by balked I mean he made the sound “BALK”
“You’re just manipulating me for attention.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In that second the world cracked open. I was awake. Suddenly I saw clearly. This person cared more about his pride than my physical well being. I didn’t have to un-be to solve this situation. I wasn’t the problem. He was the problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next thing I said to him was, “You need to leave right now,” and that was the moment I divorced from him, in my mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When he left the house, to sleep at a friend’s place, that night I felt like a gigantic weight was lifted from me. The darkness that had been engulfing me that night abated. I went through tremendous grief and angst in the oncoming month and battle, but I knew one thing was right, I could not go on living with that man. I was done with him. I had woken up. I hear about messy divorces that have back and forth efforts at reconciliation there was zero doubt in my mind my relationship was over because I woke up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to the ways of love we all have to make our own mistakes and learn our own lessons. But as I look back, I know that one of the things that lulled me to sleep was the ridiculously low standard of expectation I had developed for the men in my life. The role models I had for fatherhood and marriage were scoundrels, drunks, and child abusers. I had uncles who terrorized my cousins and aunts, and a drunken and absent father and grandfather’s who’s sins I will not list. The women in my family treated me like I had truly won some sort of lottery for finding myself a man who didn’t do these things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bar we have set for middle class white men to be considered good husband’s and family men is ridiculously low. Have job, do a few chores and refrain from hitting anybody and you’re considered an A+ catch. We let them say they are babysitting their own kids and throw a parade when they do chores. We expect their wives to organize their social lives, set up a perfect facebook and instagram image of the family, and keep everything in order. They help with the just some of the big chores around the house but in the end they are helping and aren’t they precious for it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumpers if you are living with a relationship where you are made to count yourself as blessed just on account of the absence of blatant abuse, I hope you don’t have to come as close as I did to true peril before your wake-up call comes. Taking out the trash and watching the baby twice a week so you can go to the gym does not a hero make. It can be better and you do deserve more.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Not MeToo Its You</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/30/its-not-metoo-its-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 09:30:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/30/its-not-metoo-its-you/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;it-s-not-metoo-it-s-you&#34;&gt;It’s Not #MeToo It’s You&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Men,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I understand some of you feel like you are having a hard time, lately. Things that you have always taken for granted are being questioned. The days headlines are reporting an accelerating decline in Male sexual activity in America. Some of you feel like you aren’t quite sure what you get to laugh at, what you get to say and who you get to touch. You’re being asked to think about your place in the world and question how much of your achievements are the results of hard work and what should be attributed to unfair social advantages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I witnessed this anguish last week. A gentleman I shall call Roger was seated across from me at a public HR training workshop last week. Poor Roger was a middle aged man white man struggling with the changes in culture he was experiencing in his industry. This #MeToo stuff was polluting every conversation. The young millenials he works with seemed to be in contest with each other to be the most “Wo” and the women that he worked with -he just couldn’t ever tell what could be construed as sexism.  How could he establish trust with his team and authority as a supervisor if he felt like he was about to get into trouble all the time? Poor Roger, his instructor and his classmates worked to keep him on track with the curriculum and help him understand the basics of respect and team building in a multicultural workplace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear old Roger, though he lives and works in what could be seen as a relatively small city and I had never met him before,I found out through the grapevine that he was being forced out of his job because he’s had multiple accusations of sexual harassment. This guy just couldn’t cut it in a world where he isn’t supposed to corner women, put his arm around them, touch them on their waist and hips, and say inappropriate and rude things about their sexual orientations. And what’s worse? Oh Poor Roger this is the second job Roger has lost thanks to #MeToo he got forced out of his office because he was having an affair with a junior co-worker half his age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are lots of Rogers out there. Men who just can’t seem to adjust to the needs and feelings of everyone else around you. Some of you have even found yourselves drawn into creepy sub-corners of the internet so you can gripe about the women who won’t have sex with you. The most extreme denizens of these dark corners are inspired to commit mass casualty terrorist attacks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am writing to tell you that I hear you and I understand your message. You’re confused, you’re uncomfortable, you have been dispossessed and you feel like you are being punished for the crimes of others. You’re afraid of the consequences of your actions. You don’t know when your sexual desires and activities will be turned around against you to shame you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well boys, welcome you to the club. The discomfort you are experiencing is the result of a fraction of the discomfort you have been collectively inflicting upon others, being displaced in your direction. You have been living your whole life like an airline passenger taking up half of the seat next to you and now you are being tapped on the shoulder and told you have to share the armrest. Yet for some reason, some of you are shouting and pouting about it as if you’ve been kicked off the plane and since you’re shouting and making such a tool of yourself the flight attendants are calling in the air marshals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ve been asked to speak more politely to people. To stop making rape jokes, and to desist in talking over the women and people of color in your lives and for what seems like the first time ever, some of you are being made examples of, while others are having to face the consequences of your actions. I understand that you’re scared and you want someone or something to blame the hard Truth is its not #MeToo its you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A man on the internet asked me if women weren’t getting laid because men weren’t making moves. I take a look around and I see plenty of heterosexual relationships around me humming along. I go out with my girlfriends and men still notice me and them, we still get asked to dance, and receive compliments from strangers. Sex has not stopped, blow jobs are still being given, kindly ladies on the internet are generating free content designed to help you have better sex more often. There is no crisis of flirtation. More women are having sex then men right now which means that some men and lots of ladies are doing just fine. So how are they doing it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In truth not all men are sexual predators or serial harassers or internet trolls. There are plenty of men who have figured out that the secret sauce to getting by with life and winning the affections of the ladies is mutual respect. If treating other people like their common humanity is equal to yours come naturally, you probably haven’t been experiencing any problems. If you want to know how to get by in the #MeToo era without ending up like Roger. The simple answer is don’t act like Roger. Take responsibility for your actions and respect the boundaries of others not because you are scared of the consequences but because virtue is its own reward.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Wide World Of Sex Apps</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/17/the-wide-world-of-sex-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 10:58:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/17/the-wide-world-of-sex-apps/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-wide-wild-world-of-sex-aps&#34;&gt;The Wide Wild World of Sex Aps&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Caution: The following post deals with frank talk about sex prudes need not proceed.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beloved Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s say you’ve read my background posts, done some thinking, had a talk with your partner (if you have one) and maybe you’ve explored fantasy literature and even got yourself a copy of the Ethical Slut, and now you’re feeling ready for the next step, you want to get out there and explore the world of kink and group sex hookups. It can be a scary and difficult to navigate step. My greatest joy in life is to help you with what I know. And today I am going to share some of my knowledge about the ways to enter into kink and group exploration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The apps and sites: When it comes to online life there is a plethora of hookup apps. The most popular in my area are Feeld and Fetlife.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://fetlife.com&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fetlife&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; markets itself as an online community for kinksters. Many of the people I have encountered here identify with their sexual activity as a “lifestyle”.  I have personally found that conversations here are very transactional. The people on Fetlife tend to be very experienced and are specific about what they want and what they need. They usually want to share explicit pictures right away. This can be a great place to cruise if you are interested in live cyber play with hetero sexual couples, but I’ve never personally converted it to a meetup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feeld&lt;/strong&gt;, is a smartphone app that was created to be the tinder for people looking for threesomes, but since it’s popularity has grown there are a lot more orientations and meetups here. You can find all sorts of people on feeld and many of them have never actually participated in any kind of group sex for a lot of people feeld is their first introduction, the response rate on the app is low and in spite of being functional for many years it suffers from frequent crash glitches. That being said my partner and I do use the app to meet and date women together a few times a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The general pitfalls and hangups of our sexual culture are prevalent and in many ways operative in the online dating market for hookup and group sex apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you download Feeld and start swiping it won’t take you long to discover that there is an oversupply of male-female couples seeking single females and oversupply of single males seeking male-female couples. This phenomenon is so exaggerated that couples frequently list themselves as single females,in order to make more matches and many couples will disingenuously advertise that they are seeking other couples and then target just the female in an attempt to get her to engage in a threesome without her partner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My theory is that this clearly observable market misalignment is driven by our social sexual factors.  It is beyond cliche that every man fantasizes about having threesomes with two women. Our sexual culture also encourages bisexual or heteroflexible behavior in women but discourages it in men. This seems to play out in the oversupply of mf couples seeking women. But what I have found is that women do enjoy group sex and women that enjoy sex with multiple women generally enjoy sex with multiple men. Thanks to slut shaming and stigma this kind of desire is difficult for women to express. I have personally experienced male partners shaming me for enjoying sex with multiple male partners. Few heterosexual men want to “share” a female partner with another man. Single men are generally interested in threesomes with couples but few couples want to welcome single men.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which leads us to some of the nomenclature of threesome culture many of the terms beli the market issues:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unicorns:&lt;/strong&gt; single women or partnered women who have sex with couples as singles. Since these women are in such high demand finding one is as rare and magical as finding a unicorn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unicorn hunters:&lt;/strong&gt; male-female couples seeking single women&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cucks or cuckolds&lt;/strong&gt;: Men who enjoy sharing their female partners or watching their female partners with other men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cuck-Queens:&lt;/strong&gt; Women who enjoy having a cuckold partner and or dominating a cuckold partner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hotwives:&lt;/strong&gt; married women who are in open relationships or are partnered with cuckold men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sissys- Male:&lt;/strong&gt; submissives who seek humiliation play, this often includes cross dressing in women’s underwear, or doing chores and other female associated activities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some of you this may be more than you ever wanted to know about the online world of group sex hookups. For others this might seem like a pedestrian and oversimplified summary. What I hope is that for a few of you this guide can help you in your your journey. I can’t advise anyone what choices they should make.  What ever you choose I do urge patience and compassion. Sex in all contexts is a risky and emotionally complicated. When it comes to adding multiple partners patience, compassion and communication are required. Playmates aren’t toys or objects or a means to an end they are all people, with their own dreams fantasies and desires. As always feel free to let me know your thoughts in the comments section or to find me on Twitter. I am available for questions from respectful readers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Stumped Mom&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fallen Stars</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/04/fallen-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 19:19:35 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/03/04/fallen-stars/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This weekend HBO premiered Leaving Neverland, A documentary series, that tells the stories of the men who survived Michael Jackson’s grooming and sexual abuse. I don’t have HBO go so I haven’t seen it. Instead I’m watching American Crime Stories: the Trial of OJ simpson. The Simpson story of is the fall of another cultural icon and a sad moment for our national media culture. The chatter about Leaving Neverland on new sites and on social media all week makes it pretty clear that the picture of Jackson is damning. I was overcome this weekend by the feeling that my generation has become bereft of heros. Which brought me to wonder, now that so many of our cultural heroes and leaders have been exposed as creeps, how many of my grandparents heroes and history&amp;rsquo;s giants were creeps too?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jackson joins a list of powerful men who have been accused, exposed convicted or re-examined in the last two years: Michael Jackson, Woody Allen, Bill Cosby, R. Kelly, Bill Clinton, Kevin Spacey, just to name a few. Catholic priests, boy-scout leaders, doctors coaches, athletes,pop stars, sitcom actors, newsmen (and I mean men) and politicians have all been caught and exposed. What is known cannot be unknown. In any corner of society where power, money, and celebrity are concentrated in the hands of men, you will also find sexual exploitation and violence. It is primarily perpetrated by men but also enabled and facilitated by women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The victims are disproportionately female, disabled, LGBTQ people, and people of color. The politics of of patriarchy, gets plaid out onto the bodies and souls of our most vulnerable and it is happening at epidemic rates. RAIIN gives a really good breakdown of the statistics &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.rainn.org/statistics/victims-sexual-violence&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a little Wiki &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Child_sexual_abuse&#34;&gt;fact&lt;/a&gt; to ruminate upon: “The global prevalence of child sexual abuse has been estimated at 19.7% for females and 7.9% for males.” For contrast the global prevalence of red-headedness is estimated at 2% (Its 50% if you live in the Marvel Universe). I’m no statistician but I think it’s pretty fair to say that based on the numbers I can find, chances are you know more sex abuse victims then you do redheads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We could pretend that this is a new problem; that somehow sexual violence has just recently developed. Many Americans are eager to resurrect an imaginary past. At the same time #metoo exploded online people were dawning MAGA hats and expressing their intent to return to a time of greatness. The taste of nostalgia is sweet but its recipe calls for ignorance. One of the ways the past can shine brightly in our memories is that we can harken back to a time before we knew about the evils of the world. My own childhood once seemed innocent time in my family history to me, a time before any of my cousins became drug addicts or recidivists. But those sweet feelings toward times past were overshadowed as I became an adult and learned the sordid bits of family history that were hidden from me as a child. Right now as a culture we are all growing up. We are looking at things as they were then with the knowledge that we have now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t need the celebrity cases to tell us there is a problem. Our collective and personal histories tells us we know better. Sexual abuse and exploitation have deep roots in the history and structure of our society. We can see it in the statutes with laws that until only recently protected the rights of men to do as they pleased with the women and children under their control. Rape by definition wasn’t considered possible within the context of marriage until the &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Marital_rape_(United_States_law)&#34;&gt;middle of the 20th century&lt;/a&gt;.
The laws for statutory rape in our country are written for the protection of the families investment in their children’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Statutory_rape&#34;&gt;future marriage prospects&lt;/a&gt;.  We’ve heard it in the stories of Native American Children who have been ripped from their homes and submitted to horror upon horror. And the untold number of slaves who were submitted to institutionalized rape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure we know Albert Einstein had a coercive sexual relationship with his cousin. John F. Kennedy enjoyed movie stars and prostitutes alike, and Babe Ruth was violent toward women. We think we know the biographies of the great men of the past. But how many untold secrets have been buried with victims who remained silent into their graves? Personally I’ve been at the funerals of two men who I knew were abusers, their families and victims knew what they were, but they lived their lives without facing real consequences for their actions. These men were members of the so called, “Greatest Generation.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is known cannot be unknown. We can’t go back, and if we did we would find ourselves in a time where open secrets were everywhere. A time when the only protections women and children had was the patronage of men. We can’t go on celebrating the past and recognizing its heros without acknowledging the system of sexual coercion that they participated in. Our grandfathers and their grandfathers hurt people and our grandmother’s helped. That is our collective history and no amount of nostalgia can undo it. The sooner we accept this and recognize that its a problem born out of inequality, the sooner we can start building something better to replace it. Our stars have fallen but together we can erect a new sky.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like A Girl</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/28/like-a-girl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 11:00:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/28/like-a-girl/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;like-a-girl&#34;&gt;“Like a Girl”&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now is a good time to be a girl. The future is female, so we are told. Girl boss is a hashtag and girls can be anyone they want to be. Thanks to a razor maker’s clever marketing, masculinity is toxic now. My daughter enjoys wearing glittery pink sneakers with jeans and a tutu and a boy’s superhero t-shirt to school and no one bats an eye accept to compliment her on her superior sense of style. I assure her there are as many ways to be a girl or a woman as their are women. I tell her these words but I speak them as an article of faith, it’s a promise but not a guarantee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But there are other words in my head:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sit like a lady&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You must be real fun at parties”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You’re just a tomboy”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Are you wearing makeup?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Why don’t you wear makeup?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You’re too young for a bra!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Why aren’t you wearing a bra?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We can’t teach girls martial arts then they’ll go around and beat up the boys”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You’re prettier when you smile”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Girls shouldn’t have short hair”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You hit like a girl”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Your clothing is distracting”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Can you make me a drink?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You throw like a girl”
“Hello princess”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Women can’t fight”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“She-male!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If I owned a business I would never hire any women”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This list of cringe inducing phrases, insults and compliments is selected from my girlhood but also from my daughters. Can you tell the difference? Which ones have been meant for me and which ones have been meant for her? It is a bit of a trick question because some of them overlap. The world of girls that I grew up in was one where femininity was both prescribed and disdained. This world isn’t dead or gone. Today girls are told they can be anything that they want to be but its still made very clear to them that the very best thing to be is a man. Let’s explore a few of these phrases and see if we can find out how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Can you get me a drink?”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I work in a field that is traditionally male. Last year, I was invited to speak at an industry luncheon. A man asked me to serve him a drink during the pre-meeting networking hour. I was wearing company brand apparel and one of the nametags they give you at these business luncheons, my name was on the Agenda and the meeting notices. “I’m sorry” he said, “I thought you were a waitress.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My boss has taken me aside to tell me that some of the men at work have complained that my clothing is distracting. I dress the same and at times more conservatively than other women in the office with thinner more athletic or boyish figures. She said I was reverse sexually harassing the men with my clothes. Somehow or other I was too female for my workplace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“You’re prettier when you smile”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were on a double-family outing with my ex-husband’s best friend and his son when my daughter tripped and fell. I picked her up and dried her tears and I was telling her that she was going to be fine. Her little bestie’s dad bent over and said to her, “You know, you’re prettier when you smile.” She was just three years old and a man she trusted suggested she change her expression in order to make herself more pleasing to look at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My mother claws came out, my blood ran cold, I looked at him and said, and my expression deadened as I looked at  him and said, “Don’t you ever say that to her again.” When I told my ex-husband what happened he said that I was in the wrong. His friend couldn’t have ever meant it like that he wasn’t that kind of guy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“You must be real fun at parties”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is that phrase familiar to anyone else? It isn’t a compliment, it’s sarcasm lacks irony. I’ve heard it from men when they have realized I am not going to take shit from them and or I am not going to sleep with them. It’s a parting shot meant for the wrong kind of woman. The woman who isn’t game. The one who doesn’t know her place. A woman who doesn’t smile enough, who doesn’t laugh enough. Who doesn’t take a joke. No one wants to be that kind of woman. That kind of woman is a nag, she doesn’t put out, she doesn’t do that thing you like in bed, or like sports, or get along with her man’s friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My life and all of its decisions is haunted by the wrong kind of woman. She is at turns not smart enough or too smart to be fun. She is an obsessive and a slob. She’s also a prude yet often a slut. This wrong sort of woman wants all of the attention but can’t take a joke. She’s everywhere and nowhere but everyday her presence is felt in every decision I make. “Don’t be that kind of woman,” whispers a little voice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“If I owned a business I would never hire any women”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few months ago I was driving my father home from one of his frequent hospital stays for COPD and heart disease, when he told me that he just wouldn’t hire any women if he owned a business because that is the only way to be safe from sexual harassment claims. He was completely serious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For as long as I can remember, I can recall an acute feeling of being a disappointment to my parents. I had a strong sense that whatever I was, I was supposed to be something else. Feedback from relatives about the notable lack of sons in my family got the message across. My parents needed sons and my sister’s and I were not fitting the bill. Dad served an exaggerated form of masculinity, his dominant emotional expression being anger. Relating to little girls on their level always appeared to be a stoop for him. To spend time with dad meant bringing him a beer while watching the football game, going along for the fishing trip or helping with the home or car repair. Helping usually meant holding a flashlight and holding tools while he barely tolerated a female presence. I wish I could say that as an adult, this feeling hasn’t left me; rather it has followed me out  into the world and it is reinforced from the outside on a regular basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know men who are secure in their masculinity, they walk around with a calm self-assurance that whatever other people think they are exactly who they are supposed to be. People have told me I am strong woman, and a person to be admired, for various reasons some  I judge to be more valid than others. But no matter what I do, I never feel that I have it right. There are billions of ways to be a woman but none of us are quite “right.” We live in a world where people shout that we have equality, and then whisper to us that we can never be right. There is no such thing as being secure in femininity, it is by social definition an insecure state. I want my daughter to live in a world where she can be anything and do anything but more than that I want her to live in a world where she can be a woman and be as feminine as she wants to be and never be judged the lesser for it. I want for every woman’s way to be the right way.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Defense Of Guys</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/23/in-defense-of-guys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 11:21:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/23/in-defense-of-guys/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-defense-of-guys&#34;&gt;In Defense of “Guys”&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come along with me stumpers, as I take a nerdy deep dive into the intersection of regional identity, feminism and language.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First off I am going to reveal one of my thinly veiled secrets. I am from the Pacific Northwest (PNW). My whole family is from the Pacific Northwest. My family roots in the PNW go back four generations. If you look at the population trends for the Northwestern States, the growth, powered by transplants from other states has been explosive over the course of my lifetime. Just by the numbers, lifetime natives to my community are a minority in-spite of a relatively low birth rates; the population has tripled in the last 30 years. We locals are so outnumbered we are like unicorns here and just knowing one of us gives other people access to bragging rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Believe it or not, those few of us who have lived here our whole lives have a &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pacific_Northwest_English&#34;&gt;distinct dialect&lt;/a&gt;. one that the media doesn’t bother portraying.  Jack Nicholson did not bother to learn it for &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pc0_Xnvl3t4&#34;&gt;One Flew Over The Cuckoo&amp;rsquo;s Nest&lt;/a&gt;, an A story, written, set and filmed in Oregon. Can you imagine Goodwill hunting if everyone had Southern accents? I suspect the people of boston would have nothing to do with them apples. But Jack’s portrayal of an Oregonian with a New Jersey accent is somehow film history legend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Pacific Northwestern erasure impacts perceptions all over the country. My first time venturing into the South, I was told I sounded Canadian. Gross!  Being from the PNW, I know plenty of Canadians and this confluence is offensive to all parties involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here in the Northwest, we do have one cinematic dialect-hero and he’s no Jack Nicholson. We have to go outside the arthouse and que up a copy of Goonies to hear John Matuszak
as Sloth famously deliver our native battle cry,. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4Vv5CsP1pAg&#34;&gt;“HEY YOU GUYS!!”&lt;/a&gt; in a wisconsin accent that is just obscured enough to pass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which brings us to my particular bone to pick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certain feminists hailing from parts east of the Mississippi have started to spread the notion that the use of the word “guys” when addressing mixed gendered company is sexist. Like in this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.vox.com/2015/6/11/8761227/you-guys-sexism-language&#34;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; written by Washington D.C. based Vox media in which a feminist expert, from New York,is consulted to tell us why “guys” is sexist. She argues pretty effectively that by applying the male perspective to mixed gendered groups we re-enforce the patriarchal assumption that male equals normal. We are encouraged to use this list of alternatives instead:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Folks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everyone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleagues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gang&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Y&amp;rsquo;all&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guys and girls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As socially forward as these feminists are trying to be I am afraid I must report that they have an awful lot in common with gender rigid social regressives. The first people, I encountered who ever objected my use my use of guys were southern women.Way back in 2002 I was shocked and mortified to be chided by my sister’s in law for saying “hey guys!” when they were in the room. The were Southern ladies afterall, not guys! How dare I imply that there were of another gender. These same women raised a fuss when I didn’t take my husband’s name. I could not wrap my name around their perspective. I did not mean guys as in male people. I began to realize that in the Pacific Northwest the use is so pervasive and common we really do not perceive it as being gendered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning I walked into my office and greeted the two women in the room with a  “Good morning guys”.One being a Native Oregonian Unicorn and the other a 40 year PNW  resident, they replied with a “Hey!” and all was right in the beautiful PNW.” Guys” has, for all intents and purposes, lost its gendered meaning in my region. You can convene a troupe meeting of all female girl scouts in the PNW with a, “Listen up you guys,” and each and every one of those little girls is going pipe down and put her eyes forward. (That’s another one how many of you guys say “pipe, down eyes forward?”)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another distinguishing characteristic of PNW natives is a particular form of niceness. We puzzle visitors from the East Coast, with our affable attitudes. However, we aren’t actually as nice as our reputation would suggest. We tend to be super subtle and passive aggressive and East Coast, and even Southern California natives don’t realize that they are missing, social cues which are meant to inform them when they are out of line. A typical Northwesterner will let you run around making an ass of yourself, for years, before directly saying anything to you about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Years have gone by and with the exception of a quirky satirical sketch comedy series on a cable network, in which two part-time Portlanders portray a version of our local culture, that is largely the product of the population explosion over the last 20 years; the rest of the country doesn’t seem to notice that we exist with our own regional identity. Some of these non-Northwesterners are labeling key features of our regional dialect as patently sexist without bother to consult with people from the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I’m going to say it. You guys are being real jerks! You have no right to tell us to surrender or change the use of a key part of speech that is distinctive to our region.
Language does matter, but one of the things that makes it matter, is how its meaning is social and regional context. Just as a “fag” isn’t a homesexual slur if you are an English person looking for a smoke. Guys are not a group of men if the speaker is a person from the Pacific Northwest is speaking in the second person plural.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m still down with feminism and I’m going to do plenty of other feminist stuff like: write about sex from a woman’s perspective, promote gender and queer equity, speak out about the prevalence of sexual assault, stand up for reproductive access, and refuse to accept heterosexual relationships with an unequal division of emotional labor, as inevitable. But I am not giving up a part of my speech that is one of the remaining remnants of a local identity. You won’t be able to pry “guys” out of my cold dead lips, but it will live past me in my writing and on in my child and you can’t stop it!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valentines Day For Dummies</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/11/valentines-day-for-dummies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 10:48:02 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/11/valentines-day-for-dummies/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;valentines-day-for-dummies&#34;&gt;Valentines Day For Dummies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dearest Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I wish one thing for you all this Valentine’s Day it is for you all to achieve sexual satisfaction be it alone, or with a partner. Valentine’s Day is perhaps the most awkward day of the calendar year and the sexual revolution hasn’t done it any favors. Presently, the prevailing winds indicate that it is a day for children to trade heart themed and punny pre-made notes, for teenagers to run around confused and for adults to express their affection through themed gifting or feel lonely if they are single. I can’t help everybody. But I believe as a female who has been in more than one long term relationship with men I can offer some valuable perspective to hetersexual men in relationships with women.
&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/VDay.jpeg&#34; style=&#34;width:310px;height:204px;float:left;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 10px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are single and have your eye on someone. I highly encourage you to use this day as your opportunity to take a big risk and make a grand romantic gesture. For it to work you have to commit all the way and take a big risk. If you aren’t feeling it, use the day on yourself. Disconnect from social media and go buy yourself a new sex toy. Tune the world out and do things you like for yourself. You deserve it. The rest of this post  is aimed toward men in long term relationships because they seem to need the help more than anyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Much ado has been made about so called high maintenance girlfriends and wives what to do for them or about them on Valentine’s Day. A discussion of the sexism of the term “high maintenance” will need to be tabled for another day - my goal now,  as ever, is to get us all laid real good. So for today I am going to put a bandaid over the sexism of the whole setup and focus on how to work within it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why does today’s modern liberated woman still look forward to gifts and expressions of adulation on February 14th? To this question I ask another question: does everybody not remember Christmas? How much of Christmas was powered by the emotional labor, blood sweat and tears of so many women and femmes? Don’t you see that we’re tired? We keep card lists, we wrap gifts, we plan dinners, and trips, we stay up late, we handle mothers-in-laws judgemental passive aggression. If you are in a relationship with a woman and you can’t seem to figure out what her deal is, get wise to &lt;a href=&#34;https://thebodyisnotanapology.com/magazine/50-ways-people-expect-constant-emotional-labor-from-women-and-femmes/&#34;&gt;emotional labor&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Valentine’s Day offers women in heterosexual relationships a day of respite and escape from emotional labor a guaranteed chance at being “treated” to adoration without having to set the whole damn thing up herself. If a special woman in your life seems drained, touched out, stressed, and anxious and she isn’t as sexualy responsive as she once was, take this Valentine’s Day as your wakeup call. It is time to do some emotional homework and lift the burden from your partner. No specific products or purchases are required to implement to do this. But you are going to have to do some planning, and you may have to practice some communication skills that don’t come naturally to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom’s guide to nailing Valentines Day and getting laid real good”:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do some planning. Women do a lot of the planning work in our society whether it’s in your relationship or in her family or at work. Plan something and when I say plan something I don’t mean say, “Hey babe I think we should go out on this date where do you want to go?” You need to identify a time frame, a place and an activity and the food. The only thing you should bother her about is setting aside the time. If she has kids set up child-care. The place can be home, the activity can be netflix and the food can be pizza but do the planning. Make the time the space and the effort for her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Did I mention the space? If your partner is a mother especially take time to get her out of her every day space, or at the very least clean it for her. Even if you feel like the chores in your relationship are divided evenly women experience tremendous social pressure to have a clean home and any time she is in the home cleaning anxiety can derail any chance of romance. If you don’t cohabitate clean up your place and host her, if you do consider getting a hotel room in your own city. Some of the hottest dates I have ever had have been in hotel rooms. Personally I am more likely to experiment with new things when I am not at home. And by experiment I mean, multiple partners, toys, anal, pornography and all those goodies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of your planning process. Talk your partner her about her fantasies and sexual needs. Read up in my &lt;a href=&#34;https://stumpedmom.com/2018/12/11/beginning-fantasy-talk/&#34;&gt;fantasy talk series&lt;/a&gt;  to get some ideas on basics. Try to find out about the various phases of sex and if there is anything she would like more or less of during each of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Surrender all pressure and expectation. Make yourself a zen master of romance by concentrating on gratifying your partner. Practice mindfulness and enjoy every moment of intimacy you have for what it is. If she touches your knee, try not to think about if she is going to move her hand to your groin look at her face and think about how nice her touch feels. Do not think of your dinner conversation as foreplay even if you are flirting. Concentrate on what it is you are enjoying about that moment. Focusing on the end goal will make it harder to achieve&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lay on the admiration. Women are bombarded with messages about their bodies and how they should and shouldn’t be. It is time for you to give her some verbal appreciation. The key to doing this successfully to make it detailed and specific. If this is unnatural for you take some time and think about it and even write it down. What about your partner sets her apart from others? Don’t just say “you have nice hair,” a seven year old could come up with that. Sure you can compliment her hair but be specific, include details about colors, textures, smells. Then add feeling words and action words. What emotions do you experience when you are near her? What are you motivated to do by these emotions?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If things are going well once you have given your lady some admiration you can start with som verbal foreplay. Work from those areas of admiration that you started with and tell her how you would like to touch her or be touched where and why.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Concentrate on some no pressure body care or physical intimacy. You know, shit like: snuggling, back rubs, baths and stuff. If you do decide to get in deep into beauty self care or grooming do some research and make sure you do it right. It will not be a treat for her if she has to talk you through it and teach you how.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rest, my friends, is up to you knowing the basic mechanic and this isn’t exactly that kind of blog. This advise isn’t exclusive for Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day in fact it is best when applied frequently and liberally throughout the calendar year. Love is for every day and I wish you all the best of it for yourselves and the special people in your lives.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s His Story</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/10/whats-his-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 09:36:39 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/10/whats-his-story/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-s-his-story&#34;&gt;What’s His Story?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last night, during his annual address to the United States Congress, in a move aimed at retaining his party’s grip over the religious right, the Kleptocrat who holds executive office of the world’s most powerful oligarchy, took aim at women’s rights. He piously declared the sanctity of all life, even the unborn (though let us not speak of diabetes patients in puerto rico) and attacked laws passed in New York and Virginia aimed aimed at securing access to reproductive care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations Stumped Mom you did it I!  wrote a paragraph about national politics without saying “President” or “Trump!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok stumpers here is the deal. Republicans are out to get women, because stoking our patriarchal culture’s, ancient fear of women and their reproductive power is a proven way to gain the loyalty of the people most deeply invested in that hegemony. This makes it so much easier to keep their voters from noticing that they are supporting tax and regulation policies that don’t benefit their class. It’s the oldest political bait and switch in the book. I expect if you read stumped mom you’re the kind of person that gets this but this piece is a polemic and one of the conventions of the form is to garner the support of your readers for a new argument by laying a foundation of shared context with your audience before introducing novel ideas. So now that we’ve established that people on the right use abortion stigma to heighten fear and hatred of women in order to get what they want and we don’t like that how do combat it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our best bet at killing this political strategy and seeing a more just and equitable world for our children is to take aim at the cultural root of the problem, the vilification of women. It is much harder to villainize people if you have relationships with them. If you hear their stories and see where they are in your everyday lives it is harder to attack their interests. Just as the path toward legal protections for LGBTQ people has been laid with each coming out the struggle for women’s reproductive rights relies on women coming out and declaring their personal connection to reproductive access.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.johnstonsarchive.net/policy/abortion/uslifetimeab.html&#34;&gt;According the the Johnston Archive&lt;/a&gt; “25-28% of women ages 15-64 in the U.S. today have had at least one abortion in their lifetime.” At least one in four women has a story to tell. I’m all about transparency so I will disclose that that access to comprehensive reproductive education and effective long term birth control,as well as luck has so far meant that I have never had an unplanned, or medically complicated or dangerous pregnancy. This is not my story but I do know and love women who have these stories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A very small portion of those women have been brave enough, even with their identities veiled to tell their stories. But the work is being done great journalism like this Article in &lt;a href=&#34;https://slate.com/human-interest/2018/07/the-abortions-we-dont-talk-about-six-slate-women-tell-their-stories.html&#34;&gt;Slate&lt;/a&gt;  These stories when told by real women set fire to the straw woman who is easy to dismiss and hate. They give faces and context and push out the image of the selfish, reckless heartless, narcissistic harlot the religious right wants to restrain, punish and regulate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A funny thing though. It didn’t take long for #notall men and #mentoo to pop up when women started telling their stories of sexual abuse and harassment to try to counter the narrative with a so called men’s perspective on sexual violence, oppression and abuse. But there is a strange silence among men surrounding their relationships with abortion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One in four women in the United States has terminated a pregnancy and they didn’t get their on their own. Where are the men’s voices? A woman’s right to choose is absolutely her own and the story of her choice is hers and no-one else’s to tell. But for every woman that comes forward and tells the story about how an abortion saved, her health, a career, a relationship, her position in her family, hardships on her other children, there is a sperm source that has at the very least been spared two decades of child support. Whenever I see some young male luminary, influencer or disrupter espousing his ideas and trumpeting his success I quietly ask myself could he be one of them? We will not speak of those cretins who have pressured women, or manipulated or abused them into one choice or another they don’t have a place in any conversation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The forced birthers have men on their side who stand up and tell their sob stories of the babies they never got to have because the Jezebel’s who carried them chose to terminate the pregnancy. But there must be millions of men whose educations, careers, relationships, and livelihoods have been preserved by a woman’s choice to have an abortion a choice that they supported. I know this because I know at least three in my own life. One for every woman I know has made the choice and I can see how their lives would be completely different were it not for her access to abortion. These are not men grieving for the child that they never had with that girlfriend or ex wife they now barely know. They are young men moving forward with their lives and careers and forging healthy relationships&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can see why they don’t speak, on one side they don’t want to insert themselves into a discussion of women’s bodies and rights and on the other they do not want to be outed to the people who will judge them as sinners; but right now we are engaging in conversations about reproduction as if it only impacts women. This only reinforces the social assumption that babies are ultimately a woman’s responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I am issue an opportunity and a challenge to you men. The men whose wives have been saved by a medically necessary abortion, or those of you who have kept it a secret. A secret only known to the woman you drove to the clinic. Own it as part of your story. Whether that means telling at least one other person that you trust, writing a check to planned parenthood or outing yourself to your church. Own it. If a woman made the choice to abort a pregnancy you started and you are glad she did, don’t walk around pretending that abortion is none of your business because as long as you have that privilege, a woman’s rights will always be threatened. Your silence and inaction threatens the movement that has enabled your success and unless you are contributing to it. You’re a free rider.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Creeper</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/07/my-first-creeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 19:44:45 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/07/my-first-creeper/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-first-creeper&#34;&gt;My First Creeper&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m about to let you in behind the scenes of StumpedMom.com. While the casual or even careful reader could never be blamed for assuming I pull this entire website out of my ass. I try to organize my ideas and put them out in an organized and orderly fashion. I use an Airtable (Please sponsor me) spreadsheet to organize my work from the idea stage, through to publishing. I should probably be plugging in and tracking metrics but meh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/air_table.jpg&#34; style=&#34;width:310px;height:561px;float:left;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 15px;&#34;&gt;
Sometimes I have more ideas than I can write about, at once and to get myself to focus I put those ideas into a list called “undeveloped”. On days like today, when I feel like writing but I’m not fired up about anything in particular, I linger over this section of the list and see which nuggets I might be able to massage into life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One entry into particular jumped out at me today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“My First Creeper”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I made this entry I was totally anticipating that in the very near future, my presence as a woman on the internet who openly, talks about sex, was going to attract some boundary crossing weirdos. But something strange has happened. StumpedMom.com is now a full four months old. I have done a lot of sticking my neck out and yet no verifiable, off the rails, creepers have surfaced. No one has even used the “threats” form on my contact page to register an official threat. Nobody loves me enough to hate me or hates me enough to love me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what gives? How do I explain this apparent lack of predatory attention. Feedback on my blog does come in at a pretty regular clip. Sometimes I get public shout-outs but most often I get dm’s from men on Twitter. Most of them try to use my blog and my presence online as an excuse to try and get personal information from me or to get me to sext with them. I will grant that my personal threshold for creep may be a little high but so far none of these dudes has gotten out of control. I don’t answer everyone who sends me a message. That has more to do with the timing of a first messages arrival than anything. If you say “hi” at a good time, when I am available I am likely to answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have some experience with weirdos and creepers. Waaaaay back in highschool, before social media was a thing, I pissed of the wrong weirdo and got myself a stalker. I acquired this stalker in ta rather unremarkable teenager fashion, by participating in a group slandering the wrong person at basement gathering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This person reacted by  launching a months long harassment campaign against me and those closest to me. She spammed my email inbox, she scrawled epitaphs on our high school the bathroom walls and phoned in death threats to my family from a pay-phone at all hours of the night for months on end. Sometimes she snail mailed her nasty letters and at one point she even filed a false police report against me, in which she claimed a whole different person’s identity and said I had assaulted her. She was the analog version of of a twitter mob leader. The situation was eventually resolved when her mole and chief accomplice was overcome by a wave of remorse and confessed to the school administrators. The whole debacle taught me a few lessons that I believe have been serving me well as a blogger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, I avoid slandering people as a means of getting attention.You would think this would be a lesson all adults know, but my recent observations of social media show that its a slander machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The measures I have taken to protect my identity (even passing up offers for free stuff) have all been made with this cautionary tale in mind and I started this project prepared to walk away from it at any time. No online argument or internet beef is worth putting my family through the anxiety that my last stalker caused.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I follow my own advice. When I interact with people I make my intentions clear. I tell them that I make myself available to readers for feedback but I am not available for developing any kind of relationship. If they push or make me feel uncomfortable I never escalate, I politely excuse myself, ignore or block and then I move on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am well aware that I have been exercising skills that women are socialized to learn in order to avoid some of the worst outcomes of misogynistic rape culture. These are our ways of getting out without getting hurt. Don’t cause a fuss, don’t trigger his entitlement etc. Victims are never to blame for being attacked but there are ways to minimize risk and sense bad situations and find a way out before you get in too deep.I might be out to change the world, one blog post at a time but I still have to function in it just the same. So far, this little artistic endeavor has bolstered my faith in people. Thank you stumpers for reading me and hearing me and respecting my boundaries. I look forward to continuing to interact with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monday Mom Hacks Infant Stytle</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/04/monday-mom-hacks-infant-stytle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 10:55:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/04/monday-mom-hacks-infant-stytle/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Monday Mom Hacks Infant style:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I am committed to anything here at StumpedMom.com it is learning things the hard way so you don’t have to. If you have young children or are anticipating the arrival of a new baby you’re going to be bombarded with advice. Some of it helpful-some of it pushy and unnecessary.
&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/infants_style.jpeg&#34; style=&#34;width:320px;height:213px;float:left;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 15px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not here to sell you a product, just to entertain you and hopefully make your life a little better. Below are five things for new babies that I discovered on my own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Backup Lovey:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most infants show a  preference for a particular blanket or plush toy early on. Once your child does this, purchase at least one spare so you have a backup. Go to Ebay and pay premium for it if you have to.  I have even had copies made by hand in the case of one homemade blanket.  We ordered backups for my daughters favorite plush toy and favorite blanket before she was six months old and we would regularly rotate them so that we could wash them without disruption. With regular cycling they have equal wear, so she couldn’t tell the difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your child’s favorite comfort items will last longer this way, and stay cleaner and if you play your card right you will never get caught without blankie at bedtime or find yourself going to extremes to recover a lost plush toy. When she was four she discovered our secret stash but she was totally cool with their being copies once we explained that we did it so she would never be without her favorites. When her father and I seperated she took one set to each house. She is seven now and she still treats that favorite plush like its a member of the family, in both of her houses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Lingerie bag:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did I mention that you can totally get away with washing your baby’s smaller plush toys in the washing machine and dryer if you put them in a standard lingerie bag? Go ahead and try it, pop Teddy in the wash with everything else. Careful not to put in the dryer on high heat if it has fake plastic hair. No more smelly stuffed animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Wheelchair&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I discovered this hack while I was looking after a baby, while also making, long and frequent visits to a nursing home. While the baby was fussy during one of the visits, I sat down in a spare wheelchair. I rocked him back and forth using the wheels to glide back and forth and he went to sleep. While the baby was sleeping I was still able to wheel around and do stuff! It was amazing. This became our regular go to thing the residents of the home loved that we came around to visit everyone while we wheeled about. If you can get your hands on an old wheelchair and your house is accessible enough you can be basically an unstoppable baby comforting multi-tasking machine!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diaper Service:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are open to cloth diapering and there is a cloth diaper service in your area.I highly recommend you try it. There are numerous health and environmental benefits to cloth diapering but I know for new mom’s the rubber often meets the road at convenience and affordability. It sounds super bougie and unaffordable but I did the math using spreadsheets before my baby was born and in my area, and for the first six months diaper service was cheaper than using costco brand diapers. The way it works they give you an odor controlling hamper and special bags and once a week they drop off clean cloth diaper liners and pick up the dirty ones from the week before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Benefit of Birthing at home:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did have a home birth but I am not a home birthing advocate. Expectant mothers in the US are bombarded with choices to make regarding their upcoming birth. My advice to you in this arena is to talk with your healthcare providers and do some of your own independent research and don’t let anyone else tell you what to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said, I did a ton of research before I made my choice and there was one fringe benefit to my home birth that nobody told me about - the effect it had on my pets. Giving birth at home removed the whole, introducing the baby to the animals situation. When I gave birth my faithful pooch and curious kitty patiently awaited the arrival then came around and gave everything a sniff and that was it, that was all they needed to know. They gave me plenty of space and they were gentle and accepting toward the baby. I can’t say that every pet will react like mine did but I 100% believe that having the scent of the birth in the house communicated everything she needed to know in their first language, scent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every family and every baby is different and no matter how well you prepare you’re going to discover new things every day. We pick stuff up through trial and error, conversations with friends and family and from the media and somehow we make it through.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Consent</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/01/cyber-consent/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 10:20:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/01/cyber-consent/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;cyber-consent&#34;&gt;Cyber Consent&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/chalk.jpeg&#34; style=&#34;width:320px;height:213px;float:left;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 15px;&#34;&gt;
It’s time to have a little talk about cyber boundaries and cyber consent. This isn’t going to be one of my friendly Mom talks. Because many of you are not being very nice. If I have done it right, you will all feel sufficiently chastised before reaching the end of this article.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a few weeks now, I have been ruminating on all of the talk about dick picks and cyber whores and good girls and bad girls and sluts and fuckbois, on the internet. There is a lot to unpack with the combination of slut-shaming, virtue signaling, sex advertising, sex pushing and stalking going on on social media. By at least a magnitude of ten I have seen more tweets complaining about pictures of penises then I have seen penises on social media. Sexual harassment, unsolicited pictures, revenge porn and child pornography are real problems but there seems to be a whole genre of of internet memes and tweets dedicated to shaming other people for engaging in sexual behavior. Shame on you - people who invest time and energy into shaming people who engage in fully consensual activity. You need to find something better to do with your time then body shame people. Sex is fun normal and healthy and just because some people are more comfortable sharing their sexuality in public than you are doesn’t make you a better person. Prudishness does not constitute virtue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said, I think you all need a little primer on what constitutes consent and boundaries on the internet. Since we do not have reliable ways of verifying the identities of people on-line much of this is predicated upon the assumption of honesty of all involved parties. We are all on an honor system here people but let’s lay out the rules first so you know what to honor. This is not legal advice, rather this is a guide to being a not-shitty sexy human on the internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Cyberslut’s guide to internet consent:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minors, animals, and unconscious, overpowered, unwillingly restrained or inebriated people are not capable of consent. Don’t do any kind of sex with these. This includes creating, transferring or transfering images or telling stories of a sexually explicit nature. For the purposes of this list the term person means an adult, competent, human.
Images of a person’s body belong to that person. If a person transmits an image to you via private channel you do not have the right to transmit that image to others. This includes penises. Men’s right to bodily autonomy and privacy is equal to women’s. I shouldn’t have to say this but apparently I do. Some of you seem to be under the false impression that body shaming males is a form of feminism it isn’t. It’s just not ok to tell all men that all of their penises are gross and nobody ever wants to see them. Stop it. Body parts are not gross and if you say they are then you are.
Secure positive consent, before transmitting sexually explicit materials to a person either through invitation to view public materials or direct transfer via private channel. This involves asking them if they would like to view explicit materials, or if they want to engage in sexually explicit conversation with you.
Sexual stories about another person should not be shared in a way that does not take reasonable measures to conceal their identity. This is one of the reasons I maintain an anonymous persona, so I can speak honestly about my experiences without violating the privacy and consent any of my current or former partners. In some cases some of the stories that you see here are pre-approved by the partners involved just to be double sure.
Engaging in sexually explicit conversation and sharing of sexual materials through private channels is a form of intimacy. If you are in a committed relationship and you do not have the consent of your partner to engage in such activities this is cheating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that I have clearly posted my standards for cyber consent, I expect anyone interacting directly with me to abide by them. I consider any sexual activity that falls within these guidelines to be a normal expression of human sexuality. Sex is by its very nature a little odd and we may not understand or appreciate other people’s interests. Personally I find that tension fascinating.  Stumped Mom as an artistic project is dedicated to these differences and I have no tolerance for intolerance. So play nice out there.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex For Every Body</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/29/sex-for-every-body/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 14:34:34 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/29/sex-for-every-body/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you that follow me on twitter or catch up with me on guest blogs, or have even read my full catalogue you may be aware that I am going through a bit of a personal health crisis right now.  I have badly injured my lower back. You all know I write about sex but none have you been brave enough to ask. What has the impact of your lower back injury been on your sex life? But I’m going to answer the question anyway. I’m not gonna sugar coat it kids it’s been a major fucking bummer bummer. For weeks on end my back has been so sensitive to pressure and movement that arousal, pleasure and orgasms have been very difficult to achieve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But my partner and I are still managing to stay sexually active and we have not given up on pleasuring each-other or enjoying our intimacy.  Our pornographic and hollywood culture would have us think that the only sexy bodies are fit, young, athletic and hairless.  In the scheme of things - unless death takes us suddenly and at a young age, we will all experience disability and or injury at some-point in our lives. I have set it as a personal goal to someday get busted in the community room of the old folks home. But can you imagine what would happen to the world if everyone with a backache gave up on sex entirely? What would our relationship look like if we treated each other like sexual tools to be discarded at the first sign of dysfunction? This is my second encounter with a back injury, I have also experienced being nine-months-pregnant, post partum, and a slew of other injuries that have left one part or another not working at its prime. Sex while your hurting or less mobile can be a challenge and I have fumbled through more than a few of them. But we live we learn and we adapt. Here are my tips for adaptive sex:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be Flexible: I don’t mean make yourself a contortionist. The last thing a person experiencing a mobility problem wants to be told is to make their body more flexible for sex. I mean about your patterns, methods likes and dislikes. Consider your injury as an opportunity/excuse to try new things you might not normally try and perhaps get past some old hang-ups. You may want to re-negotiate some of your sexual and relationship boundaries with your partner. Maybe now is the time to give voyeurism or some other low contact fantasy a try. You may need to change up the time of day that you have sex. You might have to give up on having orgasms with your partner as often as you are used to and focus on intimacy, connection or excitement during the time you are together; with the understanding that you’ll both be having more solo sessions on the in-between.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chart the patterns: If you are dealing with injury, mood issues, hormone fluctuations, pain or fatigue, try to identify which times of day are your best times. Communicate with your partner about these best times. Give yourself the opportunity to enjoy pleasure during the the times it works for you. My mobility is at its best during mid-day. This is a bit of a bummer because my partner and I can almost never see eachother mid-day. But I find ways of making my mid-day solo sessions into an interactive experience, through phone calls, sexting and documentation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start with no-contact foreplay. If your body is experiencing challenges your sessions might need to be shorter to minimize the risk of aggravating an injury. You can get ready for your next in person encounter by engaging in no-contact to light contact foreplay. This means lots of flirting, fantasy talk, maybe role play, this could also mean sharing erotica together or pornography. You may find a few ideas in my cyberslut back catalogue. My partner and I are big sexters. I will get ready for a session by sending him messages about the last one, telling him what I am fantasizing about, maybe sending him little hints or leaving things for him to find that I know will turn him on and get me going in the process. By the time our clothes come off our bodies are super-responsive because we’ve been practicing in our head all day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Become a gear-head: I have a confession to make. For a self-proclaimed slut, I’m not very big on toys but they are coming out of the drawer more and more often lately. I have a few but I don’t use them very often and I am considering investing in a few more. Toys can extend your reach, give you new appendages, and make up for mobility and energy you or your partner may not have.  In addition to toys, consider using furniture pillows, slings and whatever other tools help you get into positions that work for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enjoy touch in other ways. Kiss, cuddle and enjoy your body and your partner’s body(s) in the ways that bring you both comfort and intimacy. I’m spending an awful lot of time lately with my head in my partners lap, having my hair stroked, because that’s what I want and it makes me feel better. If he happens to get a hard on while I’m there I may decide to get it out and play with it. My blog jobs are getting better and better lately.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know you’ve been waiting for it so here it is….Communicate! Tell your partner where you are how you are feeling and what is and is not working for you from day to day and moment to moment. Be specific, share details about how vigorous or firmly you can be touched or held. During the first few weeks of my most recent injury one of our biggest hurdles was my partner’s fear of doing something that would hurt me. Since he shared his fears I have been more specific with him about which positions are working for me at any given time, I tell him where he should put his hands, where my leg or knee can go and what my limits are. This has built his trust and we are starting to find a new groove.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Above all be gentle and forgiving present with yourself and your partner. Sometimes things aren’t going to work and that doesn’t have to be someone’s fault. I hope you give these methods a shot even/or especially if you aren’t experiencing a significant physical challenge or illness. Sex belongs to all of us! Being injured disabled or ill doesn’t mean that your sexual self goes away. And for many of us sexual connection is an important part of our intimate relationships to make it last over time we must adapt.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind Over Matter</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/23/mind-over-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 19:49:15 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/23/mind-over-matter/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Mind over Matter&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t tell you how excited I am to have been invited to do my first guest post. When Christina G. invited me to post on her site I was incredibly excited and flattered. She is literally one of five other bloggers out there I consistently enjoy reading. If you’re a stumper you owe it to yourself to check her out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ccorral.blogspot.com/2019/01/mind-over-matter.html&#34;&gt;Mind Over Matter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>