<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/about_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/about_me/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About me:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a fiction - an artistic alter ego created to emphasize key traits of my creator’s personal identity, hile intentionally masking others. All biographies and human self presentations include exaggeration as well as obfuscation for it is only in fiction that we dispense with the pretense of factual authenticity, and free ourselves to explore larger truths. That being said, I identify as a slutty, white, divorced mother of one in the year 2018. I live in a West Coast American city, there is no hiding that. I am college educated and I own a modest home in an, “up and coming neighborhood” (The whole foods 8 blocks up just opened 2 years ago). I have a job that pays me just enough to be able to afford the mortgage on that home and do enough repairs to keep it from falling down. So I guess that makes me part of the “coastal elite.” My favorite Muppet is Gonzo. I am a weirdo, who has learned to assimilate with everyday life but every, single day I see elephants in rooms and I want to talk about them. This room is parenting and mothering in contemporary America and I want to talk about pesky pachyderms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In the words of the great Rowdie Roddie Piper, “I am here to kickass and chew bubblegum and I am all out of bubblegum!” - Stumped Mom is here to slay!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Massively Multiplayer</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/15/massively-multiplayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 10:28:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/15/massively-multiplayer/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;massively-multiplayer&#34;&gt;Massively Multiplayer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/controller.jpeg&#34; style=&#34;width:320px;height:213px;float:left;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 15px;&#34;&gt;
If you’ve been keeping up with #cyberslut, you may have intimated that I have been a little bit adventurous, in recent years, when it comes to my sex life. I have had some experiences  in group sex, tried out fantasy scenarios and visited specialty clubs and the like. I also enjoy a robust fantasy talk relationship with my main partner which has been going strong for 3 years. We have had multiple group sex encounters and each one has built the trust that we have together. I have also had group play go terribly wrong and seen it act as the catalyst for the unraveling of relationships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we continue and before you take any of my claims or observations too seriously please read “Owning Sex.”  When it comes to group sex IRL there are lots of safety issues I recommend you check out Planned Parenthood’s website for information about safer sex practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some things come down to a confluence of people and events that can’t be formulated. Group sex tends to be one of those things. But if there is a secret sauce it’s talking.
Like so many human endeavors the key to group sex, is communication. And the number one thing you need to talk about before even discussing group fantasies with a new partner or partners is your boundaries. Let me say that again. Boundaries, boundaries, boundaries. This can take time to flesh out, and can be even harder if you’re in a long term relationship and and you’ve never had this sort of conversation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If someone says they have no boundaries or lists hardly any that person isn’t ready for this rodeo or group play may not be for them. The thing to do is to take things slow, never try to push or coerce a partner that isn’t interested or ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t know what your boundaries are? Here is a starter pack of questions to get you started either on your own or with a partner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What kind of things excite you to hear about and watch?
What kinds of things frighten you, even as hypotheticals?
What feels unsafe to you?
What reassures you?
What makes you feel safe?
What doesn’t excite you but doesn’t scare or turn you off either?
How far do you want things to go?
Who can initiate?
How do you want things to start?
How do you want things to end?
What information are you willing to share with others?
If your boundaries are violated what is your default space for feeling safe?
What reinforces your trust?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In some relationships even discussing attractions to other people can be a challenge. Take things slow and check in with each other often. One boundary I have with my current partner is that fantasy talk is just that, talk. If I talk with him about a mutli-player fantasy he knows that does not imply that I intend or wish to fulfill that fantasy in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These guidelines don’t just apply to IRL situations. It is applicable for all forms of virtual group play. Including, sharing pornography, group fantasy talk and chats, camera play and virtual voyeurism/exhibitionism. If you enjoy certain kinds of pornographic materials but you are not interested in pursuing what is depicted make that boundary clear. Watching people do something on the screen does not mean you are committing to taking part in the same kinds of activities. Enjoying boxing matches doesn’t mean that you are ready to go toe to toe with the first taker in your weight class. Then again you might be a contender. The crucial element is preparation. Talk about your interests first. These kinds of conversations are great to have as a check in about your sex life in general. It is also great preparation for virtual group play.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumped MomI still don’t get “virtual group play,” what does that include?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am glad you asked  virtual group play can take place with multiple people all in different locations chatting, via text, or even party line. It can take the form of sharing pictures, fantasies, it can include virtual exhibitionism through webcam and anything else you can imagine, in which technology is involved in connecting one or more of the participants. I once live sexted someone while I was having sex with another person. It was pretty hot for everyone involved (we had a threesome later).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to boundaries you should talk about before and after care with your playmates. Before and after care are the words, activities, and steps a person requires after sex play to feel safe and supported.  This can be anything you need or your partners need to feel safe and valued. Some people want time alone. Some people want to have a long chat. Some of us want to make everyone waffles after a long cuddle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of my safety tips from beginning fantasy talk apply to group virtual play. Be mindful of privacy, and check in with your partners both before and after.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This last weekend a reader asked me over Twitter Direct Messaging (I really do respond to messages about my blog) what it is like to have a threesome. Not sexting with readers is one of my boundaries, so at the time I just said it was exhausting because I didn’t want to get too titalting. Which is true, group sex can be very taxing both emotionally and physically, so eat your wheaties and remember to drink plenty of water. Personally I am prone to over stimulation and I have never climaxed during in person group sex. That being said there is no feeling in this world quite like bringing two people to climax at the same time. Multiplayer games aren’t for everyone but they are absolutely a thrill. If you do take that step to plug-in more than two players, please be safe and above all honor yourself and care for your playmates.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Dysfunctional Ways to Avoid a bad Boss</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/09/10-dysfunctional-ways-to-avoid-a-bad-boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 20:46:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/09/10-dysfunctional-ways-to-avoid-a-bad-boss/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;10-dysfunctional-ways-to-avoid-a-bad-boss&#34;&gt;10 Dysfunctional Ways to Avoid a bad Boss&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/bad_boss.jpg&#34; style=&#34;width:320px;height:213px;float:left;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 15px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for advice on how to be an efficient part of the capitalist machine the American news media and the internet have you covered. Forbes, the Wall Street Journal and LinkedIn supply a steady stream of content designed to help you be a compliant and striving little worker bee. I haven’t seen any metrics but these pieces wouldn’t proliferate so freely if they weren’t popular and therefore profitable. And why wouldn’t they be? We all want to succeed and be happy and we all want to advance but sometimes you get stuck stuck. Sometimes you have to just put up with a bad job or a bad boss to make ends meet. I am in no way condoning staying in a toxic workplace. I have been in one for years and not for lack of striving toward new opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe I’ve been self sabotaging because I have a co-dependant personality, but I have gotten up to the second interview in three jobs in the last year and gained nothing but higher blood pressure and “practice.” In the meantime, I have a mortgage to pay and a kid to feed an ex husband who is behind on his reimbursements and a boss who can best be described as a cross between Capt. Queeg, Mallory Sterling, and The Millionaire’s wife from Gilligan’s Island. She leaves me alone with almost nothing to do for long stretches of time and then, when I do see her, she dumps on me with a load of new projects and  or criticism of work that I gave her for review or approval so long before that it’s been completely forgotten about it. If I get ambitious and try to take initiative, on anything without her approval I get a pretty rapid smackdown. I don’t have a ton of options for what to do with myself. For those of you with a boss like mine, a micromanager who also ignores her employees for long stretches and lacks basic human empathy, I have assembled this handy list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10 Dysfunctional Ways to Avoid a Bad Boss:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Know the Schedule. This is the first and most important and you’re not going to succeed at any of the others unless you have it. Know your bosses schedule. This may be simple if your boss publishes and sticks to a schedule. If they don’t publish a schedule see if you can cozy up to an assistant to get the deets. My boss publishes a schedule and she doesn’t stick to it so my system isn’t fool proof.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calibrate your hours. If at all possible start earlier and leave earlier than your boss. My office offers flexible work schedules. In that we have a three hour window in which to set our usual start time (7:00 am- 10:00 am) and a three hour window to set our end time (4:00-7:00 p.m.) My boss roles in, like the Queen of the May, between 9:30-10:00 a.m. each day. I try to get in around 8:15 a.m..  If I’m running really late and get to work at 8:45 she’s none the wiser, unless I get ratted out by those snitches in accounting. I am out the door, no later than 5:00 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Employ Conversation Repellent. When at your desk, wear headphones or earbuds, this won’t stop the old ringmaster from cracking the whip, when they really want something but it will put the breaks on small talk which are really just attempts to pry into your life so they can judge you for it later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Look Busy. During the times that you know the boss will be moving through your work spaces get out your most busy looking least fun looking projects. I save all my spreadsheets and filing project for my bosses in-office and between meeting hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lunch Early. Schedule your lunch right before your boss’s lunch.If you’re getting in before your boss you should be able to step out to lunch just after they have caught up with their inbox and to-list.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be a Go Getter (literally). Volunteer for office errands. If at all possible run those errands right when you expect your boss to get back from lunch. This can buy you another half hour and whatever it was they wanted to talk to you about when you left or lunch will likely be forgotten about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep your mind occupied. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to get up to no-good if you don’t have something productive to do. Find something creative to do with your time that enriches you and still looks like work. Like maybe a blog. but not a blog like this one. This is my market niche. Get your own!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep a log of misdeeds. If your boss is riding the line for abuse, discrimination or harassment, keep a log of misdeeds. My boss got really testy with me at my last review and I made sure she knew that I had a log and picked out a few examples from it in which she was being a total cunt. Don’t give your boss the log, keep the log on a file source that only you have access to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Send it in an Email. Get whatever it is you do need to get done and  done on time. Deliver it to the boss’s inbox before it’s asked for. If you have a question, send it in an email. Send, send, send until you are told to stop. If your boss is sorting and reading your messages they are not at your desk breathing on you. Or sneaking up to try to catch you reading stumpedmom.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be ready.  Alas you cannot avoid your boss forever so you must be ready. Have a folder or a packet ready for when the boss drops in on you. Have your list of things you need from them. Make a habit of it. You want them to know that everything has a price and the price of bothering you is being reminded of how ahead of them you are and how  underutilized your talents are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck out there stumpers. I can’t guarantee you it will get better. I can’t even guarantee you that we won’t all be jumpsuit-wearing, serf-level drones of the Bezos corporation, living off of Soil N Green in ten years but I hope these tips get you by if your boss happens to be as unbearable as mine is.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owning Sex</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/08/owning-sex/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 10:05:49 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/08/owning-sex/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;owning-sex&#34;&gt;Owning Sex&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This past week, I received my first feedback from a self described, lifestyle kinkster, about the #cyberslut. I admit, I went out on a limb and inserted myself into their conversation, hoping to reach out to new audiences and expand my reach. This feedback described some of my assertions as inaccurate fundamentally wrong. I asked them to share resources on the topics but they did not respond. I am no stranger to criticism of my position, style or punctuation, but rarely have I ever been accused of being inaccurate or fundamentally wrong and certainly not by a person who wasn’t prepared with sources of information to directly refute my claims.This spurned me on a deep level of academic pride and caused me to question my grounds upon which I wished to stake my position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/mouth.jpeg&#34; style=&#34;width:320px;height:213px;float:left;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 15px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had a pretty damn good college History professor and adviser, who did a thorough job of holding his students the difference between observation and generalization. He taught me how to avoid the latter through the employment of sufficient qualifications and citations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The difference between observation and generalization:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To observe is report on your own experience.
To generalize is to portray your own observation as a broader truth&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only truth I claim is in my own experience. Sex, pleasure and arousal by their own nature‘s belong to each individual human experience. Your sex and your experience cannot possibly claim to refute or invalidate my own no matter what your education is,or what your sexual experiences have been or how you identify.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my “Introduction to Fantasy talk,” in Particular I made it clear that all observations were based on my own experience and observations or what has been reported to me by, individuals that identify as belonging to particular named groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel I have touched on that point  in each of my edition or a that I have been speaking casually from my own limited personal understanding and experience. This blog is an art project and a form of personal recreation. I am not going to do a paper on comparative sexual and psychological studies. Not, because I lack the capacity but because I have no real interest in doing so, as it wouldn’t contribute toward my aims.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My goal is to be able to connect with as many people as I can, to start  a casual and accessible conversations about sexting, and kink and group sex and other sexual practices that are still broadly stigmatized. I wanted to be able to talk to with people in ways that are not confined to the language and codes for sex that have been dominated of the pornography industry or kink communities. For me this is personal and social feminist and progressive work. Systems of order can deprive the individual of many things but they can never take from something as inexorably attached to our intimate selves then our sexuality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may never lay claim to my sex nor may I lay claim to yours. To be clear I do use some generally recognizable categories to sort and classify my observations but my purpose in using them is only for general conversation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which brings us back to the question at hand. To write or not to write?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This  week’s post was promised to be a segment on group sexual fantasies with some points on IRL application I was calling “Massively Multi-Player”. As a person who has participated in just one foursuom, a handful of threesomes, and several live and virtual voyeuristic experiences  and has only virtually seduced one man, three women and two couples into meeting up with me and a partner for group sex, how could I possibly pretend to be able to speak with any sort of authority on the subject?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well the answer was that I was claiming no authority but my own and I shall keep writing and I shall keep repeating:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My observations are only my own, and I do not portray them to be  that but my own.
I claim no recognizable qualifications as an expert on any of these subjects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have I lost anyone, class?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I was saying, this blog is on the same academic level of: shit I say when I’m at the pub. If you could find my actual regular pub and read the bartenders there this blog, I have a feeling they could guess which patron wrote it. This is it. This is me. This is how I talk. This is how I think. This is how I write. And I pretend at nothing more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just look at the time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I have dedicated all of my readily available mental energies and faculties into sorting out this epistemological knot, I have been unable to apply appropriate attention to this week’s promised edition of cybersluttery: “Massively Multi-player.”  For this disservice, dearest stumpers, I am sorry. I promise to try to make it up to you all as I dedicate my clear head and sharpened faculties to produce a particularly juicy one for you next week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And as to the haters?
I say to thee
I do not yield sirs madams and thous
Not Today
I DO NOT!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Struggle With Ableism</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/03/my-struggle-with-ableism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/03/my-struggle-with-ableism/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-struggle-with-ableism&#34;&gt;My Struggle With Ableism&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About two years ago while I was stuck working night shift for a few weeks, I got really into the &lt;a href=&#34;https://implicit.harvard.edu/implicit/iatdetails.html&#34;&gt;Harvard Implicit Bias test&lt;/a&gt; project. The tests ask you to react quickly to a series of images and is designed to measure your unconscious bias towards groups. I felt super great about myself when I took my first test and found out I was biased in favor darker skinned people and against lighter skinned people (an outlier result for a white woman). I highly encourage any person who wants to improve their personal awareness of bias in all of its forms to check it out. The tests ask you to react quickly and repeatedly to images of people belonging to certain groups with either an up or down response. The idea is to measure your immediate associations rather than your conscious belief about groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I lost the spring in my step and my sense of personal self righteousness when I did the ableism assessment. It indicated pretty strong bias against people with disabilities. I have vacillated between shame and denial about this since. My bias and my sense of identity were at odds. My grandmother was a public accessibility activist, my favorite uncle has been wheelchair bound my entire life. I’ve gone through the local children’s museum and come out with a checklist for management about the ways they could be more accessible and inclusive. I manage my office with near obsessive attention to reasonable accommodation needs. How could I be ableist?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the past two years I have been letting this knowledge sit, while I tried to reconcile myself with it and then I hurt my back again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have already been through the back pain struggle and I mean I have really been there. I ruptured a disk about 4.5 years ago and I went through 6 months of misdiagnosis and bad treatments before surgery pretty much saved my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took me 4 years of careful rehabilitation bu this fall  I was almost back to the activity level I had achieved pre-surgery, I was back to training in my martial arts at a high level and back to lifting what I was before I hurt my disk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few weeks ago I was lifting an awkward item for work and I felt my back twinge. Its been getting worse for weeks and the pain is all too familiar. I have, for the second time in my life, gone from being able to land spinning kick to a peers face, with good humored alacrity to barely being able to get out of a chair or tie my shoes.All within a week of an accident that felt like a muscle pull at first. Now that I find myself staring down a period of possibly, open ended prolonged physical disability I’ve been forced in many ways to confront how my ableism functions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am terrible at asking for help. I pride myself on my independence, resilience and ingenuity especially when it comes to adapting to injuries. In the first week of this current injury, I was focused on how very proud I was to be able to kneel down from a tight stance with my back straight to reach things on the floor since I can’t bend over. I also did not want to use any assistive devices.  I always looked as this trait as a strength and it certainly has earned me admiration from others over the years. But this personal quality has undeniably caused me and my loved ones unnecessary pain and suffering. I have delayed treatment, violated instructions and sabotage my own recovery all because I am afraid of looking weak or being a burden on my family, friends or co-workers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This time, as I look at the possibility of going through a long period of pain again I want to do it smarter. I want to demand the treatment that I need, speak up with things cause me further pain and use accommodations, devices and assistance that will reduce my suffering.  I have committed myself to really putting myself first and advocating for the treatment that I need. But feelings of shame, over being hurt are still holding me back and this has caused me to confront the ugly roots of my own ableism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I ain’t no cripple!” I drawled “I can get it myself!” These were the loving and gracious words that came out of my mouth as my boyfriend tried to help me pick up after my dog. The line was delivered with an exaggerated affect that indicated my self-deprecating irony, but they were still real, it meant something to me.“Cripple,” Where did that ugly word even come from?  It is possibly one of the ugliest words in the English language and in that moment it came flowing from me with effortless familiarity.. When I said it I felt I heard the voices of my uncles, aunts, father and cousins slipping easily from me in what was only a half mock parody. The word was batted about with regularity and jest during my formative years often in the presence of family members with permanent mobility impairments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was raised in a family full of disabilities and differences but exposure to these differences and loving relationships with differently abled people wasn’t enough. I learned from casual jokes that there was shame in disability and that any injury I sustained was a burden on my family. I have not yet found a manual on unlearning this deeply ingrained feeling, but I know that the best version of me is ready to be rid of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumpers can you help me and come with me on this journey? Can you call out my ableism when you see it? Can you share your own stories with me and help me build my perspective and compassion? I could probably do it on my own but I think this thing will be better for everyone if I don’t try.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Fantasy Talk</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/01/advanced-fantasy-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/01/advanced-fantasy-talk/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;advanced-fantasy-talk&#34;&gt;Advanced Fantasy Talk&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two entries ago I promised to get into some more advanced fantasy tips and I am nothing if not a woman of my word. These are my more advanced tips for a slightly kinkier level of fantasy play. I claim zero expertise in kink; for that you’re going to have to go to different corners of the internet but those corners can be scary and intimidating, even if they really are actually filled with regular people who just happen to enjoy novel sexual if experiences. But there is also a lot of stuff that most people just don’t want to see. Just a quick foray can leave you feeling like 16 year old Stumped Mom did after watching &lt;em&gt;8mm&lt;/em&gt; in the theatre. There are as many kinks to be discovered as there are stars in the sky. Today I am going to give you some tips on working within some common kink sub-types. All but the first kink on my list below can be found in both dominant and submissive partners and can be applied in a range of intensities. For the basics of Dominance and Submission please read &lt;a href=&#34;https://stumpedmom.com/2018/12/17/dabling-in-kink/&#34;&gt;Dabbling in Kink.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humiliation Submission: One of the ways to express power in sex is to humiliate  others. In its gentlest form humiliation an be manifested in playful banter or name calling. For people that enjoy it, it can offer a release from their feelings of shame or guilt surrounding enjoyment. Humiliation is a delicate thing. Treat it carefully, ask your partners if they are into it, or look for signs like sexual self deprecation, before just unloading on them with verbal abuse. Pro tip- I have never found a person of color in America, who is into humiliation submission,my personal theory is that they deal with too much of that shit every damn day in our culture to find it sexy in the bedroom. I urge you to handle humiliation submission with care, it can be very damaging to relationships if it isn’t handled correctly. Personally I enjoy saying I’m sorry a lot during sex and it enhances the experience for me if my partner will tell me why I should be.*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Voyeurs:  A true voyeur is a gem and they are actually hard to find. Most of us enjoy watching sexual acts but few of us fetishize looking but not touching. My first threesome was with a woman who we only brought home to watch but she couldn’t keep her hands off, she turned out to be a marriage wrecking rhinoceros disguised as a unicorn.  That being said a true voyeur as a fantasy talk partner is great if you enjoy spinning a sexy yarn voyeurs will eagerily lap up sexy stories past future and present especially if you give them space to be the watcher in those stories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Masochists: My armchair theory about masochists is that they are show offs. Every middle school kid who has gotten a hold of H.P. lovecraft thinks they have discovered the secret to the pain pleasure cycle. There is some complex a &lt;a href=&#34;https://bodyinmind.org/pain-pleasure-relationship/&#34;&gt;neurological and hormonal&lt;/a&gt; stuff that goes on with pain and the neural pathways during sex and everyone is a bit different. What I find  gets masochists off is being able to impress you with how much pain they can take. If you have one in fantasy talk they will be very excited to talk about how you’d like to push their limits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sadists: I try not to judge but I have never stuck around to find out what makes a true sadist tick and I would advise anyone who thinks they have encountered a true sadist to avoid. But the S in and M is usually about playing the part just enough to make it exciting it’s not about getting off on hurting people.  Most people who will willingly dish out a little bit of pain with pleasure are people pleasing dominants who are excited by pushing boundaries and breaking social scripts. If someone surpases your boundaries and hurts you in a way you did not want for their own pleasure it is assault. I am switchy and I also know a bit about joint locks. When I am dominating I’ll administer a bit of pain to enhance my partners excitement but I recoil at the idea of causing pain for its own sake or allowing someone to do the same to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Risk takers: For many people just about anything that enhances the risk of sex makes it more exciting. This can include the risk of getting caught, being late, being rejected or just messing it up. If you’re trying to please a risk taker just remember it’s all about measured risk and novelty. You shouldn’t really have to fuck on the fire escape to please them you can get them excited by sending them sexy messages when they are at work or pretty much anywhere else where getting caught could lead to consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These five elements of kink are not exclusive or exhaustive. I encourage you to try them gradually if they are new for you. Start with little suggestions or questions and see where it takes you.  There is no need to dive in head first with any of these types of fantasies unless taking things on all at once is what really excites you, in that case don’t let me be the one to stop you. When I first started cyberslut  I thought was going to just be a three part series but each time I sit down to write I find myself tabling things for the next piece.  It has also been super popular because who would have guessed that people love reading about sex on the internet? Next week we’ll be talking about massive multi-player kinks: Orgy lovers, groupers, cucks, hotwifes, double-topping, Unicorns and more. And I plan to keep at it so long as the material keeps coming to mind. Thanks for reading and for playing. I love to hear about your experiences and experiments so please feel free to catch up with me through my contact page, on twitter or in the comments. Just don’t try sexting with me through dm’s it’s the internet equivalent of trying to pick up a stripper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;*&lt;/code&gt; Humorous  anecdote; a few summers ago while my partner and I were enjoying a vigorous fuck with a bit of spanking with the windows open and shouted “I’m sorry!” enough that one of the neighbors came up to my back fence and asked if I needed assistance. She started shouting at my partner to leave me alone or she would jump the fence. So try not to alarm the neighbors while you’re playing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Purge</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/20/the-purge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/20/the-purge/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-purge&#34;&gt;The Purge&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome Stumpers,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to the good vibes only zone. Come along with me on a journey to awesomeness while improving your life, your mind, your body and your soul with a thorough and complete cleansing. Now is the time to rid ourselves of negativity in our lives. You don’t need negative people or influencers pulling you down with them. If they don’t affirm you and all of your most ardent desires, or make your sandwiches and give you orgasms, flatter your taste and intelligence, block them, delete them, ignore them and feel free to abandon with abandon. It’s time to manifest only positivity by adding subtraction to your life. If you can’t identify the immediate benefit that a loved one brings to your individual goals it’s time to re-examine that relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grandma doesn’t like your vegan gluten free baking?
Maybe you don’t need to visit her anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t like awkward encounters with strangers?
Wear headphones all the time to signal to the world you have more important things to hear&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is that old friend of yours asking for too much emotional support?
Stop taking her calls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can make every moment of your life feel like those last few warm engrossing minutes of your yoga class. All can be perfect tender and toasty like a fresh beignet. You can be filled with boundless self esteem.  All doubts can be eliminated. Don’t worry about hurting others in your pursuit of creating a perfect bubble of self reflection free positive re-enforcement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom I think You’re laying it on right now!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hell’s yeah I’m laying it on right now. I don’t care if my weak attempt at satirical tone is as subtle as a flying brick.  I am sick to death of social media, celebrities regular media and people all around me in my life acting like the way to cope with all of the friction in our lives is to avoid it.  As if we can ignore away every uncomfortable interaction or piece of feedback and experience no negative consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know who was a real fucking buzzkill? The soothsayer in Shakespeare’s Julius Caesar. What did that guy say?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Beware the Ides of March!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What a douche, that guy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Caesar. He was a real go getter- the grand conqueror of the Gauls. Like a Goop blog regular he knew what to do about killjoys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“He is a dreamer; let us leave him: pass.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s modern English for “Press Ignore.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are also pretty welcome to ignore the obvious lesson here. Shakespeare knew as did countless other sage observers of humans that we need naysayers in our lives to to guard us from our own conceit.  We cannot get out of our own heads to see ourselves completely. We need the help of others not only to lift us up but to reign us in. Everything we do and say is warped by our individual perceptions and petty desires. It feels good in the short term and maybe even in the medium term to block out criticism, to don our rose colored glasses and apply a Snapchat life filter to our world, especially when we feel beset by an endless deluge of negative crap. But what becomes of us when we crop out all of our “negative relationships”- When we limit our interactions to the ones that are immediately gratifying?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the accelerating negative narratives of our time is the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/modern-mentality/201807/what-you-need-know-about-the-loneliness-epidemic&#34;&gt;epidemic of loneliness&lt;/a&gt;. Powered by social media and social anxiety, Americans are becoming increasingly isolated from real connections. Somehow, in the face of all of this, there is a proliferation of popular advice and attitudes that encourage, people, especially women, to ignore or eliminate interactions with other people. Good Vibes Only is blanketing the world with the suffocating demand that all friendships are predicated on a commitment to constant flow of positivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few weeks ago I was kvetching about my ex-husband with my oldest friend and she agreed completely with my perspective on things. I asked her if she was only agreeing with me because she’s my bestie. I cannot begin to say how refreshing it was to hear a very dear friend say to me, “If you’re wrong it’s more loving of me to call you out on it.”  And that is why we’ve been friends for over 25 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Setting boundaries is great. Encouraging one another is awesome. But demanding constant unconditional approval from all of our relationships is leaving a lot of us with a dearth of friends to turn to. We’re ghosting ourselves into an empty corner full of hollow sycophants and profiteers.  Maybe it’s time to consider addressing negativity through addition. Meet negative with positive and hold off on the purge.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dabling in Kink</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/17/dabling-in-kink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 19:43:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/17/dabling-in-kink/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;dabling-in-kink&#34;&gt;Dabling in Kink&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you frustrated with mainstream sex advice? Do you find the world fo kink frightening or inaccessible? I don’t blame you if you do. I do too, but I have dabbled enough in the virtual world of kink to get a handle on the basics. I have noticed that mainstream sex advice couples to,  “explore role play” if they are bored and stops there. Which really isn’t fair, it is a deep subject when many nuances. Where does an injeunui even begin? I’m no sex columnist or relationship therapist but I want to help my friends.  I’ve already bumbled around the world of sex and kink and made a fool of myself so you don’t have to (unless you’re into that.) Today we are going to talk about dominance and submission. If you want to understand fantasy, or kink or get just plain better at sex, it will behoove you to get a strong handle on this topic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there is a universal theory in the world of fantasy talk, sex, and kink its got to be dominance vs. submission.One of the primary engines of sexual excitement is the negotiation of power and control between partners. Everyone has certain preferences and needs when it comes to what power dynamics turn them on. Even if you believe you’re having vanilla sex, one partner is usually taking more control than the other and one may like being in control more than the other.  The partner who likes to take more initiative is dominant partner and the partner who enjoys letting others take the lead is the submissive. Get a handle on this dynamic and learn to play with it and you just may be able to save yourself from sexual monotony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like just about all things sex submission and dominance present in a spectrum and no one is just one thing all of the time. Since this is a taboo subject to talk about in most circles many people don’t identify themselves on this spectrum but figuring out where you are on the spectrum and paying attention to it in your partners is one of the keys to more exciting fantasy play and sex. Let’s talk about some of the characteristics of each and see if we can’t dispel some myths&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dominants Doms:&lt;/strong&gt; Sometimes dominants get a bad rap. There is a misconception floating around that dominants especially dominant men are abusive people who just want to hurt and control others. While this can certainly happen, enjoying dominance in the bedroom or during fantasy does not necessarily mean that a person is going to be controlling in their relationships.  My current partner is very much a dominant and he only enjoys submission as a prelude to flipping the script and regaining control. He’s also super sensitive to my needs and is categorically incapable of getting off if he senses I am uncomfortable or unhappy. In my own experience I have found that dominance is often a form of nurturing turned all the way up. A lot of doms are super caring people who are excited by taking control of other people’s pleasure. When I am in a dominant mood I feel like I want to take care of everything for my partner including telling them everything they like. I am dominating best at it when I am hyper attuned to a partners signals and needs. So if you want to get a dom off gradually reveal to them ways you enjoy being vulnerable. They also really like it when you beg for things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Submissives (subs):&lt;/strong&gt;  are conversely stereotyped as milktoast people who don’t know their own minds or have low self esteem. A lot of things can characterize the motivations of a submissive but being weak willed isn’t really correlated. For many submissives the excitement lies in surrender.  If you surrender all the time in your daily life you may not find it that exciting during sex. I find myself most excited by submission when I’m feeling tired and stressed from too many responsibilities and decisions. The best way to excite a sub is by showing fearless initiative. At the same time you need to treat submission as a gift cherish it and never take it for granted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Switches:&lt;/strong&gt; Some people treat switches liked mixed up geminis or court jesters.  A switchy person is a person who is comfortable moving pretty far into both ends of the dominant and submissive spectrum. I find  that switchers are often experimental people pleasers. They will adjust to your mood and your needs easily be careful not to abuse this flexibility, they can extend themselves too far. They can be tricksters and wild cards as well they are driven by novelty so they can be prone to boredom.The key to enjoying a switchy partner is to really meet them where they are that day. If you really want to activate a switch suggest trying something new and show that you have taken the steps to make it possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next week I promise to go into a deeper dive into some of the more esoteric kinks I have encountered. The important thing to remember is that being a sub or a dom or a switch does not reflect on your value as a person. It’s like being a cat or a dog person and if you’re dying to know where I land in that spectrum, I like both cats and dogs and all pets seem to like me. Now go out there and find yourself the perfect pet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Brain</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/13/twitter-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 08:30:27 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/13/twitter-brain/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;twitter-brain&#34;&gt;Twitter Brain&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Twitter Brain; Noun:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The condition resulting from excessive attention to Twitter characterized by intense effort toward building your personal brand  and attracting new followers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A person who thinks too much about their Twitter following.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example:
&lt;em&gt;Stump Mom’s writing and research and overall attention were suffering because she had Twitter Brain.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have recently come to terms with a reality that much America has been living with or some time - It doesn’t take much to come down with a case of Twitter Brain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Twitter started to capture the media imagination and take the public discourse by storm I reacted to it, as a typical American seven year would react to a novel food; I didn’t need to taste it, smell it, or even try it, I knew I didn’t like it. By the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.digitaltrends.com/social-media/tweet-is-now-officially-a-word-in-the-oxford-english-dictionary/&#34;&gt;time&lt;/a&gt; tweet earned its second definition in the Dictionary I had fully formed my identity as a conscientious Twitter Objector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s notorious use of the platform and Twitters unwillingness to apply any of its existing applicable policy to reign him only deepened my apprehension for the platform. And I admit, I felt superior to all those poor sad saps out there confusing their lives away on the tweets. I took a sense of comfort from knowing that I was not contributing to Twitter or to the apparent political and cultural meltdown that was taking place live on the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But in the fall of 2018 My personal convictions did not hold up very long against an emerging need. I was developing an anonymous, totally groundbreaking, form defying, norm challenging underground mommy blog. I needed readers and if I wanted to remain anonymous, readers who did not know me personally. Lacking any sort of advertising budget or promotional team I understood from all the media chatter that the best way to achieve my aim was to become a Twitter ninja.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I’m anonymous I couldn’t go out to all my real life buddies and say, “Hey guys! Support my project and follow my creative alter ego,” No “Import Contacts” for me I had to start from scratch. So I put together my profile, and started tweeting.  Words cannot describe the thrill I felt when I attracted my first follower. I’m talking about you @sarahjschlott. Once I got that first taste, I was thirsty for more. There is nothing quite like that dopamine hit that comes from receiving the endorsement of social approval from strangers even when coming from a form as superficial as the “heart” button. I started carving out time in my mornings for Twitter. After spending one particularly frenzied morning focusing on zinger re-tweets, new takes and interesting stories, I tried to develop one of my posting ideas and my writing fell flat. The words went limp on the page. No sparkling metaphors, amusing tangents or clever literary devices flowed from my brain. I couldn’t on my stories, my mind was on my Tweets and my followers. Twitter had consumed my thinking and become an end in itself. Twitter had blocked up my brain. This brought me to the edge of complete and total panic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blog content tends to come pouring out of me in big rushes. I usually have a lot more trouble editing managing and scheduling content then I do producing it and even on a rough day I am usually good for a few disjointed yet promising paragraphs.  But after dousing my brain in the social reward, live MMORPG we call Twitter I couldn’t think past 280 characters of accessible slop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But there is good news the first step to overcoming a preoccupation is to acknowledge that you have it.  So I’ve got Twitter Brain and the only cure is to write about it! Well not exactly, but the first step in recovery was starting this post on Twitter affliction.. I won’t say I have achieved ballance or that I’m happy with my Twitter habit but the following measures have helped me keep it from completely killing my productivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I downloaded a Tweet Scheduling app  I settled on Buffer but there are lots of choices. by using a Tweet Scheduling app I am able to write down my best ideas when they come to me and strategically schedule them. I can also do this without checking my feed and getting distracted with other people’s activities. This lets me sit back and enjoy family time or writing time without worrying about missing the best posting hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I turned off push notifications on my cell phone. It seems like it will give you advanced assurance but what it really does is gets you checking your feed when you picked up your phone to look at the weather or the time. I’ve also figured out how to turn off notifications on very active blog threads all together.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have started connecting directly with more bloggers and followers. I have used popular blogging hashtags to find links to other blogs similar to mine. I am starting to build more personal individualized relationships with other bloggers and followers. Trading messages and interacting with their blogs. This tends to build more lasting connections.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m doing what I want. When I first got on to Twitter the way that I answered my set-up questions and the first accounts I followed got me siloed into Parent Twitter. I love connecting with other parents but parent Twitter was a bit confining for my rebellious soul. I was very cautious in my early tweets, because my read of the room (which was full of parent bloggers) said that I needed to be. I’ve sharpened my content and my voice on Twitter to conform less to the parent Twitter ideals and reflect my Stumped Mom mission. I saw some pronounced follower losses when I first made this switch but I have recovered and made connections with writers and thinkers who appreciate my work and my irreverence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a side hustle or a blog how do you manage balancing your promotional activities with your core work? I’d love to hear from you all what your thoughts are on Social Media and connecting with your audience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginning Fantasy Talk</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/11/beginning-fantasy-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:06:13 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/11/beginning-fantasy-talk/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;beginning-fantasy-talk&#34;&gt;Beginning Fantasy Talk&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been inspired by other bloggers to talk about the things I really enjoy. And one of my favorite sources of entertainment is sex and fantasy talk. If twitter is any indication there is a lot of stigma around cyberesex, sexting and fantasy talk and that’s reason enough to talk at length about it. I do so love pissing twitter prudes off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Credentials: I haven’t gone to school for sex therapy or been in the sex industry in any way or anything like that but what I have been doing is talking dirty with people online since 1999. I’ve never had sex with a person I did not seduce online first. I once got a challenge from a friend to see how many men I could meet on Tinder and talk into jacking off and showing me proof in a picture, in one day.I got bored after bachelor number nine and it was before dinner time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On gender and sexual orientation: I am writing from the perspective of a cis gendered female whose primary sexual and romantic experiences have been with people who identify as straight cis males. For the purposes of clarity and readability when I refer to “men” I am talking about people who identify themselves as hetero and bi-sexual males. In what I am sure is a benefit to all involved I’ve never really had an attraction to or sexual experience with a gay man. I have had sexual experiences and attractions with straight men and bi-women but I’ve never felt a romantic pull toward another woman. I identify myself as a heteroromantic bisexual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I say “partner” I mean any adult person who willingly and consensually engaged in sexual behavior with me ranging from online flirtation to actual intercourse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I happen to be blessed with some pretty cool and sex positive friends and yet even among these people I find that conversation about sexting and online play are taboo. People are embarrassed to talk about it and that makes it hard to get good at. But getting good at it can be a boon to your sex life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Safety first: When it comes to online play one of the primary dangers is privacy. Everything you say or show is potentially transmittable to the whole world.  Just like when you meet someone in real life it’s a judgment call when to trust someone, be mindful of which details about yourself could be cross referenced to find your identity. Consider creating a seperate web identity for play. Set up an email and facebook with a pseudonym and use it to set up your chatting and dating apps. Don’t give out your real phone number, use an emulator. Just like with real life sex you can take precautions but there is no way to eliminate the risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be clear about your boundaries. Just as it’s good safer sex and consensual practice to talk about boundaries before physical sex, you should talk about your boundaries before during and after virtual play. Be clear about your “hard passes” and deal breakers. I am also pretty big on transparency and intent if you have no intention of escalating to IRL, be clear about it. If you are in a Romantic partnership where your partner consents to you being involved in online or virtual play, say so.  Whatever your limit is, state it, this will usually select out the jerks who will try to pressure, slut shame or guilt you into exceeding your boundaries and may also keep you from breaking any hearts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think of it as play acting. Most of the rules of improv apply. You’re creating a scene with another person and playing a part you need to listen to and observe your partner to discover what part they want to play. Just like in child’s play or improvisation if you balk at your partner&amp;rsquo;s ideas the game will come to a pretty abrupt halt.  If you do decide you want to bring a game to swift conclusion this is a good way to get someone to stop playing with you. If you outright reject someone’s kink or fantasy idea, they may not trust you to play again. I have done this intentionally when a partner said something that I found degrading or violent toward women.  I make it pretty clear when I discuss boundaries that that’s one of my hard lines.  There is a certain subset of people who do seek degradation of their desires as part of their fantasy play which I will go into more in Part II Advanced Fantasy talk next week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do some homework. Read some of the classics of erotic fiction. Pay attention to the patterns, imagery and symbols when you read, think about what turns you on and what makes you uncomfortable. Learn about sexual and social scripts.  My personal theory is that the excitement of fantasy and role play often centers around playing off of these scripts, pushing their boundaries and sometimes subverting them. The high brow thing to know here is that sexual stories are part of our culture and you are participating in it by creating and enacting your own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let yourself be a little mundane. Much of our sex culture and concepts of sexual fantasy have shaped us to believe that fantasy requires, exotic locations, improbable scenarios, hairless physiques and polished shiny bodies. I have found that partners are turned on by small bits of private life that often seem very regular and routine. Intimacy is more exciting than many people realize. Give partners the idea that they are being admitted into a special sphere of privilege. I have had tons of success by revealing little things like aspects of my grooming routine. Fantasy at its best is the perfect blend of the accessible and the ideal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anticipation, Anticipation, Anticipation! You’ll generate more excitement and keep your partners more engaged, if you give them a balance of anticipation, contribution and reward. Would Super Mario Brothers be one of the most popular video games in history and would Nintendo have become a video gaming behemoth if Mario rescued the princess after you easily defeated level 1? No, no one would  have played it because it would have been boring. Yes people, especially men  like to see and invision, body parts and penetrative acts, but it’s more fun if you work your way up to it. Don’t go straight into revealing full fantasy scenes, or just sending pictures of your body parts unless you want to be boring.Let things slowly build hold out on your good stuff until you’re really feeling it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Variety is the Spice of Life: Nobody is just one thing all the time. If you’re engaging with someone over a long period of time or across multiple platforms and in real life, give your partner&amp;rsquo;s space to play a range of roles while you try on a few complimentary versions of yourself. Treat your partners like the complex imaginative individuals that they are and they will surprise you maybe as much as you surprise them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are seven basics to get you started if you’re shy about sexting and fantasy talk.  But don’t forget the most important thing of all: Have fun. If it isn’t fun or rewarding for you don’t do it, move on to something that you like. It’s totally okay to not like things and you deserve to be with partners who won’t be satisfied if you’re not having fun. If you  have questions please feel free to send me a message and ask, just don’t ask me to practice with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whiteclaiming</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/06/whiteclaiming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/06/whiteclaiming/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Fellow White People,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The time has come for us to stop Whiteclaiming. The time has come for us to stop feigning in aspects of the cultures of non-white people by virtue of proximity.  For the sake of brevity I am dubbing this phenomenon whiteclaiming. Whiteclamining occurs when a white person claims specific special understanding of something they associate with an ethnic group based on who they know or where they are from. I’ve seen this most often in discussions of cuisine, in which people will claim to have developed particular special knowledge of Mexican, Chinese, Vietnamese or perhaps Indian food, because they come from an area with a lot of Mexican, Chinese, Vietnamese or Indian restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently my partner and I experienced a very direct and clear example of whiteclaiming. We met with a new friend for beers at a local tap room. As our new friend, a thoroughly urbane and frighteningly pale, graduate student whom we shall call Sarah, sat down she aksed about our evening so far. When mentioned that we grabbed some food at the Mexican American food restaurant across the street and she asked “But was it Good Mexican food?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My infinitely patient non-white partner who is also the son of Mexican American Immigrants (Yes documented immigrants and that question is a bigoted micro-aggression). Replied that it was solid so-cal Mex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And she went on to explain with earnest insistence, “Well I’m from the Central Valley of California so I really know Mexican food”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My boyfriend deserves an award his poise and self control as he did not reply, as I might have, “Well my abuela wasn’t in the back cooking but the tortillas were fresh,” rather he went on to politely guide our obtuse, white friend into a more neutral discussion about central California geography. I was really surprised that the entire interaction didn’t turn confrontational. Later that night after we saw Sarah to the bus stop. I brought it up as soon as she was out of earshot.  I was shocked and outraged at her condescension in the specific way that white girlfriends are when they are presented with the everyday expressions of white privilege we never noticed until we’re in an “inter-racial” relationship.  He had noticed it too and found it offensive but it wasn’t deal breaker offensive. Sometimes he just wants to have a pleasant evening and get to know a new person without having to explain to that person that her very outlook on life is predicated on assumptions she is only able to make because being a white person lets her walk around unchallenged most of the time. It was more shocking me than it was to him because the behavior is so familiar to him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being the well meaning white person that I am I can’t just let that sit. It’s incumbent upon me to use whatever platform up and tell some other white people to stop doing this shit. So fellow white people please stop whiteclaiming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom How is this an expression of white privilege or a micro-aggression or whatever you snowflakes call these things?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, my dear white person, if you lived near volcano would you claim to know all about volcanoes? Sure, you would be aware of the volcano and you know what it looks like, you might have personal stories about rumblings and ash falls but would you sit across from a known volcanologist and claim that scientific credentials? Likely, if you had any sense of self awareness you would not. Thusly growing up near Chinatown no more make you a sino-cultural anthropologist than growing up in Vancouver Washington makes you a volcanologist. So what is it about being a white person and having some tertiary experience of another culture that makes us feel like we have a form of special knowledge? Let’s just sit with that question for a while especially if it makes us feel uncomfortable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom this sounds like Whitesplaining Don’t you Mean “Whitesplaining”:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good question fellow white person. The most precise definition I can find for white splaining is in the Wiki Dictionary:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;whitesplain (third-person singular simple present whitesplains, present participle whitesplaining, simple past and past participle whitesplained)
(colloquial, derogatory, chiefly Internet) To explain (something) condescendingly to one who is not white, especially regarding race relations or minority behavior, presuming the listener&amp;rsquo;s inferior understanding because of their race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While whitesplaining is a good frame of reference for understanding whiteclaiming, I have coined the term, to call attention, more precisely, to the ways in which white people will use relational, geographic or other forms of proximity to claim expertise. I expect this may seem obvious to persons of color. And one or more person of color may have already coined a phrase for this phenomenon but I haven’t seen it nor found anything in my searches that captures this particular expression of white privilege. I have noticed that its one of the forms of racist dialogue that white people participate in most often around other white people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Stumped Mom this isn’t fair! Can’t I talk about other cultures and other cultural experiences?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course you can.  And you can do it without sounding like a total blowhard. They key is to qualify your statements. For instance. Our sweet, palid Sarah could have said, “I loved eating at the Cal-Mex restaurants in the central valley where I grew up, how would you say this place rates?”  The difference might seem subtle but by being more specific about her experience and expressing curiosity about other, this version of sarah is being humble and genuine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a parent I find it is always more effective to correct a behavior by focusing on replacing it rather than eliminating it. When you meet a person of color and you want to talk to them about your understanding of their culture, try treating them like you would an acclaimed volcanologist. Share specific experiences and ask them contextualized questions in ways that recognize them as the authority on the subject. In time you might find that this increases your understanding and maybe even helps you diversify your social circle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Path of the Cyberslut</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/04/the-path-of-the-cyberslut/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/04/the-path-of-the-cyberslut/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-path-of-the-cyberslut&#34;&gt;The Path of the Cyberslut&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following my separation which occurred under such specifically scandalous circumstances that it would completely compromise my anonymity if I were to recount it,  I went through a period of complete and reckless internet chatting and dating abandon. In my younger days and with my ex-I had dabbled in cybsex, sexting and a radical 90’s trend called phone sex. But in this stretch of newly found adult independence I decided to dive headlong into the most idiosyncratic corners of the online dating scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I slummed it up hard. I swiped right till my hand hurt and I messaged with all kinds of people.  I made it clear in my profile that I was going through an experimental phase. I would start out conversations by making it clear that I was physically unavailable, but many people stuck around to chat it up with me. You’d be amazed what can happen if you instead of recoiling at a kink, you express curiosity and stick around to investigate it.  I asked questions like an explorer and I was rewarded with priceless discoveries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do travel blogs abound? Because people want to see the world and they are willing to invest tremendous amounts of time energy and social capital into doing so.  But you know what is vaster than the entire geography of this beautiful crazy planet? The endless landscape of people’s fantasies and the unfulfilled unconscious needs that feed them. And you can access it all for almost no cost at almost any time of day almost anywhere in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s more than a cliche that the largest human sex organ is the brain. Everyone’s arousal cycles are connected to specific psychological and emotional states. And if you learn how to read your partners and play off their hidden needs and tap into their psychosexual motivations you can increase your chances of keeping your most treasured sexual relationships evergreen.  There is nothing like the internet to give you a short route to learning this art. You can get multiple strangers a day to share their fantasies and kinks and learn a ton about yourself, your interests, boundaries and needs in the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Tinder I talked to a man who’s avatar was a tiny G.I. joe sized man being handled by a giant woman. He was serious about pretending he was tiny. He addressed me as “goddess” All he wanted to talk about was riding around in my pocket and sleeping in my underwear drawer or being rescued from my cat. Talking with him helped me learn to see the signs of when my more orthodox sexual partners wanted to be nurtured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spent weeks messaging a person who wanted to be addressed as if he were his Pembroke Welsh Corgi. I can’t say exactly what I learned from that accept maybe that some men want to be treated like they are as cute as a puppy. On FEELD I came across quite a few single male submissives. I talked one into sending me pictures of himself with a pair of panties in his mouth and he thanked me for ridiculing him afterwards. From this I learned that while I am capable of playing the humiliatrix, I find it draining. My favorites were the “Sissy Maids” these men wanted to clean my house while wearing pantyhose.  I could complain to them about everything I hadn’t done around the house and they would beg me to let them do it.  I almost gave in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were plenty of typical fuck boi’s along the way and a few ernest fellows who wanted to sail off into the sunset with me. I landed myself an IRL regular, who then turned real boyfriend. He encouraged my little hobby, and expressed his boundaries and round it.  He would join me in group chats, sometimes with other couples lending me a hand. This taught me a ton about how he likes to situate himself vis a vis other men.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I got better at reading the patterns between people, I could tell pretty quickly which person would want to be challenged right away, who was secretly looking to be nurtured, who was motivated by praise and who was seeking redemption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my real sex life I developed the confidence to initiate new fantasize and push against the edges of my partners boundaries. And each fantasy success made me feel sexier.  I knew how to take control, and learned to get past a ton of my own hangups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wilder online adventures are done, at least for the foreseeable future. I am in a really great place with my current partner and I’ve lost my virtual wanderlust. But whenever things threaten to get the least bit stale, I have a wealth of slutty experience to fall back on. When I’m feeling unappealing I recall the things I’ve done and said before and I’m not scared to take a little risk to prove to myself that I’ve still got it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I urge you, if you are curious don’t let social stigma be the thing that stops you for exploring fantasy talk and sexting. You owe it to yourself to walk the path of the cyberslut and change your sex life for the better. Over the next few weeks under the tag “Cyber Sluttery” I will be sharing some of what I have learned about sexting, how to make it fun, how to translate it into your IRL sex life and ways to play it safe.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Best Teacher Holiday Gifts</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/29/5-best-teacher-holiday-gifts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/29/5-best-teacher-holiday-gifts/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;5-best-teacher-holiday-gifts&#34;&gt;5 Best Teacher Holiday Gifts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I expect you saw right through my veiled attempt at click bait and you are not expecting to see a straightforward list of suggestions for teacher gifts.  I’m not going try to trick you. It is my opinion that purchasing gifts for school teachers is a socially corrosive and ethically corrupt trend.
I can’t blame you for looking for suggestions, especially if you have a kinder or first grader just starting school and you just found out the other parents have been gifting.  No one wants to get left behind and we all want to be on our kid’s teacher’s good list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you aren’t a parent of young children in America today. You may not even know WTH I am talking about. But here is the deal. My daughter’s school has an actual gift registry for teachers in the principal&amp;rsquo;s office to which parents have been asked to refer to for teacher gifting this year. Her classroom parent message board is full of parents talking about what they are buying the teacher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For many of us gifting the teacher must feel so natural.  Nanny gifts are super common and it just feels like a carry over from that. You’re child’s teacher works hard and likely pours their heart and soul into growing your student’s mind. It feels good to give gifts to the person that does so much for your child for so little compensation. Low teacher salaries and underfunded as well as unequally funded schools are real. I do not dispute that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my many office duties is seeing to the annual gifting at work and I arrange gifts for all of the service providers who go under appreciated, the housekeeping staff, the security people the parking lot guys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re child’s teacher is not a service provider or a business partner or a family member. They are the guardian of your child’s learning, their classroom is a training ground for civic life. I spoke with my own parents about this trend of teacher gifting and they were appalled, at it they saw it as a straightforward bribe. While your intended gift may be small. Your child’s teachers hold a lot of power. Their everyday choices in the classroom and treatment of your child can have long term implications. Especially because in the school to prison pipeline primary school teachers are often the first enforcers and in many ways they act as the day to day cop, and judge for your child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However nice it feels and however generous your heart is there is no way out of. Handing your child’s educator a target gift card, in order to express your gratitude is also meant to enhance your child’s social standing in the school and it is a crude violation of the social compact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That doesn’t mean that I don’t think teachers should be given love.  I love teachers and I know and care about many primary school educators. I also know many of them love their classroom gifts. Here are some alternative ideas to channel that gratitude that don’t cheapen the relationship between student and teacher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Give time. Volunteer to help in the classroom. Ask your teacher what times would be best and take the time to go to the classroom.  You may have to plan this time months out if you are as busy as I am. I take a few vacation days a year to do this.
Work with your child and write a thoughtful thank you note incorporate the spelling vocabulary or English lessons in your child’s classroom into the note.
Write a letter to your child’s principal to tell the principal how you appreciate your teacher and their exemplary work. Or write a letter nominating your teacher for an award.&lt;br /&gt;
Ask your teacher if there is a big ticket item needed for the classroom for them to be better at their work. Start a gift pool with the rest of the classroom parents toward purchasing this item.
Get involved politically. Write your local state representative to tell them about the conditions in your school. Support a campaign that your local teachers union is involved in.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Replace Your Husband with Amazon Prime</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/26/replace-your-husband-with-amazon-prime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 13:16:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/26/replace-your-husband-with-amazon-prime/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;replace-your-husband-with-amazon-prime&#34;&gt;Replace Your Husband with Amazon Prime&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dearest Stumpers,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Do you mind if I call you Dearest? I feel like we’re getting so much closer these days)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope that one of the things I can accomplish through sharing is to show that I have learned the hard way so that you don’t have to. My divorce struck like a sudden car wreck, the causes of which were multiplicitous.  Explaining it all might take going into the sort of exacting excavation and slow revelation that might make you feel like you were being made to watch Roger Stone’s JFK and I am not a lazy, sophomore American History teacher, so I am not going to waste four hours of your time trying to convince you of a version of events, when there is no ready path toward rectification. I can’t tell you how to avoid a divorce but I can tell you some of the ways I coped with the material conditions in the immediate aftermath.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My ex demanded an instant and complete separation of parenting, household duties and finances within two weeks of his announcement of his intention to separate. Thanks to Medical debt and his recent stint of unemployment times this lead to a perilous financial situation. But the real squeeze I found in my day to day was time. In our marriage the division of labor generally landed with me managing almost all of the cooking and cleaning, childcare and household planning, while he did all of the running of last minute errands and managed the finances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being the errand boy was a role my ex relished. He got to be the hero without having to do much planning or thinking or strategizing and he got to leave the house where he was constantly reminded of the responsibilities he was avoiding. It suited me as well, I hate running errands and I loved being able to let him bask in the adulation and accomplishment of picking up things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This arrangement lasted for 14 years and suddenly losing it was practically debilitating. Some of my most frustrating moments in the months following the separation were the days when I ran out of pet food, or paper towels, and I didn’t realize it until right before my daughter’s bedtime. I can’t say I was at my best in those moments and often solved problems through force majeure. I have called favors with family members, or friends and implemented compromise solutions. My cat survived off of my-exes left behind starkist tuna pouches for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once I got past the initial shock of having my life turned upside down. I started planning ahead and that is when I fell into the embrace of Amazon Prime. Right here is where I place my disclaimer or at the very least acknowledge my own hypocrisy. I’ve read the headlines and I have heard about Amazon’s treatment of workers, its disruption to the brick and mortar economy, the environmental impact of its shipping and packaging practices.I know but&amp;hellip;when parenting we all have to make choices and when our principles are stacked against our children’s material comfort, as well as our own sanity sometimes we compromise on principle. The convenience, the pre-planning and the economics were just too seductive to resist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As long as I can stay 2-5 days ahead of any particular need I can get it at a competitive price without having to run an errand or be pressured to give a blowjob before I go to sleep. Now I have almost all of my non-perishable household supplies set up on subscription or frequent order on Amazon Prime. It’s almost too easy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As much as I pre-plan life still presents unexpected challenges that can’t wait on free two day shipping. I still have make quick stops at the store before picking up the kid from after school care. And sometimes, in select emergencies, I pull up Prime Now and order some instant satisfaction. Prime Now is certainly more expensive at the front end then asking the ol’hubs to go to the store but If you&amp;rsquo;re anything like me you will find you can more than make up the savings through frugal measures that were previously inconceivable during married life. Without the ex I have brought my utilities bills down by about 20% in the last two years, I have nearly completely eliminating spending on restaurants and takeout through careful planning and home cooking which I will talk more about in my Sunday Cooking section. And that doesn’t even account for the gas money I have save without him inventing errands to run to avoid doing household chores.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of Course this doesn’t replace childcare, or companionship or sex ( can get a vibrator with free 2 day shipping)  or the added financial stability of two incomes. But getting things shipped to my door for free within two days of ordering it totally outweighs the life of gaslighting and sexual coercion I lived in exchange for my old errand runner. If you live alone with children it’s hard to overstate the value of home delivery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So dear reader, if you’re worried that you can’t make it on your own. I can offer you this one reassurance. With a little bit of planning and some careful budgeting you too can replace your husband with Amazon prime.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrooge Shaming</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/22/scrooge-shaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/22/scrooge-shaming/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-casual-cruelty-of-scrooge-shaming&#34;&gt;The Casual Cruelty of Scrooge Shaming&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Proceed with care and self directed compassion.This post deals with trauma triggers surrounding the loss of a child.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The clock has struck! Tis Thanksgiving and America has officially plunged into a six week, long commercially fueled onslaught of seasonal Christmas themed celebration, commonly known as the Holiday Season.  An army of Christmas enthusiasts enabled by naked commercial interest go to work and transform virtually all public, commercial and private spaces (save those of the non Christian religions) to conform to their concept of winter festiveness. This seasonal mania touches every sense and acts on nearly every object. Christmas versions of pretty much anything can be purchased with the click of a mouse. There are indoor and outdoor decorations, plants, greetings, colors, fragrances,foods,  drinks, packaging, and the all pervasive christmas music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the most part and for the majority of Americans this seasonal transformation is a welcome tradition that ties them to fond memories and helps them bond with their families and communities. As they shop for presents and talk of playing Santa they share commonalities with coworkers and friends. Tradition and ritual are powerful things, they enhance memory recall and emotional connection by reinforcing the sensory patterns that link us our memories to the present. Rituals that incorporate all  of the senses and include community elements are especially powerful. Anyone who has experienced a Catholic mass with incense, candles, the liturgy and the eucharist can speak to this. But the same things that can connect people to feelings of community, memories of joy and a sense of awe can act as direct sensory triggers for trauma.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is easy to get carried away at Christmas and the feeling of sharing convivial seasonal joy can be intoxicating. This also creates tremendous pressure to conform to the expectations of shared  rituals even if you have legitimate reasons to abstain from celebrations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever called a person a Scrooge, a Grinch or a humbug? Chances are you have. Usually it is intended as a gentle form of peer pressuring, because one of the joys of the Christmas is supposed to be bringing cheer - even to the reluctant or grouchy. In my younger days I joined in on the chiding some of the, so called, Scrooges in my life, for ruining the fun. More recently I have had these very epitaphs lobbed at me.  Like a new tradition,  since I acquired PTSD within the tableau of the Christmas celebration, my reticence toward Christmas celebrations has made me into the office Scrooge.
PTSD triggers can be a tricky thing. Sufferers can learn to manage their responses to distressing stimuli but doing so takes energy.  For people like me, who have experienced tragedy at Christmas, the reminders of the worst day of our lives are everywhere we look, hear and smell and they are nonstop for a solid six weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have never heard of anyone telling a war veteran to “get over it” if he finds fireworks unnerving but I do know mother who lost her child at Christmas and saw his lifeless two and a half year old body laid out in the same room as a splendidly decorated douglas fir, be told to, “Get over it,” when she didn’t want a Christmas tree set up in her living room. Even people who know about this mother’s loss show an easy and course callousness toward the ways the seasonal celebration affects her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Character of Ebenezer Scrooge, like so many literary figures that have been commercialized has been over-simplified by popular depictions. He has become a symbol of greed and social apathy.  A Christmas Carol is a story of spiritual journey and personal redemption. But is is most frequently referenced in order to  insult, people who are likely depressed, isolated or traumatized. In truth, Scrooge was an emotionally neglected child and a scarred individual. His Journey through the past, present and the future helps him see the story of his life through the experiences and feelings of others. The message of Dickens’s tale was not that we should shame people who are different into conformity, for the sake of our own joy and entertainment, it was that if given space and shown patience and compassion, anyone can live a life of charity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Christmas I am asking for one thing. This Christmas I wish for an end to Scrooge Shaming. Please try extending understanding to the so called Scrooges among us. Their negative reaction to Christmas overload is more likely a response to pain than an attempt to spoil your fun. There is nothing joyful or festive about shaming people for experiencing negative feelings. The tradition of holiday name calling and peer pressuring is one we can all do without.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catalogue of Privledge</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/20/catalogue-of-privledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/20/catalogue-of-privledge/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;catalogue-of-privilege&#34;&gt;Catalogue of Privilege&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stumpers:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you mind if I call you Stumpers? It feels more personal than Dear Reader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the principles I have committed myself in this endeavor is include “privilege awareness”. I operate on the theory that the first step to creating a more equitable and just society is to acknowledge inequality. For those of us that benefit in some way from inequality we need to be able to name those benefits, we must be aware of our privilege. In an attempt enhance my own privilege awareness I worked on creating a Catalog of Privilege.  I am sharing it with my readers in interest of transparency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Actually spent more time developing this than any of my other posts. I’ve been working on it for close to 8 weeks. The primary reason it took me so long is I tried to create a two column feature with privileges in one column and disadvantages in another. And then I realized what I really need for this post is the privileges. The disadvantages were unnecessary. My disadvantages are going to come out in my writing. They are the part of my story I don’t have to remind myself about because they create challenges in my life every day.  The very nature of privilege is that it doesn’t demand our attention in order for us to succeed.  Millions of people are walking around every day completely oblivious to it and while it might be holding them back from some spiritual, intellectual and relationship growth it generally doesn’t hold people back in any material form.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I plan to update this list as my consciousness expands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table style=&#34;border: 1px solid black; border-collapse: collapse&#34;&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;h2&gt;Privilege Catalog:&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;White&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            This is the Big Grand-daddy of all privileges. I carry all of the markers of Whiteness: White parents, white siblings, pale skin, a first and last name with English origins, the whole thing. This impacts my life and the way people treat me in ways that I can only view by contrasting my experience with those of people who do not receive this treatment, which is frustrating because I can’t even look at it without being ethnocentric.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Straight (ish)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            I put this down in the privilege column with a few caveats.Not all of my sexual relationships have been heterosexual. I’m in a long term heterosexual relationship, so for most social purposes I carry straight privilege. Personally I see this most in the stories society tells me about the relationships I am in and how desirable they are. The relationships that feel most natural for me personally are reflected everywhere in our culture.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cis Gender&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            With the exception of a period of my life that I will call my awkward phase, during which I was frequently mistaken for a boy and harangued for my lack of appropriate girlish femininity, I have always fit squarely and comfortably into the gender I was assigned at birth. I have all kinds of qualms with the ways we enforce gender but here I am, quite assuredly a woman.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;American&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            I was born ensconced incomparable physical security of the 20th century American Military Industrial Complex. Wherever I go the power of my nation of origin and its economic and military might has an influence on my personal safety and esteem.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Temporarily Able Bodied&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            I enjoy the luxury of experiencing an urban and consumer landscape that is engineered almost exclusively for bodies that are sized and function like mine.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Average-ish body size&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            While almost all women experience fat shaming because that’s just how messed up our society is, I wear a size L in most stores and that regular everyday dress size exempts me from the bullying, and marginalization people with larger bodies experience.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Conventionally Attractive&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            I don’t want to talk about this there is no way to talk about it without “humble bragging” and no one likes humble braggers. It’s a thing and it has been shown to make the world more well disposed toward me than it otherwise could be.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;        
                                                            
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to Cook this Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/15/what-to-cook-this-thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 14:27:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/15/what-to-cook-this-thanksgiving/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-to-cook-this-thanksgiving&#34;&gt;What to Cook this Thanksgiving&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is Thanksgiving the only day of the year that you get serious about cooking?  If you’re like most Americans it probably is. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/personalfinance/2017/09/27/90-americans-dont-like-cook-and-its-costing-them-thousands-each-year/708033001/&#34;&gt;Recent surveys&lt;/a&gt; and market trends like meal kits and steady restaurant growth as well as the ever popularity of processed and frozen foods indicate that most Americans don’t cook.  Cooking,like so many other activities in America has become a commodified spectector’s sport. While less than 15% of us enjoy cooking, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.marketingcharts.com/television-13719&#34;&gt;80% of us enjoy&lt;/a&gt; watching cooking shows. Thanksgiving, however centers around a traditional old fashioned home-cooked meal. Our popular images of this Holiday include friends and family gathered around a copious meal produced with loving care. For one day a year millions of would be home cooks roll up their sleeves, open up cookbooks, consult packaging instructions, and even more likely cooking blogs, and get to work. And the results? They are mostly pathetic.  Millions of Turkeys are lead to the slaughter for the Holiday and most of them turn out dry, over oiled, under flavored or fall victim to countless other faux pas.  To eat these birds family members drown the meat in overcooked gravy.  Hundreds of thousands of us pretend to enjoy dishes so dreadful they only get made once a year.  Meanwhile millions of pounds of food waste are produced because too many people are trying to get in on the cooking action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take, for instance, my sister’s green-bean casserole. This dish is is a travesty, a mushy, salty travesty composed of canned products dumped into a casserole dish and baked until warm. If you are like my sister - if you you can’t tell the difference between mincing and chopping, if you don’t know your chef’s knife from your paring knife and and you’re hoping to find recipe’s and tips in blogs, please stop now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re doing the culinary equivalent of attempting to run a half marathon when you’ve never run further than a mile in your life. You are not ready for this. Meanwhile there are a few Americans, the few, the proud the 15% that enjoy cooking and cook most nights of the week, we have been training for this day all year. Your cooking compatriots have been boiling, roasting, chopping, slicing braising, and chilling call year long. Fifteen percent is a small minority but still a significant one. Chances are you know and love one of these people. If you want my advice, you should call this person-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom who Makes phone calls?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Right then text this person  and ask them what they want to do for the holiday, ask for instructions on how you can help and make sure to get yourself invited. Humble yourself before their experience and preparation, as the novice you are, before the master. If you are told just to bring wine, pick up a good bottle of Bordeaux.  Arrive on time, not early and not late because your gracious cook has been prepping for a while and is relying on years of experience to time every dish just right. And when it’s all said and done when the once majestic indigenous American bird is naught but a stripped carcass, as uncles are dozing on couches while aunts look at holiday circulars and children turn on early holiday specials, do the damn dishes and help box the leftovers! Not everyone can be lucky enough to know a home cook that is up to the task.  On the day of Giving Thanks you should lean into gratitude and recognize the home cooks in your life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But stumped Mom I want to radiate in the joy of knowing I fed my family!  I want to take the credit for making the blessed thanksgiving event a success!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If that’s what you want if and if you are really sincere about it. Start reading my Sunday Cooking section (starting this next Sunday) and get ready to train hard for Thanksgiving 2019 because all things worth doing are worth doing right and it’s going to take at least a year of applied training to get you ready.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down With The PTA</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/08/down-with-the-pta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/08/down-with-the-pta/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;down-with-the-pta&#34;&gt;Down With The PTA&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No bourgeoisie institution makes me want to lock arms with my proletariat brethren and forcibly seize the means of production from the soft, plump hands of our capitalist overlords quite like the Parent Teacher Association otherwise known as PTAs or PTOs .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their reasons for existing and means of sustaining themselves are entirely dependent of systems and structures that perpetuate inequality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are you talking about Stumped Mom? The PTA strengthens our communities and schools by promoting parental involvement at our schools and brings much needed resources and interest on to our campuses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumpers I can’t blame you for taking this perspective, because this is entirely what society wants you to think and I’m pretty sure it’s what makes those self righteous PTA board members look down their noses at us barely making it schleppers. Mom’s like me who are lucky if they get their kids to before-school care with clean faces each morning, let alone make it aross town after work to make the monthly PTA by 5:30 p.m. on a Wednesday are the famous objects of PTA mom disdain. I will confess, my own personal laziness makes me resent their industriousness. However, there is more to my beef with the PTA than simple personal envy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But stumped Mom, our schools are chronically underfunded, there is insecurity in staffing, and the teachers are underpaid and parental involvement at school helps kids to succeed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do not contest those points but let us and take a more critical eye and ask some crucial questions. When we do we find the classist, racist patriarchal and capitalist structures that buttress these groups are easily laid bare&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes for a good PTA?&lt;br /&gt;
Parents with organizational skills and spare time
A Community with Resources and Capital
Relationships and Connections between those parents and the people with the Capital&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of these critical components more abundant in more affluent communities, which thanks to the well documented racial income gap in this country, are overwhelmingly white. PTA participation is also a ladies game, with Mom’s far outnumbering Dad’s in participation. So the pressure to join and support the PTA weighs heavily on women adding to their emotional labor burden and straining marriages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t just take my word for it. Reports show that PTA fundraising contributes to the achievement gap, that has been well documented, between white and affluent neighborhoods and communities with less resources.  And even in diverse or well integrated schools white parents hold a disproportionate influence over decision making.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cross sections factors that make for successful PTA’s allow affluent mostly-white, people to perpetuate the privilege of their children over that of others. And most of this happens on the barely recognized volunteer efforts of women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your a parent with a kid in school you likely understand the pressure to join the PTA.  I get invitations in the school newsletter every week. Parents pressure each other into pouring time, money and energy into stop gap measures meant to fill in the holes created by and tragically unequal public education system. Many of us visit our schools and see run down facilities, stressed staff, and outdated materials. We want to do whatever we can to help our children. But shouldn’t we be talking about campaigning against the policies that undermine funding and support for public education?  Nobody talks about this at back to school night or in the school newsletter. Instead we are treated to constant plugs for more PTA volunteers and lend special thank you’s to those lovely PTA Mom’s (sorry Dads the stats show this is a ladies game).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a more just society we would stop valorizing the systemic hoarding of privilege through support of Parent Teacher Associations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But those PTA invitations won’t stop. So what’s a woke parent to do? The next time a PTA pusher approaches me on the school yard. Here is what I’m saying:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No thanks I’m going to invest what little spare time I have in direct involvement in the classroom and any spare resources I have will be dedicated to campaigns for just and equal schools,”  but I’m also gonna wait till my daughter is ready to start our daily foot-race home before I shout “DOWN WITH THE PTA” as I flee the scene. For PTA Moms are as brutal as they are industrious and I’m not hanging around for a beating.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No duh</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/01/no-duh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 19:56:48 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/01/no-duh/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A word of caution: The following post has heavy feels and addresses sexual trauma.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;noduh&#34;&gt;#NoDuh&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was eleven the first time a friend confided in me that she had been sexually abused.
I was fourteen the next time. When a friend told me that a neighbor had molested her and another girl on her street. I was sixteen when an adult, female, relative told me her abuse story.
I was 18 the first time a male told me his story….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pattern continues like a thread through my life. The confidences weaving in during late night talks in bedrooms, in basements, on rooftops - with hushed tones, clasped hands and numbed, griefed expressions. As a girl and later a woman, no-one taught me how to receive these stories, what to do with them or how to contain them but as they came it was clear to me that they must be contained. Like monthly cycles, and family christmas card lists this was something for women and girls to manage; quietly, discreetly and independently. My whole life prepared me for it. The tiny details of my socialization as a girl taught me to listen, to feel and not to act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2017 when #metoo splashed on to the scene my initial reaction was “#noduh” or “#abouttime”. How could this possibly be a surprise to anyone? But as things moved forward I realized no one was really shocked by the stories or the prevalence. The shock was the act. The act of women speaking publicly and people paying attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new refrain of the #metoo backlash is a so called “rejection of victimhood”. A slight few conservative women had come out to say it that they two have been abused but that it doesn’t matter it hasn’t affected them, “Let’s all move on” They say “Let’s talk about something else.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The weekend of October 5th I was seething with anger. There was a walkout to protest the pending Kavanaugh confirmation in my city but I knew participation would get me disciplined at work. I can’t risk the income stream that feeds my child. When the confirmation was completed.I wanted to do more than just walk out. I wanted to wreck things. I wanted to burn it down. I wanted to go through the richest, whitest neighborhood in town and rip the male symbols off of old volvos. I wanted to smash the windows out of a hooters and drag frat boys from their beer splattered dens into the streets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had my daughter by myself all weekend, she is six.  We, ran errands, got out the halloween decorations, painted mini pumpkins, and cooked together. I took some great photos to send to her great grandparents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I got to work on Monday the 8th. I wanted, so badly, speak my anger to my co-workers. I talked about the pumpkin painting.  Unless you were working in media or workplace diversity or education no one was talking about it.  When I see other parents, we don’t talk about it. Sometimes at the dojo we make sad jokes about it. But even there we dampen our anger.  We chuckle it off as just another postmodern absurdity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our late night whisperings have a new sphere now. Don’t talk about it with your neighbors or co-workers. We should take it to twitter where can feel like we are telling the world but people can filter it out of their feeds. Block it. Silence it. Stick it back into those virtual version of bedrooms, rooftops and basements so women can get back to carrying it without showing it so as not to upset the men around us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a mother of a daughter I am constantly vigilant against signs of a threat that could come from anywhere. I want her to be able to declare her boundaries, to defend them if necessary and to tell if someone crosses them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other day my daughter presented with a rash on her vulva and labia. I asked her gently, “Have you been rubbing your vulva a-lot?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No” She said casually&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I squeezed out a dollop of cream onto her finger for her, I followed up in the most casual and clinical tone I could manage “Has anyone else been touching your vulva?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No” she replied,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A wave of qualified relief washed over me. As far as I can tell she’s been kept safe thus far from the most frightening forms abuse or exploitation. But we live in a world where the Kavanaughs win and even young girls have their secrets. And what of the faithful night when she is initiated into the real covenant of womanhood? When she becomes the first keeper of someone’s horrifying story? How am I preparing her for that? I haven’t seen it in the parenting guides, her pediatrician hasn’t mentioned it. Will there be hashtag for it?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How did we get here?</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/10/25/how-did-we-get-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/10/25/how-did-we-get-here/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;dear-reader&#34;&gt;Dear reader:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All endeavors must have a beginning and this endeavor will begin with an attempt to answer a question. How did we get here? We; being you the reader me the writer. Here being the virtual space that manifests itself in this blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let us start with me. I am here because I became convinced of the narcissistic conceit that the vast and overcrowded world of mommy blogs, feminist writings, parenting advice and armchair political philosophy could possibly benefit from a space dedicated to my idiosyncratic musings. While I am not specifically trained as a writer, I have always carried a certain vanity concerning my language skills and I have been nudged along by a few people in my life with increasing urgency to channel myself into writing. So reader it appears I am able to write, I am driven to write, I can write and I am going to write.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My life is quite full and I have no shortage of responsibilities. I have a child, a full time office type job, a dog, a cat, a three bedroom home to maintain, an uncooperative co-parent, a hungry and distracting boyfriend to feed and enjoy, and a fairly demanding recreational fitness hobby. A blog is like a whole other THING to take on. If I must write could I not collect it all in a private journal and keep it to myself?  I have attempted this but I have never been able to sustain it past thinking about how great it would be to set aside journaling time each day. Journaling is like a romantic fantasy that clearly belongs to some other class of much cooler, authentic and self assured sort of person. I can’t motivate myself to do it. It seems I require the focus of a potential audience. I would be content to stuff messages into a bottle and toss them into the ocean. That distribution method is probably just as likely to reach as many people another mommy blog.  But I do not want to add any more than I already have to the Pacific Garbage Patch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright let’s get to you, because we all want to hear about ourselves. Who are you? Most likely you’re someone very close to me because this is the first post on a new blog and I haven’t even figured out how to get readers, so my first audience will most likely be a tight and trusted circle. If you are someone very close to me I ask that you take my sharing this place with you as an evidence of trust. My goal for this space is for it to be a capital R-E-A-L real. I want to be as transparent as I can be about opinions, perspectives and experiences. But I also have people in my life who depend on me who I would like to protect. Privacy doesn’t really exist in  the internet world. So if you do know me or you read this and you are able to cross reference enough about my geographic location and life particulars to triangulate who I am then you know me well enough to picture the face of my beautiful innocent child. That face that will not be appear on this blog. If you need help calling that face to mind; find me on FB. I trust you to protect her by keeping quiet about who I am because the internet can be a cruel place and there is no telling what will set people off against a writer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a little bit of luck, persistence and pluck, you could be another sort of reader.  We shall call you Not too Distant Future Reader (NTDFR).  If your a NTDFR I am guessing you became engaged through social media promotion or maybe viral sharing of my work.  You read through my more recent and more mature posts and now you’re working your way through my back catalogue. I can’t say much about you NTDFR, but I can say that your haircut is way better than it was when I wrote this. Just take a look at that selfie you took back in the fall of 2018 what were you thinking?  Perhaps we share some things in common. Maybe you’re a recently divorced parent looking for perspectives on making it work that challenge the old “single mom” paradigm?  Maybe you ask yourself, “am I the only who feels like this is not okay?” just about everywhere you go. You’re also way more patient and smart than the internet marketing firm surveys say you are because here you are reading all the way down into word 740, or so, of this post and it doesn’t even have a slideshow.  And they all said smartphones were killing our attention spans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We covered me and we’ve talked about you, so what of here? Here is a place for exploring ideas about 21st century parenthood, through the perspective of a flawed, divorced, full-time working mom, living in a rapidly changing west coast american city, without any “my kids are my life” or “#blessed” bullshit. I plan to be frank about things that can get prickly, issues like race, sex, dating, class and money.  I hope you’ll to laugh at my failures and maybe celebrate some triumphs with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yours Truly,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>