<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/about_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/about_me/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About me:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a fiction - an artistic alter ego created to emphasize key traits of my creator’s personal identity, hile intentionally masking others. All biographies and human self presentations include exaggeration as well as obfuscation for it is only in fiction that we dispense with the pretense of factual authenticity, and free ourselves to explore larger truths. That being said, I identify as a slutty, white, divorced mother of one in the year 2018. I live in a West Coast American city, there is no hiding that. I am college educated and I own a modest home in an, “up and coming neighborhood” (The whole foods 8 blocks up just opened 2 years ago). I have a job that pays me just enough to be able to afford the mortgage on that home and do enough repairs to keep it from falling down. So I guess that makes me part of the “coastal elite.” My favorite Muppet is Gonzo. I am a weirdo, who has learned to assimilate with everyday life but every, single day I see elephants in rooms and I want to talk about them. This room is parenting and mothering in contemporary America and I want to talk about pesky pachyderms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In the words of the great Rowdie Roddie Piper, “I am here to kickass and chew bubblegum and I am all out of bubblegum!” - Stumped Mom is here to slay!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Path of the Cyberslut</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/04/the-path-of-the-cyberslut/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/04/the-path-of-the-cyberslut/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-path-of-the-cyberslut&#34;&gt;The Path of the Cyberslut&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following my separation which occurred under such specifically scandalous circumstances that it would completely compromise my anonymity if I were to recount it,  I went through a period of complete and reckless internet chatting and dating abandon. In my younger days and with my ex-I had dabbled in cybsex, sexting and a radical 90’s trend called phone sex. But in this stretch of newly found adult independence I decided to dive headlong into the most idiosyncratic corners of the online dating scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I slummed it up hard. I swiped right till my hand hurt and I messaged with all kinds of people.  I made it clear in my profile that I was going through an experimental phase. I would start out conversations by making it clear that I was physically unavailable, but many people stuck around to chat it up with me. You’d be amazed what can happen if you instead of recoiling at a kink, you express curiosity and stick around to investigate it.  I asked questions like an explorer and I was rewarded with priceless discoveries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do travel blogs abound? Because people want to see the world and they are willing to invest tremendous amounts of time energy and social capital into doing so.  But you know what is vaster than the entire geography of this beautiful crazy planet? The endless landscape of people’s fantasies and the unfulfilled unconscious needs that feed them. And you can access it all for almost no cost at almost any time of day almost anywhere in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s more than a cliche that the largest human sex organ is the brain. Everyone’s arousal cycles are connected to specific psychological and emotional states. And if you learn how to read your partners and play off their hidden needs and tap into their psychosexual motivations you can increase your chances of keeping your most treasured sexual relationships evergreen.  There is nothing like the internet to give you a short route to learning this art. You can get multiple strangers a day to share their fantasies and kinks and learn a ton about yourself, your interests, boundaries and needs in the process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Tinder I talked to a man who’s avatar was a tiny G.I. joe sized man being handled by a giant woman. He was serious about pretending he was tiny. He addressed me as “goddess” All he wanted to talk about was riding around in my pocket and sleeping in my underwear drawer or being rescued from my cat. Talking with him helped me learn to see the signs of when my more orthodox sexual partners wanted to be nurtured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spent weeks messaging a person who wanted to be addressed as if he were his Pembroke Welsh Corgi. I can’t say exactly what I learned from that accept maybe that some men want to be treated like they are as cute as a puppy. On FEELD I came across quite a few single male submissives. I talked one into sending me pictures of himself with a pair of panties in his mouth and he thanked me for ridiculing him afterwards. From this I learned that while I am capable of playing the humiliatrix, I find it draining. My favorites were the “Sissy Maids” these men wanted to clean my house while wearing pantyhose.  I could complain to them about everything I hadn’t done around the house and they would beg me to let them do it.  I almost gave in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were plenty of typical fuck boi’s along the way and a few ernest fellows who wanted to sail off into the sunset with me. I landed myself an IRL regular, who then turned real boyfriend. He encouraged my little hobby, and expressed his boundaries and round it.  He would join me in group chats, sometimes with other couples lending me a hand. This taught me a ton about how he likes to situate himself vis a vis other men.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I got better at reading the patterns between people, I could tell pretty quickly which person would want to be challenged right away, who was secretly looking to be nurtured, who was motivated by praise and who was seeking redemption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my real sex life I developed the confidence to initiate new fantasize and push against the edges of my partners boundaries. And each fantasy success made me feel sexier.  I knew how to take control, and learned to get past a ton of my own hangups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wilder online adventures are done, at least for the foreseeable future. I am in a really great place with my current partner and I’ve lost my virtual wanderlust. But whenever things threaten to get the least bit stale, I have a wealth of slutty experience to fall back on. When I’m feeling unappealing I recall the things I’ve done and said before and I’m not scared to take a little risk to prove to myself that I’ve still got it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I urge you, if you are curious don’t let social stigma be the thing that stops you for exploring fantasy talk and sexting. You owe it to yourself to walk the path of the cyberslut and change your sex life for the better. Over the next few weeks under the tag “Cyber Sluttery” I will be sharing some of what I have learned about sexting, how to make it fun, how to translate it into your IRL sex life and ways to play it safe.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Best Teacher Holiday Gifts</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/29/5-best-teacher-holiday-gifts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/29/5-best-teacher-holiday-gifts/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;5-best-teacher-holiday-gifts&#34;&gt;5 Best Teacher Holiday Gifts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I expect you saw right through my veiled attempt at click bait and you are not expecting to see a straightforward list of suggestions for teacher gifts.  I’m not going try to trick you. It is my opinion that purchasing gifts for school teachers is a socially corrosive and ethically corrupt trend.
I can’t blame you for looking for suggestions, especially if you have a kinder or first grader just starting school and you just found out the other parents have been gifting.  No one wants to get left behind and we all want to be on our kid’s teacher’s good list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you aren’t a parent of young children in America today. You may not even know WTH I am talking about. But here is the deal. My daughter’s school has an actual gift registry for teachers in the principal&amp;rsquo;s office to which parents have been asked to refer to for teacher gifting this year. Her classroom parent message board is full of parents talking about what they are buying the teacher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For many of us gifting the teacher must feel so natural.  Nanny gifts are super common and it just feels like a carry over from that. You’re child’s teacher works hard and likely pours their heart and soul into growing your student’s mind. It feels good to give gifts to the person that does so much for your child for so little compensation. Low teacher salaries and underfunded as well as unequally funded schools are real. I do not dispute that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of my many office duties is seeing to the annual gifting at work and I arrange gifts for all of the service providers who go under appreciated, the housekeeping staff, the security people the parking lot guys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re child’s teacher is not a service provider or a business partner or a family member. They are the guardian of your child’s learning, their classroom is a training ground for civic life. I spoke with my own parents about this trend of teacher gifting and they were appalled, at it they saw it as a straightforward bribe. While your intended gift may be small. Your child’s teachers hold a lot of power. Their everyday choices in the classroom and treatment of your child can have long term implications. Especially because in the school to prison pipeline primary school teachers are often the first enforcers and in many ways they act as the day to day cop, and judge for your child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However nice it feels and however generous your heart is there is no way out of. Handing your child’s educator a target gift card, in order to express your gratitude is also meant to enhance your child’s social standing in the school and it is a crude violation of the social compact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That doesn’t mean that I don’t think teachers should be given love.  I love teachers and I know and care about many primary school educators. I also know many of them love their classroom gifts. Here are some alternative ideas to channel that gratitude that don’t cheapen the relationship between student and teacher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Give time. Volunteer to help in the classroom. Ask your teacher what times would be best and take the time to go to the classroom.  You may have to plan this time months out if you are as busy as I am. I take a few vacation days a year to do this.
Work with your child and write a thoughtful thank you note incorporate the spelling vocabulary or English lessons in your child’s classroom into the note.
Write a letter to your child’s principal to tell the principal how you appreciate your teacher and their exemplary work. Or write a letter nominating your teacher for an award.&lt;br /&gt;
Ask your teacher if there is a big ticket item needed for the classroom for them to be better at their work. Start a gift pool with the rest of the classroom parents toward purchasing this item.
Get involved politically. Write your local state representative to tell them about the conditions in your school. Support a campaign that your local teachers union is involved in.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Replace Your Husband with Amazon Prime</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/26/replace-your-husband-with-amazon-prime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 13:16:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/26/replace-your-husband-with-amazon-prime/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;replace-your-husband-with-amazon-prime&#34;&gt;Replace Your Husband with Amazon Prime&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dearest Stumpers,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Do you mind if I call you Dearest? I feel like we’re getting so much closer these days)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope that one of the things I can accomplish through sharing is to show that I have learned the hard way so that you don’t have to. My divorce struck like a sudden car wreck, the causes of which were multiplicitous.  Explaining it all might take going into the sort of exacting excavation and slow revelation that might make you feel like you were being made to watch Roger Stone’s JFK and I am not a lazy, sophomore American History teacher, so I am not going to waste four hours of your time trying to convince you of a version of events, when there is no ready path toward rectification. I can’t tell you how to avoid a divorce but I can tell you some of the ways I coped with the material conditions in the immediate aftermath.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My ex demanded an instant and complete separation of parenting, household duties and finances within two weeks of his announcement of his intention to separate. Thanks to Medical debt and his recent stint of unemployment times this lead to a perilous financial situation. But the real squeeze I found in my day to day was time. In our marriage the division of labor generally landed with me managing almost all of the cooking and cleaning, childcare and household planning, while he did all of the running of last minute errands and managed the finances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being the errand boy was a role my ex relished. He got to be the hero without having to do much planning or thinking or strategizing and he got to leave the house where he was constantly reminded of the responsibilities he was avoiding. It suited me as well, I hate running errands and I loved being able to let him bask in the adulation and accomplishment of picking up things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This arrangement lasted for 14 years and suddenly losing it was practically debilitating. Some of my most frustrating moments in the months following the separation were the days when I ran out of pet food, or paper towels, and I didn’t realize it until right before my daughter’s bedtime. I can’t say I was at my best in those moments and often solved problems through force majeure. I have called favors with family members, or friends and implemented compromise solutions. My cat survived off of my-exes left behind starkist tuna pouches for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once I got past the initial shock of having my life turned upside down. I started planning ahead and that is when I fell into the embrace of Amazon Prime. Right here is where I place my disclaimer or at the very least acknowledge my own hypocrisy. I’ve read the headlines and I have heard about Amazon’s treatment of workers, its disruption to the brick and mortar economy, the environmental impact of its shipping and packaging practices.I know but&amp;hellip;when parenting we all have to make choices and when our principles are stacked against our children’s material comfort, as well as our own sanity sometimes we compromise on principle. The convenience, the pre-planning and the economics were just too seductive to resist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As long as I can stay 2-5 days ahead of any particular need I can get it at a competitive price without having to run an errand or be pressured to give a blowjob before I go to sleep. Now I have almost all of my non-perishable household supplies set up on subscription or frequent order on Amazon Prime. It’s almost too easy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As much as I pre-plan life still presents unexpected challenges that can’t wait on free two day shipping. I still have make quick stops at the store before picking up the kid from after school care. And sometimes, in select emergencies, I pull up Prime Now and order some instant satisfaction. Prime Now is certainly more expensive at the front end then asking the ol’hubs to go to the store but If you&amp;rsquo;re anything like me you will find you can more than make up the savings through frugal measures that were previously inconceivable during married life. Without the ex I have brought my utilities bills down by about 20% in the last two years, I have nearly completely eliminating spending on restaurants and takeout through careful planning and home cooking which I will talk more about in my Sunday Cooking section. And that doesn’t even account for the gas money I have save without him inventing errands to run to avoid doing household chores.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of Course this doesn’t replace childcare, or companionship or sex ( can get a vibrator with free 2 day shipping)  or the added financial stability of two incomes. But getting things shipped to my door for free within two days of ordering it totally outweighs the life of gaslighting and sexual coercion I lived in exchange for my old errand runner. If you live alone with children it’s hard to overstate the value of home delivery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So dear reader, if you’re worried that you can’t make it on your own. I can offer you this one reassurance. With a little bit of planning and some careful budgeting you too can replace your husband with Amazon prime.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrooge Shaming</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/22/scrooge-shaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/22/scrooge-shaming/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-casual-cruelty-of-scrooge-shaming&#34;&gt;The Casual Cruelty of Scrooge Shaming&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Proceed with care and self directed compassion.This post deals with trauma triggers surrounding the loss of a child.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The clock has struck! Tis Thanksgiving and America has officially plunged into a six week, long commercially fueled onslaught of seasonal Christmas themed celebration, commonly known as the Holiday Season.  An army of Christmas enthusiasts enabled by naked commercial interest go to work and transform virtually all public, commercial and private spaces (save those of the non Christian religions) to conform to their concept of winter festiveness. This seasonal mania touches every sense and acts on nearly every object. Christmas versions of pretty much anything can be purchased with the click of a mouse. There are indoor and outdoor decorations, plants, greetings, colors, fragrances,foods,  drinks, packaging, and the all pervasive christmas music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the most part and for the majority of Americans this seasonal transformation is a welcome tradition that ties them to fond memories and helps them bond with their families and communities. As they shop for presents and talk of playing Santa they share commonalities with coworkers and friends. Tradition and ritual are powerful things, they enhance memory recall and emotional connection by reinforcing the sensory patterns that link us our memories to the present. Rituals that incorporate all  of the senses and include community elements are especially powerful. Anyone who has experienced a Catholic mass with incense, candles, the liturgy and the eucharist can speak to this. But the same things that can connect people to feelings of community, memories of joy and a sense of awe can act as direct sensory triggers for trauma.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is easy to get carried away at Christmas and the feeling of sharing convivial seasonal joy can be intoxicating. This also creates tremendous pressure to conform to the expectations of shared  rituals even if you have legitimate reasons to abstain from celebrations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever called a person a Scrooge, a Grinch or a humbug? Chances are you have. Usually it is intended as a gentle form of peer pressuring, because one of the joys of the Christmas is supposed to be bringing cheer - even to the reluctant or grouchy. In my younger days I joined in on the chiding some of the, so called, Scrooges in my life, for ruining the fun. More recently I have had these very epitaphs lobbed at me.  Like a new tradition,  since I acquired PTSD within the tableau of the Christmas celebration, my reticence toward Christmas celebrations has made me into the office Scrooge.
PTSD triggers can be a tricky thing. Sufferers can learn to manage their responses to distressing stimuli but doing so takes energy.  For people like me, who have experienced tragedy at Christmas, the reminders of the worst day of our lives are everywhere we look, hear and smell and they are nonstop for a solid six weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have never heard of anyone telling a war veteran to “get over it” if he finds fireworks unnerving but I do know mother who lost her child at Christmas and saw his lifeless two and a half year old body laid out in the same room as a splendidly decorated douglas fir, be told to, “Get over it,” when she didn’t want a Christmas tree set up in her living room. Even people who know about this mother’s loss show an easy and course callousness toward the ways the seasonal celebration affects her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Character of Ebenezer Scrooge, like so many literary figures that have been commercialized has been over-simplified by popular depictions. He has become a symbol of greed and social apathy.  A Christmas Carol is a story of spiritual journey and personal redemption. But is is most frequently referenced in order to  insult, people who are likely depressed, isolated or traumatized. In truth, Scrooge was an emotionally neglected child and a scarred individual. His Journey through the past, present and the future helps him see the story of his life through the experiences and feelings of others. The message of Dickens’s tale was not that we should shame people who are different into conformity, for the sake of our own joy and entertainment, it was that if given space and shown patience and compassion, anyone can live a life of charity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Christmas I am asking for one thing. This Christmas I wish for an end to Scrooge Shaming. Please try extending understanding to the so called Scrooges among us. Their negative reaction to Christmas overload is more likely a response to pain than an attempt to spoil your fun. There is nothing joyful or festive about shaming people for experiencing negative feelings. The tradition of holiday name calling and peer pressuring is one we can all do without.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catalogue of Privledge</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/20/catalogue-of-privledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/20/catalogue-of-privledge/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;catalogue-of-privilege&#34;&gt;Catalogue of Privilege&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stumpers:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you mind if I call you Stumpers? It feels more personal than Dear Reader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the principles I have committed myself in this endeavor is include “privilege awareness”. I operate on the theory that the first step to creating a more equitable and just society is to acknowledge inequality. For those of us that benefit in some way from inequality we need to be able to name those benefits, we must be aware of our privilege. In an attempt enhance my own privilege awareness I worked on creating a Catalog of Privilege.  I am sharing it with my readers in interest of transparency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I Actually spent more time developing this than any of my other posts. I’ve been working on it for close to 8 weeks. The primary reason it took me so long is I tried to create a two column feature with privileges in one column and disadvantages in another. And then I realized what I really need for this post is the privileges. The disadvantages were unnecessary. My disadvantages are going to come out in my writing. They are the part of my story I don’t have to remind myself about because they create challenges in my life every day.  The very nature of privilege is that it doesn’t demand our attention in order for us to succeed.  Millions of people are walking around every day completely oblivious to it and while it might be holding them back from some spiritual, intellectual and relationship growth it generally doesn’t hold people back in any material form.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I plan to update this list as my consciousness expands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table style=&#34;border: 1px solid black; border-collapse: collapse&#34;&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;h2&gt;Privilege Catalog:&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;White&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            This is the Big Grand-daddy of all privileges. I carry all of the markers of Whiteness: White parents, white siblings, pale skin, a first and last name with English origins, the whole thing. This impacts my life and the way people treat me in ways that I can only view by contrasting my experience with those of people who do not receive this treatment, which is frustrating because I can’t even look at it without being ethnocentric.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Straight (ish)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            I put this down in the privilege column with a few caveats.Not all of my sexual relationships have been heterosexual. I’m in a long term heterosexual relationship, so for most social purposes I carry straight privilege. Personally I see this most in the stories society tells me about the relationships I am in and how desirable they are. The relationships that feel most natural for me personally are reflected everywhere in our culture.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cis Gender&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            With the exception of a period of my life that I will call my awkward phase, during which I was frequently mistaken for a boy and harangued for my lack of appropriate girlish femininity, I have always fit squarely and comfortably into the gender I was assigned at birth. I have all kinds of qualms with the ways we enforce gender but here I am, quite assuredly a woman.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;American&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            I was born ensconced incomparable physical security of the 20th century American Military Industrial Complex. Wherever I go the power of my nation of origin and its economic and military might has an influence on my personal safety and esteem.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Temporarily Able Bodied&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            I enjoy the luxury of experiencing an urban and consumer landscape that is engineered almost exclusively for bodies that are sized and function like mine.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Average-ish body size&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            While almost all women experience fat shaming because that’s just how messed up our society is, I wear a size L in most stores and that regular everyday dress size exempts me from the bullying, and marginalization people with larger bodies experience.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
        &lt;td&gt;
            &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Conventionally Attractive&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            I don’t want to talk about this there is no way to talk about it without “humble bragging” and no one likes humble braggers. It’s a thing and it has been shown to make the world more well disposed toward me than it otherwise could be.
        &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;        
                                                            
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to Cook this Thanksgiving</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/15/what-to-cook-this-thanksgiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 14:27:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/15/what-to-cook-this-thanksgiving/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;what-to-cook-this-thanksgiving&#34;&gt;What to Cook this Thanksgiving&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is Thanksgiving the only day of the year that you get serious about cooking?  If you’re like most Americans it probably is. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/personalfinance/2017/09/27/90-americans-dont-like-cook-and-its-costing-them-thousands-each-year/708033001/&#34;&gt;Recent surveys&lt;/a&gt; and market trends like meal kits and steady restaurant growth as well as the ever popularity of processed and frozen foods indicate that most Americans don’t cook.  Cooking,like so many other activities in America has become a commodified spectector’s sport. While less than 15% of us enjoy cooking, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.marketingcharts.com/television-13719&#34;&gt;80% of us enjoy&lt;/a&gt; watching cooking shows. Thanksgiving, however centers around a traditional old fashioned home-cooked meal. Our popular images of this Holiday include friends and family gathered around a copious meal produced with loving care. For one day a year millions of would be home cooks roll up their sleeves, open up cookbooks, consult packaging instructions, and even more likely cooking blogs, and get to work. And the results? They are mostly pathetic.  Millions of Turkeys are lead to the slaughter for the Holiday and most of them turn out dry, over oiled, under flavored or fall victim to countless other faux pas.  To eat these birds family members drown the meat in overcooked gravy.  Hundreds of thousands of us pretend to enjoy dishes so dreadful they only get made once a year.  Meanwhile millions of pounds of food waste are produced because too many people are trying to get in on the cooking action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take, for instance, my sister’s green-bean casserole. This dish is is a travesty, a mushy, salty travesty composed of canned products dumped into a casserole dish and baked until warm. If you are like my sister - if you you can’t tell the difference between mincing and chopping, if you don’t know your chef’s knife from your paring knife and and you’re hoping to find recipe’s and tips in blogs, please stop now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’re doing the culinary equivalent of attempting to run a half marathon when you’ve never run further than a mile in your life. You are not ready for this. Meanwhile there are a few Americans, the few, the proud the 15% that enjoy cooking and cook most nights of the week, we have been training for this day all year. Your cooking compatriots have been boiling, roasting, chopping, slicing braising, and chilling call year long. Fifteen percent is a small minority but still a significant one. Chances are you know and love one of these people. If you want my advice, you should call this person-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom who Makes phone calls?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Right then text this person  and ask them what they want to do for the holiday, ask for instructions on how you can help and make sure to get yourself invited. Humble yourself before their experience and preparation, as the novice you are, before the master. If you are told just to bring wine, pick up a good bottle of Bordeaux.  Arrive on time, not early and not late because your gracious cook has been prepping for a while and is relying on years of experience to time every dish just right. And when it’s all said and done when the once majestic indigenous American bird is naught but a stripped carcass, as uncles are dozing on couches while aunts look at holiday circulars and children turn on early holiday specials, do the damn dishes and help box the leftovers! Not everyone can be lucky enough to know a home cook that is up to the task.  On the day of Giving Thanks you should lean into gratitude and recognize the home cooks in your life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But stumped Mom I want to radiate in the joy of knowing I fed my family!  I want to take the credit for making the blessed thanksgiving event a success!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If that’s what you want if and if you are really sincere about it. Start reading my Sunday Cooking section (starting this next Sunday) and get ready to train hard for Thanksgiving 2019 because all things worth doing are worth doing right and it’s going to take at least a year of applied training to get you ready.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down with the PTA!</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/13/down-with-the-pta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 10:33:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/13/down-with-the-pta/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;down-with-the-pta&#34;&gt;Down with the PTA!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No bourgeoisie institution makes me want to lock arms with my proletariat brethren and forcibly seize the means of production from the soft, plump hands of our capitalist overlords quite like the Parent Teacher Association otherwise known as PTAs or PTOs .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their reasons for existing and means of sustaining themselves are entirely dependent of systems and structures that perpetuate inequality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are you talking about Stumped Mom? The PTA strengthens our communities and schools by promoting parental involvement at our schools and brings much needed resources and interest on to our campuses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumpers I can’t blame you for taking this perspective, because this is entirely what society wants you to think and I’m pretty sure it’s what makes those self righteous PTA board members look down their noses at us barely making it schleppers. Mom’s like me who are lucky if they get their kids to before-school care with clean faces each morning, let alone make it aross town after work to make the monthly PTA by 5:30 p.m. on a Wednesday are the famous objects of PTA mom disdain. I will confess, my own personal laziness makes me resent their industriousness. However, there is more to my beef with the PTA than simple personal envy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But stumped Mom, our schools are chronically underfunded, there is insecurity in staffing, and the teachers are underpaid and parental involvement at school helps kids to succeed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do not contest those points but let us and take a more critical eye and ask some crucial questions. When we do we find the classist, racist patriarchal and capitalist structures that buttress these groups are easily laid bare&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What makes for a good PTA?&lt;br /&gt;
Parents with organizational skills and spare time
A Community with Resources and Capital
Relationships and Connections between those parents and the people with the Capital&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of these critical components more abundant in more affluent communities, which thanks to the well documented racial income gap in this country, are overwhelmingly white. PTA participation is also a ladies game, with Mom’s far outnumbering Dad’s in participation. So the pressure to join and support the PTA weights heavily on women adding to their emotional labor burden and straining marriages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t just take my word for it. Reports show that PTA fundraising contributes to the achievement gap, that has been well documented, between white and affluent neighborhoods and communities with less resources.  And even in diverse or well integrated schools white parents hold a disproportionate influence over decision making.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cross sections factors that make for successful PTA’s allow affluent mostly-white, people to perpetuate the privilege of their children over that of others. And most of this happens on the barely recognized volunteer efforts of women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your a parent with a kid in school you likely understand the pressure to join the PTA.  I get invitations in the school newsletter every week. Parents pressure each other into pouring time, money and energy into stop gap measures meant to fill in the holes created by and tragically unequal public education system. Many of us visit our schools and see run down facilities, stressed staff, and outdated materials. We want to do whatever we can to help our children. But shouldn’t we be talking about campaigning against the policies that undermine funding and support for public education?  Nobody talks about this at back to school night or in the school newsletter. Instead we are treated to constant plugs for more PTA volunteers and lend special thank you’s to those lovely PTA Mom’s (sorry Dads the stats show this is a ladies game).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a more just society we would stop valorizing the systemic hoarding of privilege through support of Parent Teacher Associations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But those PTA invitations won’t stop. So what’s a woke parent to do? The next time a PTA pusher approaches me on the school yard. Here is what I’m saying:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No thanks I’m going to invest what little spare time I have in direct involvement in the classroom and any spare resources I have will be dedicated to campaigns for just and equal schools,”  but I’m also gonna wait till my daughter is ready to start our daily foot-race home before I shout “DOWN WITH THE PTA” as I flee the scene. For PTA Moms are brutal are as brutal as they are industrious and I’m not hanging around for a beating.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No duh</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/01/no-duh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 19:56:48 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/01/no-duh/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A word of caution: The following post has heavy feels and addresses sexual trauma.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;noduh&#34;&gt;#NoDuh&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was eleven the first time a friend confided in me that she had been sexually abused.
I was fourteen the next time. When a friend told me that a neighbor had molested her and another girl on her street. I was sixteen when an adult, female, relative told me her abuse story.
I was 18 the first time a male told me his story….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pattern continues like a thread through my life. The confidences weaving in during late night talks in bedrooms, in basements, on rooftops - with hushed tones, clasped hands and numbed, griefed expressions. As a girl and later a woman, no-one taught me how to receive these stories, what to do with them or how to contain them but as they came it was clear to me that they must be contained. Like monthly cycles, and family christmas card lists this was something for women and girls to manage; quietly, discreetly and independently. My whole life prepared me for it. The tiny details of my socialization as a girl taught me to listen, to feel and not to act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2017 when #metoo splashed on to the scene my initial reaction was “#noduh” or “#abouttime”. How could this possibly be a surprise to anyone? But as things moved forward I realized no one was really shocked by the stories or the prevalence. The shock was the act. The act of women speaking publicly and people paying attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new refrain of the #metoo backlash is a so called “rejection of victimhood”. A slight few conservative women had come out to say it that they two have been abused but that it doesn’t matter it hasn’t affected them, “Let’s all move on” They say “Let’s talk about something else.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The weekend of October 5th I was seething with anger. There was a walkout to protest the pending Kavanaugh confirmation in my city but I knew participation would get me disciplined at work. I can’t risk the income stream that feeds my child. When the confirmation was completed.I wanted to do more than just walk out. I wanted to wreck things. I wanted to burn it down. I wanted to go through the richest, whitest neighborhood in town and rip the male symbols off of old volvos. I wanted to smash the windows out of a hooters and drag frat boys from their beer splattered dens into the streets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had my daughter by myself all weekend, she is six.  We, ran errands, got out the halloween decorations, painted mini pumpkins, and cooked together. I took some great photos to send to her great grandparents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I got to work on Monday the 8th. I wanted, so badly, speak my anger to my co-workers. I talked about the pumpkin painting.  Unless you were working in media or workplace diversity or education no one was talking about it.  When I see other parents, we don’t talk about it. Sometimes at the dojo we make sad jokes about it. But even there we dampen our anger.  We chuckle it off as just another postmodern absurdity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our late night whisperings have a new sphere now. Don’t talk about it with your neighbors or co-workers. We should take it to twitter where can feel like we are telling the world but people can filter it out of their feeds. Block it. Silence it. Stick it back into those virtual version of bedrooms, rooftops and basements so women can get back to carrying it without showing it so as not to upset the men around us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a mother of a daughter I am constantly vigilant against signs of a threat that could come from anywhere. I want her to be able to declare her boundaries, to defend them if necessary and to tell if someone crosses them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other day my daughter presented with a rash on her vulva and labia. I asked her gently, “Have you been rubbing your vulva a-lot?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No” She said casually&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I squeezed out a dollop of cream onto her finger for her, I followed up in the most casual and clinical tone I could manage “Has anyone else been touching your vulva?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No” she replied,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A wave of qualified relief washed over me. As far as I can tell she’s been kept safe thus far from the most frightening forms abuse or exploitation. But we live in a world where the Kavanaughs win and even young girls have their secrets. And what of the faithful night when she is initiated into the real covenant of womanhood? When she becomes the first keeper of someone’s horrifying story? How am I preparing her for that? I haven’t seen it in the parenting guides, her pediatrician hasn’t mentioned it. Will there be hashtag for it?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How did we get here?</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/10/25/how-did-we-get-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/10/25/how-did-we-get-here/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;dear-reader&#34;&gt;Dear reader:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All endeavors must have a beginning and this endeavor will begin with an attempt to answer a question. How did we get here? We; being you the reader me the writer. Here being the virtual space that manifests itself in this blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let us start with me. I am here because I became convinced of the narcissistic conceit that the vast and overcrowded world of mommy blogs, feminist writings, parenting advice and armchair political philosophy could possibly benefit from a space dedicated to my idiosyncratic musings. While I am not specifically trained as a writer, I have always carried a certain vanity concerning my language skills and I have been nudged along by a few people in my life with increasing urgency to channel myself into writing. So reader it appears I am able to write, I am driven to write, I can write and I am going to write.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My life is quite full and I have no shortage of responsibilities. I have a child, a full time office type job, a dog, a cat, a three bedroom home to maintain, an uncooperative co-parent, a hungry and distracting boyfriend to feed and enjoy, and a fairly demanding recreational fitness hobby. A blog is like a whole other THING to take on. If I must write could I not collect it all in a private journal and keep it to myself?  I have attempted this but I have never been able to sustain it past thinking about how great it would be to set aside journaling time each day. Journaling is like a romantic fantasy that clearly belongs to some other class of much cooler, authentic and self assured sort of person. I can’t motivate myself to do it. It seems I require the focus of a potential audience. I would be content to stuff messages into a bottle and toss them into the ocean. That distribution method is probably just as likely to reach as many people another mommy blog.  But I do not want to add any more than I already have to the Pacific Garbage Patch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright let’s get to you, because we all want to hear about ourselves. Who are you? Most likely you’re someone very close to me because this is the first post on a new blog and I haven’t even figured out how to get readers, so my first audience will most likely be a tight and trusted circle. If you are someone very close to me I ask that you take my sharing this place with you as an evidence of trust. My goal for this space is for it to be a capital R-E-A-L real. I want to be as transparent as I can be about opinions, perspectives and experiences. But I also have people in my life who depend on me who I would like to protect. Privacy doesn’t really exist in  the internet world. So if you do know me or you read this and you are able to cross reference enough about my geographic location and life particulars to triangulate who I am then you know me well enough to picture the face of my beautiful innocent child. That face that will not be appear on this blog. If you need help calling that face to mind; find me on FB. I trust you to protect her by keeping quiet about who I am because the internet can be a cruel place and there is no telling what will set people off against a writer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a little bit of luck, persistence and pluck, you could be another sort of reader.  We shall call you Not too Distant Future Reader (NTDFR).  If your a NTDFR I am guessing you became engaged through social media promotion or maybe viral sharing of my work.  You read through my more recent and more mature posts and now you’re working your way through my back catalogue. I can’t say much about you NTDFR, but I can say that your haircut is way better than it was when I wrote this. Just take a look at that selfie you took back in the fall of 2018 what were you thinking?  Perhaps we share some things in common. Maybe you’re a recently divorced parent looking for perspectives on making it work that challenge the old “single mom” paradigm?  Maybe you ask yourself, “am I the only who feels like this is not okay?” just about everywhere you go. You’re also way more patient and smart than the internet marketing firm surveys say you are because here you are reading all the way down into word 740, or so, of this post and it doesn’t even have a slideshow.  And they all said smartphones were killing our attention spans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We covered me and we’ve talked about you, so what of here? Here is a place for exploring ideas about 21st century parenthood, through the perspective of a flawed, divorced, full-time working mom, living in a rapidly changing west coast american city, without any “my kids are my life” or “#blessed” bullshit. I plan to be frank about things that can get prickly, issues like race, sex, dating, class and money.  I hope you’ll to laugh at my failures and maybe celebrate some triumphs with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yours Truly,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/contact/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact-stumped-mom&#34;&gt;Contact Stumped Mom&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;form method=&#34;POST&#34; action=&#34;https://formspree.io/StumpedMomblog@gmail.com&#34;&gt;
  &lt;b&gt;Email:   &lt;/b&gt;&lt;input type=&#34;email&#34; name=&#34;email&#34; placeholder=&#34;Your email&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  &lt;b&gt;Subject: &lt;/b&gt; 
  &lt;input type= &#34;radio&#34; name=&#34;subject&#34; value=&#34;questions&#34;&gt; Questions
  &lt;input type= &#34;radio&#34; name=&#34;subject&#34; value=&#34;threats&#34;&gt; Threats&lt;br&gt;

  &lt;textarea name=&#34;message&#34; placeholder=&#34;Enter Message&#34; style=&#34;height: 150px; width: 500px&#34;&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  &lt;button type=&#34;submit&#34;&gt;Send&lt;/button&gt;
  
&lt;/form&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>