<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/about_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/about_me/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About me:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a fiction - an artistic alter ego created to emphasize key traits of my creator’s personal identity, hile intentionally masking others. All biographies and human self presentations include exaggeration as well as obfuscation for it is only in fiction that we dispense with the pretense of factual authenticity, and free ourselves to explore larger truths. That being said, I identify as a slutty, white, divorced mother of one in the year 2018. I live in a West Coast American city, there is no hiding that. I am college educated and I own a modest home in an, “up and coming neighborhood” (The whole foods 8 blocks up just opened 2 years ago). I have a job that pays me just enough to be able to afford the mortgage on that home and do enough repairs to keep it from falling down. So I guess that makes me part of the “coastal elite.” My favorite Muppet is Gonzo. I am a weirdo, who has learned to assimilate with everyday life but every, single day I see elephants in rooms and I want to talk about them. This room is parenting and mothering in contemporary America and I want to talk about pesky pachyderms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In the words of the great Rowdie Roddie Piper, “I am here to kickass and chew bubblegum and I am all out of bubblegum!” - Stumped Mom is here to slay!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No duh</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/01/no-duh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 19:56:48 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/11/01/no-duh/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A word of caution: The following post has heavy feels and addresses sexual trauma.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;noduh&#34;&gt;#NoDuh&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was eleven the first time a friend confided in me that she had been sexually abused.
I was fourteen the next time. When a friend told me that a neighbor had molested her and another girl on her street. I was sixteen when an adult, female, relative told me her abuse story.
I was 18 the first time a male told me his story….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pattern continues like a thread through my life. The confidences weaving in during late night talks in bedrooms, in basements, on rooftops - with hushed tones, clasped hands and numbed, griefed expressions. As a girl and later a woman, no-one taught me how to receive these stories, what to do with them or how to contain them but as they came it was clear to me that they must be contained. Like monthly cycles, and family christmas card lists this was something for women and girls to manage; quietly, discreetly and independently. My whole life prepared me for it. The tiny details of my socialization as a girl taught me to listen, to feel and not to act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2017 when #metoo splashed on to the scene my initial reaction was “#noduh” or “#abouttime”. How could this possibly be a surprise to anyone? But as things moved forward I realized no one was really shocked by the stories or the prevalence. The shock was the act. The act of women speaking publicly and people paying attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new refrain of the #metoo backlash is a so called “rejection of victimhood”. A slight few conservative women had come out to say it that they two have been abused but that it doesn’t matter it hasn’t affected them, “Let’s all move on” They say “Let’s talk about something else.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The weekend of October 5th I was seething with anger. There was a walkout to protest the pending Kavanaugh confirmation in my city but I knew participation would get me disciplined at work. I can’t risk the income stream that feeds my child. When the confirmation was completed.I wanted to do more than just walk out. I wanted to wreck things. I wanted to burn it down. I wanted to go through the richest, whitest neighborhood in town and rip the male symbols off of old volvos. I wanted to smash the windows out of a hooters and drag frat boys from their beer splattered dens into the streets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had my daughter by myself all weekend, she is six.  We, ran errands, got out the halloween decorations, painted mini pumpkins, and cooked together. I took some great photos to send to her great grandparents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I got to work on Monday the 8th. I wanted, so badly, speak my anger to my co-workers. I talked about the pumpkin painting.  Unless you were working in media or workplace diversity or education no one was talking about it.  When I see other parents, we don’t talk about it. Sometimes at the dojo we make sad jokes about it. But even there we dampen our anger.  We chuckle it off as just another postmodern absurdity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our late night whisperings have a new sphere now. Don’t talk about it with your neighbors or co-workers. We should take it to twitter where can feel like we are telling the world but people can filter it out of their feeds. Block it. Silence it. Stick it back into those virtual version of bedrooms, rooftops and basements so women can get back to carrying it without showing it so as not to upset the men around us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a mother of a daughter I am constantly vigilant against signs of a threat that could come from anywhere. I want her to be able to declare her boundaries, to defend them if necessary and to tell if someone crosses them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other day my daughter presented with a rash on her vulva and labia. I asked her gently, “Have you been rubbing your vulva a-lot?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No” She said casually&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I squeezed out a dollop of cream onto her finger for her, I followed up in the most casual and clinical tone I could manage “Has anyone else been touching your vulva?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No” she replied,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A wave of qualified relief washed over me. As far as I can tell she’s been kept safe thus far from the most frightening forms abuse or exploitation. But we live in a world where the Kavanaughs win and even young girls have their secrets. And what of the faithful night when she is initiated into the real covenant of womanhood? When she becomes the first keeper of someone’s horrifying story? How am I preparing her for that? I haven’t seen it in the parenting guides, her pediatrician hasn’t mentioned it. Will there be hashtag for it?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How did we get here?</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/10/25/how-did-we-get-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/10/25/how-did-we-get-here/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;dear-reader&#34;&gt;Dear reader:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All endeavors must have a beginning and this endeavor will begin with an attempt to answer a question. How did we get here? We; being you the reader me the writer. Here being the virtual space that manifests itself in this blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let us start with me. I am here because I became convinced of the narcissistic conceit that the vast and overcrowded world of mommy blogs, feminist writings, parenting advice and armchair political philosophy could possibly benefit from a space dedicated to my idiosyncratic musings. While I am not specifically trained as a writer, I have always carried a certain vanity concerning my language skills and I have been nudged along by a few people in my life with increasing urgency to channel myself into writing. So reader it appears I am able to write, I am driven to write, I can write and I am going to write.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My life is quite full and I have no shortage of responsibilities. I have a child, a full time office type job, a dog, a cat, a three bedroom home to maintain, an uncooperative co-parent, a hungry and distracting boyfriend to feed and enjoy, and a fairly demanding recreational fitness hobby. A blog is like a whole other THING to take on. If I must write could I not collect it all in a private journal and keep it to myself?  I have attempted this but I have never been able to sustain it past thinking about how great it would be to set aside journaling time each day. Journaling is like a romantic fantasy that clearly belongs to some other class of much cooler, authentic and self assured sort of person. I can’t motivate myself to do it. It seems I require the focus of a potential audience. I would be content to stuff messages into a bottle and toss them into the ocean. That distribution method is probably just as likely to reach as many people another mommy blog.  But I do not want to add any more than I already have to the Pacific Garbage Patch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright let’s get to you, because we all want to hear about ourselves. Who are you? Most likely you’re someone very close to me because this is the first post on a new blog and I haven’t even figured out how to get readers, so my first audience will most likely be a tight and trusted circle. If you are someone very close to me I ask that you take my sharing this place with you as an evidence of trust. My goal for this space is for it to be a capital R-E-A-L real. I want to be as transparent as I can be about opinions, perspectives and experiences. But I also have people in my life who depend on me who I would like to protect. Privacy doesn’t really exist in  the internet world. So if you do know me or you read this and you are able to cross reference enough about my geographic location and life particulars to triangulate who I am then you know me well enough to picture the face of my beautiful innocent child. That face that will not be appear on this blog. If you need help calling that face to mind; find me on FB. I trust you to protect her by keeping quiet about who I am because the internet can be a cruel place and there is no telling what will set people off against a writer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a little bit of luck, persistence and pluck, you could be another sort of reader.  We shall call you Not too Distant Future Reader (NTDFR).  If your a NTDFR I am guessing you became engaged through social media promotion or maybe viral sharing of my work.  You read through my more recent and more mature posts and now you’re working your way through my back catalogue. I can’t say much about you NTDFR, but I can say that your haircut is way better than it was when I wrote this. Just take a look at that selfie you took back in the fall of 2018 what were you thinking?  Perhaps we share some things in common. Maybe you’re a recently divorced parent looking for perspectives on making it work that challenge the old “single mom” paradigm?  Maybe you ask yourself, “am I the only who feels like this is not okay?” just about everywhere you go. You’re also way more patient and smart than the internet marketing firm surveys say you are because here you are reading all the way down into word 740, or so, of this post and it doesn’t even have a slideshow.  And they all said smartphones were killing our attention spans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We covered me and we’ve talked about you, so what of here? Here is a place for exploring ideas about 21st century parenthood, through the perspective of a flawed, divorced, full-time working mom, living in a rapidly changing west coast american city, without any “my kids are my life” or “#blessed” bullshit. I plan to be frank about things that can get prickly, issues like race, sex, dating, class and money.  I hope you’ll to laugh at my failures and maybe celebrate some triumphs with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yours Truly,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/contact/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact-stumped-mom&#34;&gt;Contact Stumped Mom&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;form method=&#34;POST&#34; action=&#34;https://formspree.io/StumpedMomblog@gmail.com&#34;&gt;
  &lt;b&gt;Email:   &lt;/b&gt;&lt;input type=&#34;email&#34; name=&#34;email&#34; placeholder=&#34;Your email&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  &lt;b&gt;Subject: &lt;/b&gt; 
  &lt;input type= &#34;radio&#34; name=&#34;subject&#34; value=&#34;questions&#34;&gt; Questions
  &lt;input type= &#34;radio&#34; name=&#34;subject&#34; value=&#34;threats&#34;&gt; Threats&lt;br&gt;

  &lt;textarea name=&#34;message&#34; placeholder=&#34;Enter Message&#34; style=&#34;height: 150px; width: 500px&#34;&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  &lt;button type=&#34;submit&#34;&gt;Send&lt;/button&gt;
  
&lt;/form&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>