<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stumped Mom</title>
    <link>https://StumpedMom.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Stumped Mom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Stumped Mom</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://StumpedMom.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/about_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 12:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/about_me/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About me:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a fiction - an artistic alter ego created to emphasize key traits of my creator’s personal identity, hile intentionally masking others. All biographies and human self presentations include exaggeration as well as obfuscation for it is only in fiction that we dispense with the pretense of factual authenticity, and free ourselves to explore larger truths. That being said, I identify as a slutty, white, divorced mother of one in the year 2018. I live in a West Coast American city, there is no hiding that. I am college educated and I own a modest home in an, “up and coming neighborhood” (The whole foods 8 blocks up just opened 2 years ago). I have a job that pays me just enough to be able to afford the mortgage on that home and do enough repairs to keep it from falling down. So I guess that makes me part of the “coastal elite.” My favorite Muppet is Gonzo. I am a weirdo, who has learned to assimilate with everyday life but every, single day I see elephants in rooms and I want to talk about them. This room is parenting and mothering in contemporary America and I want to talk about pesky pachyderms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In the words of the great Rowdie Roddie Piper, “I am here to kickass and chew bubblegum and I am all out of bubblegum!” - Stumped Mom is here to slay!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Defense Of Guys</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/23/in-defense-of-guys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 11:21:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/23/in-defense-of-guys/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;in-defense-of-guys&#34;&gt;In Defense of “Guys”&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come along with me stumpers, as I take a nerdy deep dive into the intersection of regional identity, feminism and language.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First off I am going to reveal one of my thinly veiled secrets. I am from the Pacific Northwest (PNW). My whole family is from the Pacific Northwest. My family roots in the PNW go back four generations. If you look at the population trends for the Northwestern States, the growth, powered by transplants from other states has been explosive over the course of my lifetime. Just by the numbers, lifetime natives to my community are a minority in-spite of a relatively low birth rates; the population has tripled in the last 30 years. We locals are so outnumbered we are like unicorns here and just knowing one of us gives other people access to bragging rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Believe it or not, those few of us who have lived here our whole lives have a &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pacific_Northwest_English&#34;&gt;distinct dialect&lt;/a&gt;. one that the media doesn’t bother portraying.  Jack Nicholson did not bother to learn it for &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pc0_Xnvl3t4&#34;&gt;One Flew Over The Cuckoo&amp;rsquo;s Nest&lt;/a&gt;, an A story, written, set and filmed in Oregon. Can you imagine Goodwill hunting if everyone had Southern accents? I suspect the people of boston would have nothing to do with them apples. But Jack’s portrayal of an Oregonian with a New Jersey accent is somehow film history legend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Pacific Northwestern erasure impacts perceptions all over the country. My first time venturing into the South, I was told I sounded Canadian. Gross!  Being from the PNW, I know plenty of Canadians and this confluence is offensive to all parties involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here in the Northwest, we do have one cinematic dialect-hero and he’s no Jack Nicholson. We have to go outside the arthouse and que up a copy of Goonies to hear John Matuszak
as Sloth famously deliver our native battle cry,. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4Vv5CsP1pAg&#34;&gt;“HEY YOU GUYS!!”&lt;/a&gt; in a wisconsin accent that is just obscured enough to pass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which brings us to my particular bone to pick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certain feminists hailing from parts east of the Mississippi have started to spread the notion that the use of the word “guys” when addressing mixed gendered company is sexist. Like in this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.vox.com/2015/6/11/8761227/you-guys-sexism-language&#34;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; written by Washington D.C. based Vox media in which a feminist expert, from New York,is consulted to tell us why “guys” is sexist. She argues pretty effectively that by applying the male perspective to mixed gendered groups we re-enforce the patriarchal assumption that male equals normal. We are encouraged to use this list of alternatives instead:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Folks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everyone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colleagues&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gang&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Y&amp;rsquo;all&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guys and girls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As socially forward as these feminists are trying to be I am afraid I must report that they have an awful lot in common with gender rigid social regressives. The first people, I encountered who ever objected my use my use of guys were southern women.Way back in 2002 I was shocked and mortified to be chided by my sister’s in law for saying “hey guys!” when they were in the room. The were Southern ladies afterall, not guys! How dare I imply that there were of another gender. These same women raised a fuss when I didn’t take my husband’s name. I could not wrap my name around their perspective. I did not mean guys as in male people. I began to realize that in the Pacific Northwest the use is so pervasive and common we really do not perceive it as being gendered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning I walked into my office and greeted the two women in the room with a  “Good morning guys”.One being a Native Oregonian Unicorn and the other a 40 year PNW  resident, they replied with a “Hey!” and all was right in the beautiful PNW.” Guys” has, for all intents and purposes, lost its gendered meaning in my region. You can convene a troupe meeting of all female girl scouts in the PNW with a, “Listen up you guys,” and each and every one of those little girls is going pipe down and put her eyes forward. (That’s another one how many of you guys say “pipe, down eyes forward?”)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another distinguishing characteristic of PNW natives is a particular form of niceness. We puzzle visitors from the East Coast, with our affable attitudes. However, we aren’t actually as nice as our reputation would suggest. We tend to be super subtle and passive aggressive and East Coast, and even Southern California natives don’t realize that they are missing, social cues which are meant to inform them when they are out of line. A typical Northwesterner will let you run around making an ass of yourself, for years, before directly saying anything to you about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Years have gone by and with the exception of a quirky satirical sketch comedy series on a cable network, in which two part-time Portlanders portray a version of our local culture, that is largely the product of the population explosion over the last 20 years; the rest of the country doesn’t seem to notice that we exist with our own regional identity. Some of these non-Northwesterners are labeling key features of our regional dialect as patently sexist without bother to consult with people from the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I’m going to say it. You guys are being real jerks! You have no right to tell us to surrender or change the use of a key part of speech that is distinctive to our region.
Language does matter, but one of the things that makes it matter, is how its meaning is social and regional context. Just as a “fag” isn’t a homesexual slur if you are an English person looking for a smoke. Guys are not a group of men if the speaker is a person from the Pacific Northwest is speaking in the second person plural.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m still down with feminism and I’m going to do plenty of other feminist stuff like: write about sex from a woman’s perspective, promote gender and queer equity, speak out about the prevalence of sexual assault, stand up for reproductive access, and refuse to accept heterosexual relationships with an unequal division of emotional labor, as inevitable. But I am not giving up a part of my speech that is one of the remaining remnants of a local identity. You won’t be able to pry “guys” out of my cold dead lips, but it will live past me in my writing and on in my child and you can’t stop it!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valentines Day For Dummies</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/11/valentines-day-for-dummies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 10:48:02 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/11/valentines-day-for-dummies/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;valentines-day-for-dummies&#34;&gt;Valentines Day For Dummies&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dearest Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I wish one thing for you all this Valentine’s Day it is for you all to achieve sexual satisfaction be it alone, or with a partner. Valentine’s Day is perhaps the most awkward day of the calendar year and the sexual revolution hasn’t done it any favors. Presently, the prevailing winds indicate that it is a day for children to trade heart themed and punny pre-made notes, for teenagers to run around confused and for adults to express their affection through themed gifting or feel lonely if they are single. I can’t help everybody. But I believe as a female who has been in more than one long term relationship with men I can offer some valuable perspective to hetersexual men in relationships with women.
&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/VDay.jpeg&#34; style=&#34;width:310px;height:204px;float:left;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 10px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are single and have your eye on someone. I highly encourage you to use this day as your opportunity to take a big risk and make a grand romantic gesture. For it to work you have to commit all the way and take a big risk. If you aren’t feeling it, use the day on yourself. Disconnect from social media and go buy yourself a new sex toy. Tune the world out and do things you like for yourself. You deserve it. The rest of this post  is aimed toward men in long term relationships because they seem to need the help more than anyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Much ado has been made about so called high maintenance girlfriends and wives what to do for them or about them on Valentine’s Day. A discussion of the sexism of the term “high maintenance” will need to be tabled for another day - my goal now,  as ever, is to get us all laid real good. So for today I am going to put a bandaid over the sexism of the whole setup and focus on how to work within it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why does today’s modern liberated woman still look forward to gifts and expressions of adulation on February 14th? To this question I ask another question: does everybody not remember Christmas? How much of Christmas was powered by the emotional labor, blood sweat and tears of so many women and femmes? Don’t you see that we’re tired? We keep card lists, we wrap gifts, we plan dinners, and trips, we stay up late, we handle mothers-in-laws judgemental passive aggression. If you are in a relationship with a woman and you can’t seem to figure out what her deal is, get wise to &lt;a href=&#34;https://thebodyisnotanapology.com/magazine/50-ways-people-expect-constant-emotional-labor-from-women-and-femmes/&#34;&gt;emotional labor&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Valentine’s Day offers women in heterosexual relationships a day of respite and escape from emotional labor a guaranteed chance at being “treated” to adoration without having to set the whole damn thing up herself. If a special woman in your life seems drained, touched out, stressed, and anxious and she isn’t as sexualy responsive as she once was, take this Valentine’s Day as your wakeup call. It is time to do some emotional homework and lift the burden from your partner. No specific products or purchases are required to implement to do this. But you are going to have to do some planning, and you may have to practice some communication skills that don’t come naturally to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom’s guide to nailing Valentines Day and getting laid real good”:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do some planning. Women do a lot of the planning work in our society whether it’s in your relationship or in her family or at work. Plan something and when I say plan something I don’t mean say, “Hey babe I think we should go out on this date where do you want to go?” You need to identify a time frame, a place and an activity and the food. The only thing you should bother her about is setting aside the time. If she has kids set up child-care. The place can be home, the activity can be netflix and the food can be pizza but do the planning. Make the time the space and the effort for her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Did I mention the space? If your partner is a mother especially take time to get her out of her every day space, or at the very least clean it for her. Even if you feel like the chores in your relationship are divided evenly women experience tremendous social pressure to have a clean home and any time she is in the home cleaning anxiety can derail any chance of romance. If you don’t cohabitate clean up your place and host her, if you do consider getting a hotel room in your own city. Some of the hottest dates I have ever had have been in hotel rooms. Personally I am more likely to experiment with new things when I am not at home. And by experiment I mean, multiple partners, toys, anal, pornography and all those goodies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of your planning process. Talk your partner her about her fantasies and sexual needs. Read up in my &lt;a href=&#34;https://stumpedmom.com/2018/12/11/beginning-fantasy-talk/&#34;&gt;fantasy talk series&lt;/a&gt;  to get some ideas on basics. Try to find out about the various phases of sex and if there is anything she would like more or less of during each of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Surrender all pressure and expectation. Make yourself a zen master of romance by concentrating on gratifying your partner. Practice mindfulness and enjoy every moment of intimacy you have for what it is. If she touches your knee, try not to think about if she is going to move her hand to your groin look at her face and think about how nice her touch feels. Do not think of your dinner conversation as foreplay even if you are flirting. Concentrate on what it is you are enjoying about that moment. Focusing on the end goal will make it harder to achieve&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lay on the admiration. Women are bombarded with messages about their bodies and how they should and shouldn’t be. It is time for you to give her some verbal appreciation. The key to doing this successfully to make it detailed and specific. If this is unnatural for you take some time and think about it and even write it down. What about your partner sets her apart from others? Don’t just say “you have nice hair,” a seven year old could come up with that. Sure you can compliment her hair but be specific, include details about colors, textures, smells. Then add feeling words and action words. What emotions do you experience when you are near her? What are you motivated to do by these emotions?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If things are going well once you have given your lady some admiration you can start with som verbal foreplay. Work from those areas of admiration that you started with and tell her how you would like to touch her or be touched where and why.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Concentrate on some no pressure body care or physical intimacy. You know, shit like: snuggling, back rubs, baths and stuff. If you do decide to get in deep into beauty self care or grooming do some research and make sure you do it right. It will not be a treat for her if she has to talk you through it and teach you how.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rest, my friends, is up to you knowing the basic mechanic and this isn’t exactly that kind of blog. This advise isn’t exclusive for Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day in fact it is best when applied frequently and liberally throughout the calendar year. Love is for every day and I wish you all the best of it for yourselves and the special people in your lives.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s His Story</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/10/whats-his-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 09:36:39 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/10/whats-his-story/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-s-his-story&#34;&gt;What’s His Story?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last night, during his annual address to the United States Congress, in a move aimed at retaining his party’s grip over the religious right, the Kleptocrat who holds executive office of the world’s most powerful oligarchy, took aim at women’s rights. He piously declared the sanctity of all life, even the unborn (though let us not speak of diabetes patients in puerto rico) and attacked laws passed in New York and Virginia aimed aimed at securing access to reproductive care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations Stumped Mom you did it I!  wrote a paragraph about national politics without saying “President” or “Trump!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok stumpers here is the deal. Republicans are out to get women, because stoking our patriarchal culture’s, ancient fear of women and their reproductive power is a proven way to gain the loyalty of the people most deeply invested in that hegemony. This makes it so much easier to keep their voters from noticing that they are supporting tax and regulation policies that don’t benefit their class. It’s the oldest political bait and switch in the book. I expect if you read stumped mom you’re the kind of person that gets this but this piece is a polemic and one of the conventions of the form is to garner the support of your readers for a new argument by laying a foundation of shared context with your audience before introducing novel ideas. So now that we’ve established that people on the right use abortion stigma to heighten fear and hatred of women in order to get what they want and we don’t like that how do combat it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our best bet at killing this political strategy and seeing a more just and equitable world for our children is to take aim at the cultural root of the problem, the vilification of women. It is much harder to villainize people if you have relationships with them. If you hear their stories and see where they are in your everyday lives it is harder to attack their interests. Just as the path toward legal protections for LGBTQ people has been laid with each coming out the struggle for women’s reproductive rights relies on women coming out and declaring their personal connection to reproductive access.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.johnstonsarchive.net/policy/abortion/uslifetimeab.html&#34;&gt;According the the Johnston Archive&lt;/a&gt; “25-28% of women ages 15-64 in the U.S. today have had at least one abortion in their lifetime.” At least one in four women has a story to tell. I’m all about transparency so I will disclose that that access to comprehensive reproductive education and effective long term birth control,as well as luck has so far meant that I have never had an unplanned, or medically complicated or dangerous pregnancy. This is not my story but I do know and love women who have these stories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A very small portion of those women have been brave enough, even with their identities veiled to tell their stories. But the work is being done great journalism like this Article in &lt;a href=&#34;https://slate.com/human-interest/2018/07/the-abortions-we-dont-talk-about-six-slate-women-tell-their-stories.html&#34;&gt;Slate&lt;/a&gt;  These stories when told by real women set fire to the straw woman who is easy to dismiss and hate. They give faces and context and push out the image of the selfish, reckless heartless, narcissistic harlot the religious right wants to restrain, punish and regulate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A funny thing though. It didn’t take long for #notall men and #mentoo to pop up when women started telling their stories of sexual abuse and harassment to try to counter the narrative with a so called men’s perspective on sexual violence, oppression and abuse. But there is a strange silence among men surrounding their relationships with abortion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One in four women in the United States has terminated a pregnancy and they didn’t get their on their own. Where are the men’s voices? A woman’s right to choose is absolutely her own and the story of her choice is hers and no-one else’s to tell. But for every woman that comes forward and tells the story about how an abortion saved, her health, a career, a relationship, her position in her family, hardships on her other children, there is a sperm source that has at the very least been spared two decades of child support. Whenever I see some young male luminary, influencer or disrupter espousing his ideas and trumpeting his success I quietly ask myself could he be one of them? We will not speak of those cretins who have pressured women, or manipulated or abused them into one choice or another they don’t have a place in any conversation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The forced birthers have men on their side who stand up and tell their sob stories of the babies they never got to have because the Jezebel’s who carried them chose to terminate the pregnancy. But there must be millions of men whose educations, careers, relationships, and livelihoods have been preserved by a woman’s choice to have an abortion a choice that they supported. I know this because I know at least three in my own life. One for every woman I know has made the choice and I can see how their lives would be completely different were it not for her access to abortion. These are not men grieving for the child that they never had with that girlfriend or ex wife they now barely know. They are young men moving forward with their lives and careers and forging healthy relationships&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can see why they don’t speak, on one side they don’t want to insert themselves into a discussion of women’s bodies and rights and on the other they do not want to be outed to the people who will judge them as sinners; but right now we are engaging in conversations about reproduction as if it only impacts women. This only reinforces the social assumption that babies are ultimately a woman’s responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I am issue an opportunity and a challenge to you men. The men whose wives have been saved by a medically necessary abortion, or those of you who have kept it a secret. A secret only known to the woman you drove to the clinic. Own it as part of your story. Whether that means telling at least one other person that you trust, writing a check to planned parenthood or outing yourself to your church. Own it. If a woman made the choice to abort a pregnancy you started and you are glad she did, don’t walk around pretending that abortion is none of your business because as long as you have that privilege, a woman’s rights will always be threatened. Your silence and inaction threatens the movement that has enabled your success and unless you are contributing to it. You’re a free rider.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Creeper</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/07/my-first-creeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 19:44:45 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/07/my-first-creeper/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-first-creeper&#34;&gt;My First Creeper&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m about to let you in behind the scenes of StumpedMom.com. While the casual or even careful reader could never be blamed for assuming I pull this entire website out of my ass. I try to organize my ideas and put them out in an organized and orderly fashion. I use an Airtable (Please sponsor me) spreadsheet to organize my work from the idea stage, through to publishing. I should probably be plugging in and tracking metrics but meh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/air_table.jpg&#34; style=&#34;width:310px;height:561px;float:left;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 15px;&#34;&gt;
Sometimes I have more ideas than I can write about, at once and to get myself to focus I put those ideas into a list called “undeveloped”. On days like today, when I feel like writing but I’m not fired up about anything in particular, I linger over this section of the list and see which nuggets I might be able to massage into life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One entry into particular jumped out at me today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“My First Creeper”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I made this entry I was totally anticipating that in the very near future, my presence as a woman on the internet who openly, talks about sex, was going to attract some boundary crossing weirdos. But something strange has happened. StumpedMom.com is now a full four months old. I have done a lot of sticking my neck out and yet no verifiable, off the rails, creepers have surfaced. No one has even used the “threats” form on my contact page to register an official threat. Nobody loves me enough to hate me or hates me enough to love me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what gives? How do I explain this apparent lack of predatory attention. Feedback on my blog does come in at a pretty regular clip. Sometimes I get public shout-outs but most often I get dm’s from men on Twitter. Most of them try to use my blog and my presence online as an excuse to try and get personal information from me or to get me to sext with them. I will grant that my personal threshold for creep may be a little high but so far none of these dudes has gotten out of control. I don’t answer everyone who sends me a message. That has more to do with the timing of a first messages arrival than anything. If you say “hi” at a good time, when I am available I am likely to answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have some experience with weirdos and creepers. Waaaaay back in highschool, before social media was a thing, I pissed of the wrong weirdo and got myself a stalker. I acquired this stalker in ta rather unremarkable teenager fashion, by participating in a group slandering the wrong person at basement gathering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This person reacted by  launching a months long harassment campaign against me and those closest to me. She spammed my email inbox, she scrawled epitaphs on our high school the bathroom walls and phoned in death threats to my family from a pay-phone at all hours of the night for months on end. Sometimes she snail mailed her nasty letters and at one point she even filed a false police report against me, in which she claimed a whole different person’s identity and said I had assaulted her. She was the analog version of of a twitter mob leader. The situation was eventually resolved when her mole and chief accomplice was overcome by a wave of remorse and confessed to the school administrators. The whole debacle taught me a few lessons that I believe have been serving me well as a blogger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, I avoid slandering people as a means of getting attention.You would think this would be a lesson all adults know, but my recent observations of social media show that its a slander machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The measures I have taken to protect my identity (even passing up offers for free stuff) have all been made with this cautionary tale in mind and I started this project prepared to walk away from it at any time. No online argument or internet beef is worth putting my family through the anxiety that my last stalker caused.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I follow my own advice. When I interact with people I make my intentions clear. I tell them that I make myself available to readers for feedback but I am not available for developing any kind of relationship. If they push or make me feel uncomfortable I never escalate, I politely excuse myself, ignore or block and then I move on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am well aware that I have been exercising skills that women are socialized to learn in order to avoid some of the worst outcomes of misogynistic rape culture. These are our ways of getting out without getting hurt. Don’t cause a fuss, don’t trigger his entitlement etc. Victims are never to blame for being attacked but there are ways to minimize risk and sense bad situations and find a way out before you get in too deep.I might be out to change the world, one blog post at a time but I still have to function in it just the same. So far, this little artistic endeavor has bolstered my faith in people. Thank you stumpers for reading me and hearing me and respecting my boundaries. I look forward to continuing to interact with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monday Mom Hacks Infant Stytle</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/04/monday-mom-hacks-infant-stytle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 10:55:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/04/monday-mom-hacks-infant-stytle/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Monday Mom Hacks Infant style:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I am committed to anything here at StumpedMom.com it is learning things the hard way so you don’t have to. If you have young children or are anticipating the arrival of a new baby you’re going to be bombarded with advice. Some of it helpful-some of it pushy and unnecessary.
&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/infants_style.jpeg&#34; style=&#34;width:320px;height:213px;float:left;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 15px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not here to sell you a product, just to entertain you and hopefully make your life a little better. Below are five things for new babies that I discovered on my own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Backup Lovey:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most infants show a  preference for a particular blanket or plush toy early on. Once your child does this, purchase at least one spare so you have a backup. Go to Ebay and pay premium for it if you have to.  I have even had copies made by hand in the case of one homemade blanket.  We ordered backups for my daughters favorite plush toy and favorite blanket before she was six months old and we would regularly rotate them so that we could wash them without disruption. With regular cycling they have equal wear, so she couldn’t tell the difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your child’s favorite comfort items will last longer this way, and stay cleaner and if you play your card right you will never get caught without blankie at bedtime or find yourself going to extremes to recover a lost plush toy. When she was four she discovered our secret stash but she was totally cool with their being copies once we explained that we did it so she would never be without her favorites. When her father and I seperated she took one set to each house. She is seven now and she still treats that favorite plush like its a member of the family, in both of her houses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Lingerie bag:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did I mention that you can totally get away with washing your baby’s smaller plush toys in the washing machine and dryer if you put them in a standard lingerie bag? Go ahead and try it, pop Teddy in the wash with everything else. Careful not to put in the dryer on high heat if it has fake plastic hair. No more smelly stuffed animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Wheelchair&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I discovered this hack while I was looking after a baby, while also making, long and frequent visits to a nursing home. While the baby was fussy during one of the visits, I sat down in a spare wheelchair. I rocked him back and forth using the wheels to glide back and forth and he went to sleep. While the baby was sleeping I was still able to wheel around and do stuff! It was amazing. This became our regular go to thing the residents of the home loved that we came around to visit everyone while we wheeled about. If you can get your hands on an old wheelchair and your house is accessible enough you can be basically an unstoppable baby comforting multi-tasking machine!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diaper Service:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are open to cloth diapering and there is a cloth diaper service in your area.I highly recommend you try it. There are numerous health and environmental benefits to cloth diapering but I know for new mom’s the rubber often meets the road at convenience and affordability. It sounds super bougie and unaffordable but I did the math using spreadsheets before my baby was born and in my area, and for the first six months diaper service was cheaper than using costco brand diapers. The way it works they give you an odor controlling hamper and special bags and once a week they drop off clean cloth diaper liners and pick up the dirty ones from the week before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Benefit of Birthing at home:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did have a home birth but I am not a home birthing advocate. Expectant mothers in the US are bombarded with choices to make regarding their upcoming birth. My advice to you in this arena is to talk with your healthcare providers and do some of your own independent research and don’t let anyone else tell you what to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said, I did a ton of research before I made my choice and there was one fringe benefit to my home birth that nobody told me about - the effect it had on my pets. Giving birth at home removed the whole, introducing the baby to the animals situation. When I gave birth my faithful pooch and curious kitty patiently awaited the arrival then came around and gave everything a sniff and that was it, that was all they needed to know. They gave me plenty of space and they were gentle and accepting toward the baby. I can’t say that every pet will react like mine did but I 100% believe that having the scent of the birth in the house communicated everything she needed to know in their first language, scent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every family and every baby is different and no matter how well you prepare you’re going to discover new things every day. We pick stuff up through trial and error, conversations with friends and family and from the media and somehow we make it through.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Consent</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/01/cyber-consent/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 10:20:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/02/01/cyber-consent/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;cyber-consent&#34;&gt;Cyber Consent&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/chalk.jpeg&#34; style=&#34;width:320px;height:213px;float:left;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 15px;&#34;&gt;
It’s time to have a little talk about cyber boundaries and cyber consent. This isn’t going to be one of my friendly Mom talks. Because many of you are not being very nice. If I have done it right, you will all feel sufficiently chastised before reaching the end of this article.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a few weeks now, I have been ruminating on all of the talk about dick picks and cyber whores and good girls and bad girls and sluts and fuckbois, on the internet. There is a lot to unpack with the combination of slut-shaming, virtue signaling, sex advertising, sex pushing and stalking going on on social media. By at least a magnitude of ten I have seen more tweets complaining about pictures of penises then I have seen penises on social media. Sexual harassment, unsolicited pictures, revenge porn and child pornography are real problems but there seems to be a whole genre of of internet memes and tweets dedicated to shaming other people for engaging in sexual behavior. Shame on you - people who invest time and energy into shaming people who engage in fully consensual activity. You need to find something better to do with your time then body shame people. Sex is fun normal and healthy and just because some people are more comfortable sharing their sexuality in public than you are doesn’t make you a better person. Prudishness does not constitute virtue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said, I think you all need a little primer on what constitutes consent and boundaries on the internet. Since we do not have reliable ways of verifying the identities of people on-line much of this is predicated upon the assumption of honesty of all involved parties. We are all on an honor system here people but let’s lay out the rules first so you know what to honor. This is not legal advice, rather this is a guide to being a not-shitty sexy human on the internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Cyberslut’s guide to internet consent:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minors, animals, and unconscious, overpowered, unwillingly restrained or inebriated people are not capable of consent. Don’t do any kind of sex with these. This includes creating, transferring or transfering images or telling stories of a sexually explicit nature. For the purposes of this list the term person means an adult, competent, human.
Images of a person’s body belong to that person. If a person transmits an image to you via private channel you do not have the right to transmit that image to others. This includes penises. Men’s right to bodily autonomy and privacy is equal to women’s. I shouldn’t have to say this but apparently I do. Some of you seem to be under the false impression that body shaming males is a form of feminism it isn’t. It’s just not ok to tell all men that all of their penises are gross and nobody ever wants to see them. Stop it. Body parts are not gross and if you say they are then you are.
Secure positive consent, before transmitting sexually explicit materials to a person either through invitation to view public materials or direct transfer via private channel. This involves asking them if they would like to view explicit materials, or if they want to engage in sexually explicit conversation with you.
Sexual stories about another person should not be shared in a way that does not take reasonable measures to conceal their identity. This is one of the reasons I maintain an anonymous persona, so I can speak honestly about my experiences without violating the privacy and consent any of my current or former partners. In some cases some of the stories that you see here are pre-approved by the partners involved just to be double sure.
Engaging in sexually explicit conversation and sharing of sexual materials through private channels is a form of intimacy. If you are in a committed relationship and you do not have the consent of your partner to engage in such activities this is cheating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that I have clearly posted my standards for cyber consent, I expect anyone interacting directly with me to abide by them. I consider any sexual activity that falls within these guidelines to be a normal expression of human sexuality. Sex is by its very nature a little odd and we may not understand or appreciate other people’s interests. Personally I find that tension fascinating.  Stumped Mom as an artistic project is dedicated to these differences and I have no tolerance for intolerance. So play nice out there.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex For Every Body</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/29/sex-for-every-body/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 14:34:34 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/29/sex-for-every-body/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you that follow me on twitter or catch up with me on guest blogs, or have even read my full catalogue you may be aware that I am going through a bit of a personal health crisis right now.  I have badly injured my lower back. You all know I write about sex but none have you been brave enough to ask. What has the impact of your lower back injury been on your sex life? But I’m going to answer the question anyway. I’m not gonna sugar coat it kids it’s been a major fucking bummer bummer. For weeks on end my back has been so sensitive to pressure and movement that arousal, pleasure and orgasms have been very difficult to achieve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But my partner and I are still managing to stay sexually active and we have not given up on pleasuring each-other or enjoying our intimacy.  Our pornographic and hollywood culture would have us think that the only sexy bodies are fit, young, athletic and hairless.  In the scheme of things - unless death takes us suddenly and at a young age, we will all experience disability and or injury at some-point in our lives. I have set it as a personal goal to someday get busted in the community room of the old folks home. But can you imagine what would happen to the world if everyone with a backache gave up on sex entirely? What would our relationship look like if we treated each other like sexual tools to be discarded at the first sign of dysfunction? This is my second encounter with a back injury, I have also experienced being nine-months-pregnant, post partum, and a slew of other injuries that have left one part or another not working at its prime. Sex while your hurting or less mobile can be a challenge and I have fumbled through more than a few of them. But we live we learn and we adapt. Here are my tips for adaptive sex:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be Flexible: I don’t mean make yourself a contortionist. The last thing a person experiencing a mobility problem wants to be told is to make their body more flexible for sex. I mean about your patterns, methods likes and dislikes. Consider your injury as an opportunity/excuse to try new things you might not normally try and perhaps get past some old hang-ups. You may want to re-negotiate some of your sexual and relationship boundaries with your partner. Maybe now is the time to give voyeurism or some other low contact fantasy a try. You may need to change up the time of day that you have sex. You might have to give up on having orgasms with your partner as often as you are used to and focus on intimacy, connection or excitement during the time you are together; with the understanding that you’ll both be having more solo sessions on the in-between.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chart the patterns: If you are dealing with injury, mood issues, hormone fluctuations, pain or fatigue, try to identify which times of day are your best times. Communicate with your partner about these best times. Give yourself the opportunity to enjoy pleasure during the the times it works for you. My mobility is at its best during mid-day. This is a bit of a bummer because my partner and I can almost never see eachother mid-day. But I find ways of making my mid-day solo sessions into an interactive experience, through phone calls, sexting and documentation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start with no-contact foreplay. If your body is experiencing challenges your sessions might need to be shorter to minimize the risk of aggravating an injury. You can get ready for your next in person encounter by engaging in no-contact to light contact foreplay. This means lots of flirting, fantasy talk, maybe role play, this could also mean sharing erotica together or pornography. You may find a few ideas in my cyberslut back catalogue. My partner and I are big sexters. I will get ready for a session by sending him messages about the last one, telling him what I am fantasizing about, maybe sending him little hints or leaving things for him to find that I know will turn him on and get me going in the process. By the time our clothes come off our bodies are super-responsive because we’ve been practicing in our head all day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Become a gear-head: I have a confession to make. For a self-proclaimed slut, I’m not very big on toys but they are coming out of the drawer more and more often lately. I have a few but I don’t use them very often and I am considering investing in a few more. Toys can extend your reach, give you new appendages, and make up for mobility and energy you or your partner may not have.  In addition to toys, consider using furniture pillows, slings and whatever other tools help you get into positions that work for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enjoy touch in other ways. Kiss, cuddle and enjoy your body and your partner’s body(s) in the ways that bring you both comfort and intimacy. I’m spending an awful lot of time lately with my head in my partners lap, having my hair stroked, because that’s what I want and it makes me feel better. If he happens to get a hard on while I’m there I may decide to get it out and play with it. My blog jobs are getting better and better lately.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know you’ve been waiting for it so here it is….Communicate! Tell your partner where you are how you are feeling and what is and is not working for you from day to day and moment to moment. Be specific, share details about how vigorous or firmly you can be touched or held. During the first few weeks of my most recent injury one of our biggest hurdles was my partner’s fear of doing something that would hurt me. Since he shared his fears I have been more specific with him about which positions are working for me at any given time, I tell him where he should put his hands, where my leg or knee can go and what my limits are. This has built his trust and we are starting to find a new groove.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Above all be gentle and forgiving present with yourself and your partner. Sometimes things aren’t going to work and that doesn’t have to be someone’s fault. I hope you give these methods a shot even/or especially if you aren’t experiencing a significant physical challenge or illness. Sex belongs to all of us! Being injured disabled or ill doesn’t mean that your sexual self goes away. And for many of us sexual connection is an important part of our intimate relationships to make it last over time we must adapt.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind Over Matter</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/23/mind-over-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 19:49:15 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/23/mind-over-matter/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Mind over Matter&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t tell you how excited I am to have been invited to do my first guest post. When Christina G. invited me to post on her site I was incredibly excited and flattered. She is literally one of five other bloggers out there I consistently enjoy reading. If you’re a stumper you owe it to yourself to check her out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ccorral.blogspot.com/2019/01/mind-over-matter.html&#34;&gt;Mind Over Matter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Segregation</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/20/supermarket-segregation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 10:32:10 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/20/supermarket-segregation/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;supermarket-segregation&#34;&gt;Supermarket Segregation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is segregation going on right under our noses in a place you depend on and likely bring your children. It is Supermarket segregation and it’s happening in grocery chains that have invested heavily in cultivating progressive images and niche markets. This isn’t an overt kind of Jim Crow segregation, where specific people are banned from employment or shopping at the stores. This segregation is a coded message written in product grouping, placement and signage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/kroger_dir.jpg&#34; class = &#34;lImage&#34; style=&#34;width:240px;height:320px;margin-top:5px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 15px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While most of the grocery store is organized by food grouping, breads, meats, pasta, spices, canned goods ets; foods deemed by supermarket managers, and product placement consultants to be sufficiently exotic to the customer base are placed in a specific isle labeled to mark these foods as different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At my neighborhood New Seasons, the self proclaimed, “Friendliest store in town”, much of the Latin American and Asian foods are shelved in the “global goods section” which is then subdivided into sub-categories including; “Mexican Food,” I highly doubt that any Mexican person has ever seen this sign and thought, “How convenient they have thoughtfully set aside all the food for Mexicans”. Italian inspired food has graduated from ethnic labeling and is just labeled “pasta” and “pasta sauce.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ever popular Target has the somewhat  outdated “Hispanic Meals” on isle 22. And they accomplish the amazing feat of getting the foods from ¾ of the world’s land mass into “Asian Meals and Sides” on isles 23. In these two rows you can find the Mexican classics Pace Picante Sauce (Made in San Antonio Texas by folks who know what salsa is supposed to taste like) and the Pacific Rim favorite Uncle Ben’s rice. Once again pasta and pasta sauce have graduated, you know, because all of the people who ever considered Italian people to be “colored” are dead now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/pace.jpg&#34; class=&#34;rImage&#34; style=&#34;width:240px;height:320px;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-left: 40px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At My local Kroger this section is called “international food and it is divided into asian foods, Latin American food and once again pasta. Here you can find your gumbo mix in this section as well as the super authentic Mexican Soft Tortilla Bowls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/wrong_item.jpg&#34; class = &#34;lImage&#34; style=&#34;width:240px;height:320px;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 15px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What does this kind of section labeling and product placement say about what they are expecting of their shopper?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To most of the customers it says:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are just going to go ahead and assume you are a white person who is only familiar with European and American cooking styles. So we put all of the exotic ingredients in one section and grouped them only partially accurately by regional cuisine, to make your fusion cooking experiment more user-friendly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other hidden message.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a person who’s family cooking style regularly uses these ingredients it says:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’d like you to know that your food is a little weird, and so are it’s regionally specific or imported products. By extension, you’re weird and you eat strange things, so we put it all in one place, so as not to confuse the normal people who are here to buy macaroni and cheese.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you feel like I am making a stretch ask yourself what if all the pillsbury mixes, quaker oats, maple syrup stove top stuffing and hamburger helper were in a section called, “Domestic Food”? I would like to point out that this bizarre segregation only applies to the shelf stable foods. Items that have to be refrigerated or frozen live with their food group categories in refrigerator cases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why are Rosarita’s Refried Beans not shelved with the other canned bean products? Can tortillas not be shelved with the bread? Why can’t dried peppers reside with the other dried foods? Why is the rice in the Asian foods when it is a staple of Cajun, Mexican, South American, and Caribbean cuisines?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is another model and to see it we need look no further than the quixotic and I’ll be it less than perfect grocery chain, Trader Joe’s. When it comes to shelf stable food they do just as I am suggesting. They organize them by ingredient type. Canned legumes go with canned legumes, soups with soups, grains with grains, and condiments regardless of origin, are all in the same isle. I’ve never seen a customer get confused about this and I’ve never heard a single person, in there ask where they can find the Mexican or Asian food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its so stupid it’s laughable but the cumulative impact of this kind of otherization is real. For Latinos it’s especially harmful. The racist language against Latinos in America has largely centered on food culture. We all remember “Taco trucks on every corner,” but lets not forget the pernicious slur “beaner” and the loathsom cultural tendency to describe latin women as “spicey”. Sure Germans were once routinely called Krauts but at least we have the decency to shelf the sauerkraut in the condiment section next to the ketchup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why should any of this matter Stumped Mom it’s just a grocery store?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well Stumpers it wouldn’t matter if it wasn’t just the grocery stores. The way that prejudice and racism is conveyed isn’t just through big overt actions, like institutionalized segregation, or redlining,it also operates on the level of these little things. Small interactions and signals that pile up like grains of sand that by themselves are insignificant but when piled en masse can crush a person. So what is it going to take to get our neighborhood grocery stores to de-exoticize foods that a routine part of American life? Just like any kind of change people need to speak up and it can’t just be the groups that are being targeted.  I like to say that I live by the credo. If you see it say it. Fill out a comment card, ask to speak to the manager and pass this blog post along.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Massively Multiplayer</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/15/massively-multiplayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 10:28:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/15/massively-multiplayer/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;massively-multiplayer&#34;&gt;Massively Multiplayer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/controller.jpeg&#34; style=&#34;width:320px;height:213px;float:left;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 15px;&#34;&gt;
If you’ve been keeping up with #cyberslut, you may have intimated that I have been a little bit adventurous, in recent years, when it comes to my sex life. I have had some experiences  in group sex, tried out fantasy scenarios and visited specialty clubs and the like. I also enjoy a robust fantasy talk relationship with my main partner which has been going strong for 3 years. We have had multiple group sex encounters and each one has built the trust that we have together. I have also had group play go terribly wrong and seen it act as the catalyst for the unraveling of relationships.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we continue and before you take any of my claims or observations too seriously please read “Owning Sex.”  When it comes to group sex IRL there are lots of safety issues I recommend you check out Planned Parenthood’s website for information about safer sex practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some things come down to a confluence of people and events that can’t be formulated. Group sex tends to be one of those things. But if there is a secret sauce it’s talking.
Like so many human endeavors the key to group sex, is communication. And the number one thing you need to talk about before even discussing group fantasies with a new partner or partners is your boundaries. Let me say that again. Boundaries, boundaries, boundaries. This can take time to flesh out, and can be even harder if you’re in a long term relationship and and you’ve never had this sort of conversation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If someone says they have no boundaries or lists hardly any that person isn’t ready for this rodeo or group play may not be for them. The thing to do is to take things slow, never try to push or coerce a partner that isn’t interested or ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t know what your boundaries are? Here is a starter pack of questions to get you started either on your own or with a partner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What kind of things excite you to hear about and watch?
What kinds of things frighten you, even as hypotheticals?
What feels unsafe to you?
What reassures you?
What makes you feel safe?
What doesn’t excite you but doesn’t scare or turn you off either?
How far do you want things to go?
Who can initiate?
How do you want things to start?
How do you want things to end?
What information are you willing to share with others?
If your boundaries are violated what is your default space for feeling safe?
What reinforces your trust?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In some relationships even discussing attractions to other people can be a challenge. Take things slow and check in with each other often. One boundary I have with my current partner is that fantasy talk is just that, talk. If I talk with him about a mutli-player fantasy he knows that does not imply that I intend or wish to fulfill that fantasy in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These guidelines don’t just apply to IRL situations. It is applicable for all forms of virtual group play. Including, sharing pornography, group fantasy talk and chats, camera play and virtual voyeurism/exhibitionism. If you enjoy certain kinds of pornographic materials but you are not interested in pursuing what is depicted make that boundary clear. Watching people do something on the screen does not mean you are committing to taking part in the same kinds of activities. Enjoying boxing matches doesn’t mean that you are ready to go toe to toe with the first taker in your weight class. Then again you might be a contender. The crucial element is preparation. Talk about your interests first. These kinds of conversations are great to have as a check in about your sex life in general. It is also great preparation for virtual group play.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sumped MomI still don’t get “virtual group play,” what does that include?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am glad you asked  virtual group play can take place with multiple people all in different locations chatting, via text, or even party line. It can take the form of sharing pictures, fantasies, it can include virtual exhibitionism through webcam and anything else you can imagine, in which technology is involved in connecting one or more of the participants. I once live sexted someone while I was having sex with another person. It was pretty hot for everyone involved (we had a threesome later).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to boundaries you should talk about before and after care with your playmates. Before and after care are the words, activities, and steps a person requires after sex play to feel safe and supported.  This can be anything you need or your partners need to feel safe and valued. Some people want time alone. Some people want to have a long chat. Some of us want to make everyone waffles after a long cuddle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of my safety tips from beginning fantasy talk apply to group virtual play. Be mindful of privacy, and check in with your partners both before and after.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This last weekend a reader asked me over Twitter Direct Messaging (I really do respond to messages about my blog) what it is like to have a threesome. Not sexting with readers is one of my boundaries, so at the time I just said it was exhausting because I didn’t want to get too titalting. Which is true, group sex can be very taxing both emotionally and physically, so eat your wheaties and remember to drink plenty of water. Personally I am prone to over stimulation and I have never climaxed during in person group sex. That being said there is no feeling in this world quite like bringing two people to climax at the same time. Multiplayer games aren’t for everyone but they are absolutely a thrill. If you do take that step to plug-in more than two players, please be safe and above all honor yourself and care for your playmates.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Dysfunctional Ways to Avoid a bad Boss</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/09/10-dysfunctional-ways-to-avoid-a-bad-boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 20:46:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/09/10-dysfunctional-ways-to-avoid-a-bad-boss/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;10-dysfunctional-ways-to-avoid-a-bad-boss&#34;&gt;10 Dysfunctional Ways to Avoid a bad Boss&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/bad_boss.jpg&#34; style=&#34;width:320px;height:213px;float:left;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 15px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for advice on how to be an efficient part of the capitalist machine the American news media and the internet have you covered. Forbes, the Wall Street Journal and LinkedIn supply a steady stream of content designed to help you be a compliant and striving little worker bee. I haven’t seen any metrics but these pieces wouldn’t proliferate so freely if they weren’t popular and therefore profitable. And why wouldn’t they be? We all want to succeed and be happy and we all want to advance but sometimes you get stuck stuck. Sometimes you have to just put up with a bad job or a bad boss to make ends meet. I am in no way condoning staying in a toxic workplace. I have been in one for years and not for lack of striving toward new opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe I’ve been self sabotaging because I have a co-dependant personality, but I have gotten up to the second interview in three jobs in the last year and gained nothing but higher blood pressure and “practice.” In the meantime, I have a mortgage to pay and a kid to feed an ex husband who is behind on his reimbursements and a boss who can best be described as a cross between Capt. Queeg, Mallory Sterling, and The Millionaire’s wife from Gilligan’s Island. She leaves me alone with almost nothing to do for long stretches of time and then, when I do see her, she dumps on me with a load of new projects and  or criticism of work that I gave her for review or approval so long before that it’s been completely forgotten about it. If I get ambitious and try to take initiative, on anything without her approval I get a pretty rapid smackdown. I don’t have a ton of options for what to do with myself. For those of you with a boss like mine, a micromanager who also ignores her employees for long stretches and lacks basic human empathy, I have assembled this handy list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10 Dysfunctional Ways to Avoid a Bad Boss:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Know the Schedule. This is the first and most important and you’re not going to succeed at any of the others unless you have it. Know your bosses schedule. This may be simple if your boss publishes and sticks to a schedule. If they don’t publish a schedule see if you can cozy up to an assistant to get the deets. My boss publishes a schedule and she doesn’t stick to it so my system isn’t fool proof.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calibrate your hours. If at all possible start earlier and leave earlier than your boss. My office offers flexible work schedules. In that we have a three hour window in which to set our usual start time (7:00 am- 10:00 am) and a three hour window to set our end time (4:00-7:00 p.m.) My boss roles in, like the Queen of the May, between 9:30-10:00 a.m. each day. I try to get in around 8:15 a.m..  If I’m running really late and get to work at 8:45 she’s none the wiser, unless I get ratted out by those snitches in accounting. I am out the door, no later than 5:00 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Employ Conversation Repellent. When at your desk, wear headphones or earbuds, this won’t stop the old ringmaster from cracking the whip, when they really want something but it will put the breaks on small talk which are really just attempts to pry into your life so they can judge you for it later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Look Busy. During the times that you know the boss will be moving through your work spaces get out your most busy looking least fun looking projects. I save all my spreadsheets and filing project for my bosses in-office and between meeting hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lunch Early. Schedule your lunch right before your boss’s lunch.If you’re getting in before your boss you should be able to step out to lunch just after they have caught up with their inbox and to-list.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be a Go Getter (literally). Volunteer for office errands. If at all possible run those errands right when you expect your boss to get back from lunch. This can buy you another half hour and whatever it was they wanted to talk to you about when you left or lunch will likely be forgotten about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep your mind occupied. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to get up to no-good if you don’t have something productive to do. Find something creative to do with your time that enriches you and still looks like work. Like maybe a blog. but not a blog like this one. This is my market niche. Get your own!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep a log of misdeeds. If your boss is riding the line for abuse, discrimination or harassment, keep a log of misdeeds. My boss got really testy with me at my last review and I made sure she knew that I had a log and picked out a few examples from it in which she was being a total cunt. Don’t give your boss the log, keep the log on a file source that only you have access to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Send it in an Email. Get whatever it is you do need to get done and  done on time. Deliver it to the boss’s inbox before it’s asked for. If you have a question, send it in an email. Send, send, send until you are told to stop. If your boss is sorting and reading your messages they are not at your desk breathing on you. Or sneaking up to try to catch you reading stumpedmom.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be ready.  Alas you cannot avoid your boss forever so you must be ready. Have a folder or a packet ready for when the boss drops in on you. Have your list of things you need from them. Make a habit of it. You want them to know that everything has a price and the price of bothering you is being reminded of how ahead of them you are and how  underutilized your talents are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck out there stumpers. I can’t guarantee you it will get better. I can’t even guarantee you that we won’t all be jumpsuit-wearing, serf-level drones of the Bezos corporation, living off of Soil N Green in ten years but I hope these tips get you by if your boss happens to be as unbearable as mine is.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owning Sex</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/08/owning-sex/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 10:05:49 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/08/owning-sex/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;owning-sex&#34;&gt;Owning Sex&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This past week, I received my first feedback from a self described, lifestyle kinkster, about the #cyberslut. I admit, I went out on a limb and inserted myself into their conversation, hoping to reach out to new audiences and expand my reach. This feedback described some of my assertions as inaccurate fundamentally wrong. I asked them to share resources on the topics but they did not respond. I am no stranger to criticism of my position, style or punctuation, but rarely have I ever been accused of being inaccurate or fundamentally wrong and certainly not by a person who wasn’t prepared with sources of information to directly refute my claims.This spurned me on a deep level of academic pride and caused me to question my grounds upon which I wished to stake my position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src = &#34;../../../../images/mouth.jpeg&#34; style=&#34;width:320px;height:213px;float:left;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px; margin-right: 15px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had a pretty damn good college History professor and adviser, who did a thorough job of holding his students the difference between observation and generalization. He taught me how to avoid the latter through the employment of sufficient qualifications and citations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The difference between observation and generalization:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To observe is report on your own experience.
To generalize is to portray your own observation as a broader truth&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only truth I claim is in my own experience. Sex, pleasure and arousal by their own nature‘s belong to each individual human experience. Your sex and your experience cannot possibly claim to refute or invalidate my own no matter what your education is,or what your sexual experiences have been or how you identify.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my “Introduction to Fantasy talk,” in Particular I made it clear that all observations were based on my own experience and observations or what has been reported to me by, individuals that identify as belonging to particular named groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel I have touched on that point  in each of my edition or a that I have been speaking casually from my own limited personal understanding and experience. This blog is an art project and a form of personal recreation. I am not going to do a paper on comparative sexual and psychological studies. Not, because I lack the capacity but because I have no real interest in doing so, as it wouldn’t contribute toward my aims.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My goal is to be able to connect with as many people as I can, to start  a casual and accessible conversations about sexting, and kink and group sex and other sexual practices that are still broadly stigmatized. I wanted to be able to talk to with people in ways that are not confined to the language and codes for sex that have been dominated of the pornography industry or kink communities. For me this is personal and social feminist and progressive work. Systems of order can deprive the individual of many things but they can never take from something as inexorably attached to our intimate selves then our sexuality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may never lay claim to my sex nor may I lay claim to yours. To be clear I do use some generally recognizable categories to sort and classify my observations but my purpose in using them is only for general conversation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which brings us back to the question at hand. To write or not to write?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This  week’s post was promised to be a segment on group sexual fantasies with some points on IRL application I was calling “Massively Multi-Player”. As a person who has participated in just one foursuom, a handful of threesomes, and several live and virtual voyeuristic experiences  and has only virtually seduced one man, three women and two couples into meeting up with me and a partner for group sex, how could I possibly pretend to be able to speak with any sort of authority on the subject?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well the answer was that I was claiming no authority but my own and I shall keep writing and I shall keep repeating:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My observations are only my own, and I do not portray them to be  that but my own.
I claim no recognizable qualifications as an expert on any of these subjects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have I lost anyone, class?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I was saying, this blog is on the same academic level of: shit I say when I’m at the pub. If you could find my actual regular pub and read the bartenders there this blog, I have a feeling they could guess which patron wrote it. This is it. This is me. This is how I talk. This is how I think. This is how I write. And I pretend at nothing more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just look at the time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I have dedicated all of my readily available mental energies and faculties into sorting out this epistemological knot, I have been unable to apply appropriate attention to this week’s promised edition of cybersluttery: “Massively Multi-player.”  For this disservice, dearest stumpers, I am sorry. I promise to try to make it up to you all as I dedicate my clear head and sharpened faculties to produce a particularly juicy one for you next week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And as to the haters?
I say to thee
I do not yield sirs madams and thous
Not Today
I DO NOT!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Struggle With Ableism</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/03/my-struggle-with-ableism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/03/my-struggle-with-ableism/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-struggle-with-ableism&#34;&gt;My Struggle With Ableism&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About two years ago while I was stuck working night shift for a few weeks, I got really into the &lt;a href=&#34;https://implicit.harvard.edu/implicit/iatdetails.html&#34;&gt;Harvard Implicit Bias test&lt;/a&gt; project. The tests ask you to react quickly to a series of images and is designed to measure your unconscious bias towards groups. I felt super great about myself when I took my first test and found out I was biased in favor darker skinned people and against lighter skinned people (an outlier result for a white woman). I highly encourage any person who wants to improve their personal awareness of bias in all of its forms to check it out. The tests ask you to react quickly and repeatedly to images of people belonging to certain groups with either an up or down response. The idea is to measure your immediate associations rather than your conscious belief about groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I lost the spring in my step and my sense of personal self righteousness when I did the ableism assessment. It indicated pretty strong bias against people with disabilities. I have vacillated between shame and denial about this since. My bias and my sense of identity were at odds. My grandmother was a public accessibility activist, my favorite uncle has been wheelchair bound my entire life. I’ve gone through the local children’s museum and come out with a checklist for management about the ways they could be more accessible and inclusive. I manage my office with near obsessive attention to reasonable accommodation needs. How could I be ableist?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the past two years I have been letting this knowledge sit, while I tried to reconcile myself with it and then I hurt my back again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have already been through the back pain struggle and I mean I have really been there. I ruptured a disk about 4.5 years ago and I went through 6 months of misdiagnosis and bad treatments before surgery pretty much saved my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took me 4 years of careful rehabilitation bu this fall  I was almost back to the activity level I had achieved pre-surgery, I was back to training in my martial arts at a high level and back to lifting what I was before I hurt my disk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few weeks ago I was lifting an awkward item for work and I felt my back twinge. Its been getting worse for weeks and the pain is all too familiar. I have, for the second time in my life, gone from being able to land spinning kick to a peers face, with good humored alacrity to barely being able to get out of a chair or tie my shoes.All within a week of an accident that felt like a muscle pull at first. Now that I find myself staring down a period of possibly, open ended prolonged physical disability I’ve been forced in many ways to confront how my ableism functions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am terrible at asking for help. I pride myself on my independence, resilience and ingenuity especially when it comes to adapting to injuries. In the first week of this current injury, I was focused on how very proud I was to be able to kneel down from a tight stance with my back straight to reach things on the floor since I can’t bend over. I also did not want to use any assistive devices.  I always looked as this trait as a strength and it certainly has earned me admiration from others over the years. But this personal quality has undeniably caused me and my loved ones unnecessary pain and suffering. I have delayed treatment, violated instructions and sabotage my own recovery all because I am afraid of looking weak or being a burden on my family, friends or co-workers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This time, as I look at the possibility of going through a long period of pain again I want to do it smarter. I want to demand the treatment that I need, speak up with things cause me further pain and use accommodations, devices and assistance that will reduce my suffering.  I have committed myself to really putting myself first and advocating for the treatment that I need. But feelings of shame, over being hurt are still holding me back and this has caused me to confront the ugly roots of my own ableism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I ain’t no cripple!” I drawled “I can get it myself!” These were the loving and gracious words that came out of my mouth as my boyfriend tried to help me pick up after my dog. The line was delivered with an exaggerated affect that indicated my self-deprecating irony, but they were still real, it meant something to me.“Cripple,” Where did that ugly word even come from?  It is possibly one of the ugliest words in the English language and in that moment it came flowing from me with effortless familiarity.. When I said it I felt I heard the voices of my uncles, aunts, father and cousins slipping easily from me in what was only a half mock parody. The word was batted about with regularity and jest during my formative years often in the presence of family members with permanent mobility impairments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was raised in a family full of disabilities and differences but exposure to these differences and loving relationships with differently abled people wasn’t enough. I learned from casual jokes that there was shame in disability and that any injury I sustained was a burden on my family. I have not yet found a manual on unlearning this deeply ingrained feeling, but I know that the best version of me is ready to be rid of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumpers can you help me and come with me on this journey? Can you call out my ableism when you see it? Can you share your own stories with me and help me build my perspective and compassion? I could probably do it on my own but I think this thing will be better for everyone if I don’t try.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Fantasy Talk</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/01/advanced-fantasy-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2019/01/01/advanced-fantasy-talk/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;advanced-fantasy-talk&#34;&gt;Advanced Fantasy Talk&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two entries ago I promised to get into some more advanced fantasy tips and I am nothing if not a woman of my word. These are my more advanced tips for a slightly kinkier level of fantasy play. I claim zero expertise in kink; for that you’re going to have to go to different corners of the internet but those corners can be scary and intimidating, even if they really are actually filled with regular people who just happen to enjoy novel sexual if experiences. But there is also a lot of stuff that most people just don’t want to see. Just a quick foray can leave you feeling like 16 year old Stumped Mom did after watching &lt;em&gt;8mm&lt;/em&gt; in the theatre. There are as many kinks to be discovered as there are stars in the sky. Today I am going to give you some tips on working within some common kink sub-types. All but the first kink on my list below can be found in both dominant and submissive partners and can be applied in a range of intensities. For the basics of Dominance and Submission please read &lt;a href=&#34;https://stumpedmom.com/2018/12/17/dabling-in-kink/&#34;&gt;Dabbling in Kink.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humiliation Submission: One of the ways to express power in sex is to humiliate  others. In its gentlest form humiliation an be manifested in playful banter or name calling. For people that enjoy it, it can offer a release from their feelings of shame or guilt surrounding enjoyment. Humiliation is a delicate thing. Treat it carefully, ask your partners if they are into it, or look for signs like sexual self deprecation, before just unloading on them with verbal abuse. Pro tip- I have never found a person of color in America, who is into humiliation submission,my personal theory is that they deal with too much of that shit every damn day in our culture to find it sexy in the bedroom. I urge you to handle humiliation submission with care, it can be very damaging to relationships if it isn’t handled correctly. Personally I enjoy saying I’m sorry a lot during sex and it enhances the experience for me if my partner will tell me why I should be.*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Voyeurs:  A true voyeur is a gem and they are actually hard to find. Most of us enjoy watching sexual acts but few of us fetishize looking but not touching. My first threesome was with a woman who we only brought home to watch but she couldn’t keep her hands off, she turned out to be a marriage wrecking rhinoceros disguised as a unicorn.  That being said a true voyeur as a fantasy talk partner is great if you enjoy spinning a sexy yarn voyeurs will eagerily lap up sexy stories past future and present especially if you give them space to be the watcher in those stories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Masochists: My armchair theory about masochists is that they are show offs. Every middle school kid who has gotten a hold of H.P. lovecraft thinks they have discovered the secret to the pain pleasure cycle. There is some complex a &lt;a href=&#34;https://bodyinmind.org/pain-pleasure-relationship/&#34;&gt;neurological and hormonal&lt;/a&gt; stuff that goes on with pain and the neural pathways during sex and everyone is a bit different. What I find  gets masochists off is being able to impress you with how much pain they can take. If you have one in fantasy talk they will be very excited to talk about how you’d like to push their limits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sadists: I try not to judge but I have never stuck around to find out what makes a true sadist tick and I would advise anyone who thinks they have encountered a true sadist to avoid. But the S in and M is usually about playing the part just enough to make it exciting it’s not about getting off on hurting people.  Most people who will willingly dish out a little bit of pain with pleasure are people pleasing dominants who are excited by pushing boundaries and breaking social scripts. If someone surpases your boundaries and hurts you in a way you did not want for their own pleasure it is assault. I am switchy and I also know a bit about joint locks. When I am dominating I’ll administer a bit of pain to enhance my partners excitement but I recoil at the idea of causing pain for its own sake or allowing someone to do the same to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Risk takers: For many people just about anything that enhances the risk of sex makes it more exciting. This can include the risk of getting caught, being late, being rejected or just messing it up. If you’re trying to please a risk taker just remember it’s all about measured risk and novelty. You shouldn’t really have to fuck on the fire escape to please them you can get them excited by sending them sexy messages when they are at work or pretty much anywhere else where getting caught could lead to consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These five elements of kink are not exclusive or exhaustive. I encourage you to try them gradually if they are new for you. Start with little suggestions or questions and see where it takes you.  There is no need to dive in head first with any of these types of fantasies unless taking things on all at once is what really excites you, in that case don’t let me be the one to stop you. When I first started cyberslut  I thought was going to just be a three part series but each time I sit down to write I find myself tabling things for the next piece.  It has also been super popular because who would have guessed that people love reading about sex on the internet? Next week we’ll be talking about massive multi-player kinks: Orgy lovers, groupers, cucks, hotwifes, double-topping, Unicorns and more. And I plan to keep at it so long as the material keeps coming to mind. Thanks for reading and for playing. I love to hear about your experiences and experiments so please feel free to catch up with me through my contact page, on twitter or in the comments. Just don’t try sexting with me through dm’s it’s the internet equivalent of trying to pick up a stripper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;*&lt;/code&gt; Humorous  anecdote; a few summers ago while my partner and I were enjoying a vigorous fuck with a bit of spanking with the windows open and shouted “I’m sorry!” enough that one of the neighbors came up to my back fence and asked if I needed assistance. She started shouting at my partner to leave me alone or she would jump the fence. So try not to alarm the neighbors while you’re playing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Purge</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/20/the-purge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/20/the-purge/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-purge&#34;&gt;The Purge&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome Stumpers,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to the good vibes only zone. Come along with me on a journey to awesomeness while improving your life, your mind, your body and your soul with a thorough and complete cleansing. Now is the time to rid ourselves of negativity in our lives. You don’t need negative people or influencers pulling you down with them. If they don’t affirm you and all of your most ardent desires, or make your sandwiches and give you orgasms, flatter your taste and intelligence, block them, delete them, ignore them and feel free to abandon with abandon. It’s time to manifest only positivity by adding subtraction to your life. If you can’t identify the immediate benefit that a loved one brings to your individual goals it’s time to re-examine that relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grandma doesn’t like your vegan gluten free baking?
Maybe you don’t need to visit her anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t like awkward encounters with strangers?
Wear headphones all the time to signal to the world you have more important things to hear&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is that old friend of yours asking for too much emotional support?
Stop taking her calls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can make every moment of your life feel like those last few warm engrossing minutes of your yoga class. All can be perfect tender and toasty like a fresh beignet. You can be filled with boundless self esteem.  All doubts can be eliminated. Don’t worry about hurting others in your pursuit of creating a perfect bubble of self reflection free positive re-enforcement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom I think You’re laying it on right now!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hell’s yeah I’m laying it on right now. I don’t care if my weak attempt at satirical tone is as subtle as a flying brick.  I am sick to death of social media, celebrities regular media and people all around me in my life acting like the way to cope with all of the friction in our lives is to avoid it.  As if we can ignore away every uncomfortable interaction or piece of feedback and experience no negative consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know who was a real fucking buzzkill? The soothsayer in Shakespeare’s Julius Caesar. What did that guy say?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Beware the Ides of March!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What a douche, that guy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Caesar. He was a real go getter- the grand conqueror of the Gauls. Like a Goop blog regular he knew what to do about killjoys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“He is a dreamer; let us leave him: pass.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s modern English for “Press Ignore.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are also pretty welcome to ignore the obvious lesson here. Shakespeare knew as did countless other sage observers of humans that we need naysayers in our lives to to guard us from our own conceit.  We cannot get out of our own heads to see ourselves completely. We need the help of others not only to lift us up but to reign us in. Everything we do and say is warped by our individual perceptions and petty desires. It feels good in the short term and maybe even in the medium term to block out criticism, to don our rose colored glasses and apply a Snapchat life filter to our world, especially when we feel beset by an endless deluge of negative crap. But what becomes of us when we crop out all of our “negative relationships”- When we limit our interactions to the ones that are immediately gratifying?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the accelerating negative narratives of our time is the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/modern-mentality/201807/what-you-need-know-about-the-loneliness-epidemic&#34;&gt;epidemic of loneliness&lt;/a&gt;. Powered by social media and social anxiety, Americans are becoming increasingly isolated from real connections. Somehow, in the face of all of this, there is a proliferation of popular advice and attitudes that encourage, people, especially women, to ignore or eliminate interactions with other people. Good Vibes Only is blanketing the world with the suffocating demand that all friendships are predicated on a commitment to constant flow of positivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few weeks ago I was kvetching about my ex-husband with my oldest friend and she agreed completely with my perspective on things. I asked her if she was only agreeing with me because she’s my bestie. I cannot begin to say how refreshing it was to hear a very dear friend say to me, “If you’re wrong it’s more loving of me to call you out on it.”  And that is why we’ve been friends for over 25 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Setting boundaries is great. Encouraging one another is awesome. But demanding constant unconditional approval from all of our relationships is leaving a lot of us with a dearth of friends to turn to. We’re ghosting ourselves into an empty corner full of hollow sycophants and profiteers.  Maybe it’s time to consider addressing negativity through addition. Meet negative with positive and hold off on the purge.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dabling in Kink</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/17/dabling-in-kink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 19:43:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/17/dabling-in-kink/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;dabling-in-kink&#34;&gt;Dabling in Kink&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you frustrated with mainstream sex advice? Do you find the world fo kink frightening or inaccessible? I don’t blame you if you do. I do too, but I have dabbled enough in the virtual world of kink to get a handle on the basics. I have noticed that mainstream sex advice couples to,  “explore role play” if they are bored and stops there. Which really isn’t fair, it is a deep subject when many nuances. Where does an injeunui even begin? I’m no sex columnist or relationship therapist but I want to help my friends.  I’ve already bumbled around the world of sex and kink and made a fool of myself so you don’t have to (unless you’re into that.) Today we are going to talk about dominance and submission. If you want to understand fantasy, or kink or get just plain better at sex, it will behoove you to get a strong handle on this topic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there is a universal theory in the world of fantasy talk, sex, and kink its got to be dominance vs. submission.One of the primary engines of sexual excitement is the negotiation of power and control between partners. Everyone has certain preferences and needs when it comes to what power dynamics turn them on. Even if you believe you’re having vanilla sex, one partner is usually taking more control than the other and one may like being in control more than the other.  The partner who likes to take more initiative is dominant partner and the partner who enjoys letting others take the lead is the submissive. Get a handle on this dynamic and learn to play with it and you just may be able to save yourself from sexual monotony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like just about all things sex submission and dominance present in a spectrum and no one is just one thing all of the time. Since this is a taboo subject to talk about in most circles many people don’t identify themselves on this spectrum but figuring out where you are on the spectrum and paying attention to it in your partners is one of the keys to more exciting fantasy play and sex. Let’s talk about some of the characteristics of each and see if we can’t dispel some myths&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dominants Doms:&lt;/strong&gt; Sometimes dominants get a bad rap. There is a misconception floating around that dominants especially dominant men are abusive people who just want to hurt and control others. While this can certainly happen, enjoying dominance in the bedroom or during fantasy does not necessarily mean that a person is going to be controlling in their relationships.  My current partner is very much a dominant and he only enjoys submission as a prelude to flipping the script and regaining control. He’s also super sensitive to my needs and is categorically incapable of getting off if he senses I am uncomfortable or unhappy. In my own experience I have found that dominance is often a form of nurturing turned all the way up. A lot of doms are super caring people who are excited by taking control of other people’s pleasure. When I am in a dominant mood I feel like I want to take care of everything for my partner including telling them everything they like. I am dominating best at it when I am hyper attuned to a partners signals and needs. So if you want to get a dom off gradually reveal to them ways you enjoy being vulnerable. They also really like it when you beg for things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Submissives (subs):&lt;/strong&gt;  are conversely stereotyped as milktoast people who don’t know their own minds or have low self esteem. A lot of things can characterize the motivations of a submissive but being weak willed isn’t really correlated. For many submissives the excitement lies in surrender.  If you surrender all the time in your daily life you may not find it that exciting during sex. I find myself most excited by submission when I’m feeling tired and stressed from too many responsibilities and decisions. The best way to excite a sub is by showing fearless initiative. At the same time you need to treat submission as a gift cherish it and never take it for granted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Switches:&lt;/strong&gt; Some people treat switches liked mixed up geminis or court jesters.  A switchy person is a person who is comfortable moving pretty far into both ends of the dominant and submissive spectrum. I find  that switchers are often experimental people pleasers. They will adjust to your mood and your needs easily be careful not to abuse this flexibility, they can extend themselves too far. They can be tricksters and wild cards as well they are driven by novelty so they can be prone to boredom.The key to enjoying a switchy partner is to really meet them where they are that day. If you really want to activate a switch suggest trying something new and show that you have taken the steps to make it possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next week I promise to go into a deeper dive into some of the more esoteric kinks I have encountered. The important thing to remember is that being a sub or a dom or a switch does not reflect on your value as a person. It’s like being a cat or a dog person and if you’re dying to know where I land in that spectrum, I like both cats and dogs and all pets seem to like me. Now go out there and find yourself the perfect pet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Brain</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/13/twitter-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 08:30:27 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/13/twitter-brain/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;twitter-brain&#34;&gt;Twitter Brain&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Twitter Brain; Noun:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The condition resulting from excessive attention to Twitter characterized by intense effort toward building your personal brand  and attracting new followers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A person who thinks too much about their Twitter following.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example:
&lt;em&gt;Stump Mom’s writing and research and overall attention were suffering because she had Twitter Brain.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have recently come to terms with a reality that much America has been living with or some time - It doesn’t take much to come down with a case of Twitter Brain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Twitter started to capture the media imagination and take the public discourse by storm I reacted to it, as a typical American seven year would react to a novel food; I didn’t need to taste it, smell it, or even try it, I knew I didn’t like it. By the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.digitaltrends.com/social-media/tweet-is-now-officially-a-word-in-the-oxford-english-dictionary/&#34;&gt;time&lt;/a&gt; tweet earned its second definition in the Dictionary I had fully formed my identity as a conscientious Twitter Objector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump’s notorious use of the platform and Twitters unwillingness to apply any of its existing applicable policy to reign him only deepened my apprehension for the platform. And I admit, I felt superior to all those poor sad saps out there confusing their lives away on the tweets. I took a sense of comfort from knowing that I was not contributing to Twitter or to the apparent political and cultural meltdown that was taking place live on the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But in the fall of 2018 My personal convictions did not hold up very long against an emerging need. I was developing an anonymous, totally groundbreaking, form defying, norm challenging underground mommy blog. I needed readers and if I wanted to remain anonymous, readers who did not know me personally. Lacking any sort of advertising budget or promotional team I understood from all the media chatter that the best way to achieve my aim was to become a Twitter ninja.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I’m anonymous I couldn’t go out to all my real life buddies and say, “Hey guys! Support my project and follow my creative alter ego,” No “Import Contacts” for me I had to start from scratch. So I put together my profile, and started tweeting.  Words cannot describe the thrill I felt when I attracted my first follower. I’m talking about you @sarahjschlott. Once I got that first taste, I was thirsty for more. There is nothing quite like that dopamine hit that comes from receiving the endorsement of social approval from strangers even when coming from a form as superficial as the “heart” button. I started carving out time in my mornings for Twitter. After spending one particularly frenzied morning focusing on zinger re-tweets, new takes and interesting stories, I tried to develop one of my posting ideas and my writing fell flat. The words went limp on the page. No sparkling metaphors, amusing tangents or clever literary devices flowed from my brain. I couldn’t on my stories, my mind was on my Tweets and my followers. Twitter had consumed my thinking and become an end in itself. Twitter had blocked up my brain. This brought me to the edge of complete and total panic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blog content tends to come pouring out of me in big rushes. I usually have a lot more trouble editing managing and scheduling content then I do producing it and even on a rough day I am usually good for a few disjointed yet promising paragraphs.  But after dousing my brain in the social reward, live MMORPG we call Twitter I couldn’t think past 280 characters of accessible slop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But there is good news the first step to overcoming a preoccupation is to acknowledge that you have it.  So I’ve got Twitter Brain and the only cure is to write about it! Well not exactly, but the first step in recovery was starting this post on Twitter affliction.. I won’t say I have achieved ballance or that I’m happy with my Twitter habit but the following measures have helped me keep it from completely killing my productivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I downloaded a Tweet Scheduling app  I settled on Buffer but there are lots of choices. by using a Tweet Scheduling app I am able to write down my best ideas when they come to me and strategically schedule them. I can also do this without checking my feed and getting distracted with other people’s activities. This lets me sit back and enjoy family time or writing time without worrying about missing the best posting hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I turned off push notifications on my cell phone. It seems like it will give you advanced assurance but what it really does is gets you checking your feed when you picked up your phone to look at the weather or the time. I’ve also figured out how to turn off notifications on very active blog threads all together.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have started connecting directly with more bloggers and followers. I have used popular blogging hashtags to find links to other blogs similar to mine. I am starting to build more personal individualized relationships with other bloggers and followers. Trading messages and interacting with their blogs. This tends to build more lasting connections.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m doing what I want. When I first got on to Twitter the way that I answered my set-up questions and the first accounts I followed got me siloed into Parent Twitter. I love connecting with other parents but parent Twitter was a bit confining for my rebellious soul. I was very cautious in my early tweets, because my read of the room (which was full of parent bloggers) said that I needed to be. I’ve sharpened my content and my voice on Twitter to conform less to the parent Twitter ideals and reflect my Stumped Mom mission. I saw some pronounced follower losses when I first made this switch but I have recovered and made connections with writers and thinkers who appreciate my work and my irreverence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a side hustle or a blog how do you manage balancing your promotional activities with your core work? I’d love to hear from you all what your thoughts are on Social Media and connecting with your audience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginning Fantasy Talk</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/11/beginning-fantasy-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 00:06:13 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/11/beginning-fantasy-talk/</guid>
      
        <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;beginning-fantasy-talk&#34;&gt;Beginning Fantasy Talk&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Stumpers:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been inspired by other bloggers to talk about the things I really enjoy. And one of my favorite sources of entertainment is sex and fantasy talk. If twitter is any indication there is a lot of stigma around cyberesex, sexting and fantasy talk and that’s reason enough to talk at length about it. I do so love pissing twitter prudes off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Credentials: I haven’t gone to school for sex therapy or been in the sex industry in any way or anything like that but what I have been doing is talking dirty with people online since 1999. I’ve never had sex with a person I did not seduce online first. I once got a challenge from a friend to see how many men I could meet on Tinder and talk into jacking off and showing me proof in a picture, in one day.I got bored after bachelor number nine and it was before dinner time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On gender and sexual orientation: I am writing from the perspective of a cis gendered female whose primary sexual and romantic experiences have been with people who identify as straight cis males. For the purposes of clarity and readability when I refer to “men” I am talking about people who identify themselves as hetero and bi-sexual males. In what I am sure is a benefit to all involved I’ve never really had an attraction to or sexual experience with a gay man. I have had sexual experiences and attractions with straight men and bi-women but I’ve never felt a romantic pull toward another woman. I identify myself as a heteroromantic bisexual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I say “partner” I mean any adult person who willingly and consensually engaged in sexual behavior with me ranging from online flirtation to actual intercourse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I happen to be blessed with some pretty cool and sex positive friends and yet even among these people I find that conversation about sexting and online play are taboo. People are embarrassed to talk about it and that makes it hard to get good at. But getting good at it can be a boon to your sex life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Safety first: When it comes to online play one of the primary dangers is privacy. Everything you say or show is potentially transmittable to the whole world.  Just like when you meet someone in real life it’s a judgment call when to trust someone, be mindful of which details about yourself could be cross referenced to find your identity. Consider creating a seperate web identity for play. Set up an email and facebook with a pseudonym and use it to set up your chatting and dating apps. Don’t give out your real phone number, use an emulator. Just like with real life sex you can take precautions but there is no way to eliminate the risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be clear about your boundaries. Just as it’s good safer sex and consensual practice to talk about boundaries before physical sex, you should talk about your boundaries before during and after virtual play. Be clear about your “hard passes” and deal breakers. I am also pretty big on transparency and intent if you have no intention of escalating to IRL, be clear about it. If you are in a Romantic partnership where your partner consents to you being involved in online or virtual play, say so.  Whatever your limit is, state it, this will usually select out the jerks who will try to pressure, slut shame or guilt you into exceeding your boundaries and may also keep you from breaking any hearts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think of it as play acting. Most of the rules of improv apply. You’re creating a scene with another person and playing a part you need to listen to and observe your partner to discover what part they want to play. Just like in child’s play or improvisation if you balk at your partner&amp;rsquo;s ideas the game will come to a pretty abrupt halt.  If you do decide you want to bring a game to swift conclusion this is a good way to get someone to stop playing with you. If you outright reject someone’s kink or fantasy idea, they may not trust you to play again. I have done this intentionally when a partner said something that I found degrading or violent toward women.  I make it pretty clear when I discuss boundaries that that’s one of my hard lines.  There is a certain subset of people who do seek degradation of their desires as part of their fantasy play which I will go into more in Part II Advanced Fantasy talk next week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do some homework. Read some of the classics of erotic fiction. Pay attention to the patterns, imagery and symbols when you read, think about what turns you on and what makes you uncomfortable. Learn about sexual and social scripts.  My personal theory is that the excitement of fantasy and role play often centers around playing off of these scripts, pushing their boundaries and sometimes subverting them. The high brow thing to know here is that sexual stories are part of our culture and you are participating in it by creating and enacting your own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let yourself be a little mundane. Much of our sex culture and concepts of sexual fantasy have shaped us to believe that fantasy requires, exotic locations, improbable scenarios, hairless physiques and polished shiny bodies. I have found that partners are turned on by small bits of private life that often seem very regular and routine. Intimacy is more exciting than many people realize. Give partners the idea that they are being admitted into a special sphere of privilege. I have had tons of success by revealing little things like aspects of my grooming routine. Fantasy at its best is the perfect blend of the accessible and the ideal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anticipation, Anticipation, Anticipation! You’ll generate more excitement and keep your partners more engaged, if you give them a balance of anticipation, contribution and reward. Would Super Mario Brothers be one of the most popular video games in history and would Nintendo have become a video gaming behemoth if Mario rescued the princess after you easily defeated level 1? No, no one would  have played it because it would have been boring. Yes people, especially men  like to see and invision, body parts and penetrative acts, but it’s more fun if you work your way up to it. Don’t go straight into revealing full fantasy scenes, or just sending pictures of your body parts unless you want to be boring.Let things slowly build hold out on your good stuff until you’re really feeling it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Variety is the Spice of Life: Nobody is just one thing all the time. If you’re engaging with someone over a long period of time or across multiple platforms and in real life, give your partner&amp;rsquo;s space to play a range of roles while you try on a few complimentary versions of yourself. Treat your partners like the complex imaginative individuals that they are and they will surprise you maybe as much as you surprise them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are seven basics to get you started if you’re shy about sexting and fantasy talk.  But don’t forget the most important thing of all: Have fun. If it isn’t fun or rewarding for you don’t do it, move on to something that you like. It’s totally okay to not like things and you deserve to be with partners who won’t be satisfied if you’re not having fun. If you  have questions please feel free to send me a message and ask, just don’t ask me to practice with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whiteclaiming</title>
      <link>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/06/whiteclaiming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://StumpedMom.com/2018/12/06/whiteclaiming/</guid>
      
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Fellow White People,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The time has come for us to stop Whiteclaiming. The time has come for us to stop feigning in aspects of the cultures of non-white people by virtue of proximity.  For the sake of brevity I am dubbing this phenomenon whiteclaiming. Whiteclamining occurs when a white person claims specific special understanding of something they associate with an ethnic group based on who they know or where they are from. I’ve seen this most often in discussions of cuisine, in which people will claim to have developed particular special knowledge of Mexican, Chinese, Vietnamese or perhaps Indian food, because they come from an area with a lot of Mexican, Chinese, Vietnamese or Indian restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently my partner and I experienced a very direct and clear example of whiteclaiming. We met with a new friend for beers at a local tap room. As our new friend, a thoroughly urbane and frighteningly pale, graduate student whom we shall call Sarah, sat down she aksed about our evening so far. When mentioned that we grabbed some food at the Mexican American food restaurant across the street and she asked “But was it Good Mexican food?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My infinitely patient non-white partner who is also the son of Mexican American Immigrants (Yes documented immigrants and that question is a bigoted micro-aggression). Replied that it was solid so-cal Mex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And she went on to explain with earnest insistence, “Well I’m from the Central Valley of California so I really know Mexican food”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My boyfriend deserves an award his poise and self control as he did not reply, as I might have, “Well my abuela wasn’t in the back cooking but the tortillas were fresh,” rather he went on to politely guide our obtuse, white friend into a more neutral discussion about central California geography. I was really surprised that the entire interaction didn’t turn confrontational. Later that night after we saw Sarah to the bus stop. I brought it up as soon as she was out of earshot.  I was shocked and outraged at her condescension in the specific way that white girlfriends are when they are presented with the everyday expressions of white privilege we never noticed until we’re in an “inter-racial” relationship.  He had noticed it too and found it offensive but it wasn’t deal breaker offensive. Sometimes he just wants to have a pleasant evening and get to know a new person without having to explain to that person that her very outlook on life is predicated on assumptions she is only able to make because being a white person lets her walk around unchallenged most of the time. It was more shocking me than it was to him because the behavior is so familiar to him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being the well meaning white person that I am I can’t just let that sit. It’s incumbent upon me to use whatever platform up and tell some other white people to stop doing this shit. So fellow white people please stop whiteclaiming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom How is this an expression of white privilege or a micro-aggression or whatever you snowflakes call these things?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, my dear white person, if you lived near volcano would you claim to know all about volcanoes? Sure, you would be aware of the volcano and you know what it looks like, you might have personal stories about rumblings and ash falls but would you sit across from a known volcanologist and claim that scientific credentials? Likely, if you had any sense of self awareness you would not. Thusly growing up near Chinatown no more make you a sino-cultural anthropologist than growing up in Vancouver Washington makes you a volcanologist. So what is it about being a white person and having some tertiary experience of another culture that makes us feel like we have a form of special knowledge? Let’s just sit with that question for a while especially if it makes us feel uncomfortable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom this sounds like Whitesplaining Don’t you Mean “Whitesplaining”:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good question fellow white person. The most precise definition I can find for white splaining is in the Wiki Dictionary:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;whitesplain (third-person singular simple present whitesplains, present participle whitesplaining, simple past and past participle whitesplained)
(colloquial, derogatory, chiefly Internet) To explain (something) condescendingly to one who is not white, especially regarding race relations or minority behavior, presuming the listener&amp;rsquo;s inferior understanding because of their race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While whitesplaining is a good frame of reference for understanding whiteclaiming, I have coined the term, to call attention, more precisely, to the ways in which white people will use relational, geographic or other forms of proximity to claim expertise. I expect this may seem obvious to persons of color. And one or more person of color may have already coined a phrase for this phenomenon but I haven’t seen it nor found anything in my searches that captures this particular expression of white privilege. I have noticed that its one of the forms of racist dialogue that white people participate in most often around other white people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Stumped Mom this isn’t fair! Can’t I talk about other cultures and other cultural experiences?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course you can.  And you can do it without sounding like a total blowhard. They key is to qualify your statements. For instance. Our sweet, palid Sarah could have said, “I loved eating at the Cal-Mex restaurants in the central valley where I grew up, how would you say this place rates?”  The difference might seem subtle but by being more specific about her experience and expressing curiosity about other, this version of sarah is being humble and genuine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a parent I find it is always more effective to correct a behavior by focusing on replacing it rather than eliminating it. When you meet a person of color and you want to talk to them about your understanding of their culture, try treating them like you would an acclaimed volcanologist. Share specific experiences and ask them contextualized questions in ways that recognize them as the authority on the subject. In time you might find that this increases your understanding and maybe even helps you diversify your social circle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stumped Mom&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>